[{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "To help keep our community safe and trusted, we\u2019ve published Standards and Expectations for all of our hosts and travelers.  We developed these standards based on our extensive experience interacting with members of the Airbnb community.  These standards are intended to gather together our existing policies into a single framework that will help members of the Airbnb community better understand what to expect from us and what we expect of them. How will the standards be enforced? Each enforcement decision is the result of careful and detailed work by a team of experts devoted to ensuring we make the right call. Our responses to violations of these policies have been and will continue to be based on the seriousness of the issue. We will strive to take the circumstances of each situation into account when reaching our enforcement decision, but we have limited discretion in our response to serious violations of the policies. What can I do if I disagree with a decision? Our enforcement teams are made up of dedicated professionals, but they\u2019re still human.  So, in rare cases, enforcement decisions may be incorrect. If you disagree with a decision we\u2019ve made, you can contact us and we\u2019ll re-review the decision carefully. The definitions of the standards and expectations themselves aren\u2019t subject to review. Will the standards change over time? We\u2019re always learning and growing and the standards and expectations will evolve over time. Make sure to review the standards if you have any questions about a particular situation.", "question": "Standards & Expectations"},
{"answer": "Reviews are a way for Airbnb guests and hosts to share their experiences with the community. Any attempt to use reviews to force a user to do something they aren\u2019t obligated to do is a misuse of reviews, and we don\u2019t allow it. This also means that: Guests are not allowed to threaten to use reviews or ratings in an attempt to force a host to provide refunds, additional compensation, or a reciprocal positive review. Hosts are not allowed to require a guest to leave a positive review or rating, or to revise a review in exchange for a partial or full refund, or reciprocal review. The host also cannot offer a free or discounted stay in exchange for a guest revising an existing review. If a guest contacts a host with a problem, the host should make every effort to resolve it. The host can't ask the guest to take specific actions related to a review in exchange for the resolution of the problem. After the issue is fixed, a host may ask the guest to leave a positive review or rating. A host may also ask a guest to revise a negative review provided certain time constraints are met.  Whether you're a guest or host, make sure you follow these guidelines. If you don't, your account may be restricted, suspended, or terminated. By posting a review, you agree to follow the Airbnb guidelines and policies that Airbnb may enforce at our sole discretion. If you think you've experienced extortion, please contact us.", "question": "Extortion Policy"},
{"answer": "The Community Center is a place to connect with other hosts, share stories, ask for advice, and get updates from the Airbnb team. You can also plan or join meetups. Getting started Here are a few of the features the Community Center offers:    Conversations: Ask a question, share a story, or connect with other hosts by starting a conversation\u2014or joining in on an existing one. Tags: Add topic tags to your conversations to help people find and follow them. We\u2019ll show trending topics on the Community Center homepage. You can also follow a topic to get updates whenever new content is posted. Top contributors: We\u2019re so lucky to have a vibrant and active community of hosts, and we want to make sure your amazing contributions to the community get recognized\u2014that\u2019s why you\u2019ll see a Top Contributors section on the homepage. New to hosting? Use this section to find a community expert. Direct messaging: Want to ask another host a private question? You can now direct message other community members right from the Community Center. Meetups: Meetups are a great way to meet other hosts, share best practices, and get advice from people like you. Over 12,000 meetups have been organized by hosts in 85 cities around the world.    Available languages The Community Center is available in English, French, Italian, German, Spanish, Brazilian Portuguese, Korean, Dutch, and Japanese. We plan to offer support more languages soon.   Cities Cities boards are location-specific boards you can use to connect with other hosts in your area. You can view any Cities board to connect with hosts in that area. Don\u2019t see your city yet? Use the Where in the world? board to start a location-specific conversation. You can use tags to help other community members find your post. Managing the Community Center This is your community. You own the discussions, and the Community Center will ultimately rely heavily on your level of engagement.  The Community Center will be largely self-moderated, but you may also see a faces from the Airbnb team around from time to time to to share updates, answer tricky questions, and help keep things clean and safe.  Related Content   Visit the Community Center", "question": "What is the Airbnb Community Center?"},
{"answer": "By posting content on Airbnb, you agree to abide by these guidelines and other Airbnb policies. We reserve the right to remove content, in whole or part, that violates these guidelines or the Airbnb Terms of Service, or for any other reason at our sole discretion.   In the event of repeated or severe violations, we may suspend or permanently deactivate the account(s) in question. Airbnb's determination on whether any specific content is prohibited will be final and conclusive.   You can contact us or flag Group posts to report content that violates our Terms of Service or Content Guidelines.  Listings and Profiles   We expect Hosts to create listings that are honest, clear, and helpful to potential guests. We prohibit:        Advertising or other commercial content.     Content that endorses or promotes illegal or harmful activity or violence, or is profane, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, threatening, or discriminatory.     Political, religious, or social commentary.     Attempts to impersonate another person.     Content that is fraudulent, false, misleading or deceptive.     Content that refers to an Airbnb investigation.     Content that violates another person or entity\u2019s rights, including intellectual property rights and privacy rights.    Reviews and Neighborhood Feedback   Genuine reviews are the cornerstone of our community. We prohibit:        Reviews that do not represent users\u2019 personal experience.     Reviews unrelated to the actual reservation (ex: political, religious, or social commentary).     Content that endorses or promotes illegal or harmful activity or violence, or is profane, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, threatening, or discriminatory.     Content that violates another person or entity\u2019s rights, including intellectual property rights and privacy rights (ex: publishing another person\u2019s full name, address or other identifying information without permission).     Content that is proven to be used as extortion.     Content that refers to an Airbnb investigation.    Groups   Airbnb Groups are a way for people around the world to connect and build community. When you create a Group, you are responsible for determining its membership. You may accept or remove members at your discretion. In addition, we prohibit:        Advertising or other commercial content (ex: advertising for your business). Discussions or posts unrelated to Airbnb community building (ex: Groups devoted to investing or building a property management business).     Content that endorses or promotes illegal or harmful activity or violence, or is profane, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, threatening, or discriminatory.     Political, religious, or social commentary.     Attempts to impersonate another person.     Content that refers to an Airbnb investigation.     Content that violates another person or entity\u2019s rights, including intellectual property rights and privacy rights. For example, sometimes people use Groups to create local meetups. In these circumstances, please make sure to get permission before publishing another person\u2019s real name or other identifying information.", "question": "Content Policy"},
{"answer": "It's important for U.S. hosts to understand their responsibilities under the Fair Housing Act (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). We've included some useful information and resources below.                 The Fair Housing Act (FHA)       The Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA)       Improper Discriminatory Practices       Service Animals       State and Local Laws            The Fair Housing Act (FHA)              The FHA prohibits housing providers from discriminating against applicants or residents because of race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability, and familial status\u2014including children under the age of 18 staying with parents or legal custodians and pregnant women\u2014in most housing related transactions, with a few limited exceptions.                   The FHA also makes it unlawful to advertise any preference, limitation, or discrimination based on these categories. One type of disability discrimination prohibited by the FHA is the refusal \"to make reasonable accommodations in rules, policies, practices, or services, when such accommodations may be necessary to afford person(s) [with disabilities] equal opportunity to use and enjoy a dwelling.\"                   Additionally, the FHA prohibits housing providers from treating persons less favorably than others because of their disability, refusing residency to persons with disabilities, or placing conditions on their residency, because those persons may require reasonable accommodations, and the FHA requires that new covered multifamily housing be designed and constructed to be accessible. The FHA also prohibits harassment of anyone exercising a fair housing right and retaliation against an individual because he or she has assisted\u2014or participated in any manner\u2014in a fair housing investigation.          Does the FHA apply to me as a host?              The FHA does not apply to all hosts. The FHA contains exemptions for owner-occupied buildings with no more than four units, single-family housing rented without the use of a broker if the private individual owner doesn\u2019t own more than three such single-family units at one time, and housing operated by organizations and private clubs that limit occupancy to members and so long as all advertising is nondiscriminatory. There is also a bed-and-breakfast or rooming house exemption for properties \"containing living quarters occupied or intended to be occupied by no more than four families living independently of each other, if the owner actually maintains and occupies one of such living quarters as his or her residence\" which might apply to some hosts' listings.                   The FHA also specifically exempts some senior housing facilities and communities from liability for discrimination based on familial status. To qualify for this exemption, such housing must be intended and operated for occupancy by persons 55 years of age or older or intended for and solely occupied by persons 62 years of age or older. This \"housing for older persons\" exemption does protect against liability for housing discrimination based on race, color, religion, gender, disability or national origin.                   However, even if you\u2019re exempt from complying with the FHA, it is still illegal to advertise or make any statement that indicates a limitation or preference based on race, color, national origin, religion, sex, familial status, or handicap. This prohibition against discriminatory advertising applies to single-family and owner-occupied housing that is otherwise exempt from the FHA. More information can be found at 24 C.F.R. pt. 100.                   Even if the FHA does not apply to you, we expect our hosts to conduct themselves in a respectful manner and work to bridge differences and make accommodations where possible. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe.              Under the FHA, may I exclude people with children?              If the FHA applies to you, in most instances, you may not exclude children. More information on this exemption can be found at 24 C.F.R. pt. 100, subpart E.               Back to Top               The Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA)              The ADA prohibits discrimination on the basis of disability by places of public accommodation and places of public accommodation must comply with basic nondiscrimination requirements that prohibit exclusion, segregation, and unequal treatment. They also must comply with specific requirements related to architectural standards for new and altered buildings; reasonable modifications to policies, practices, and procedures; effective communication with people with hearing, vision, or speech disabilities; and other access requirements. Additionally, public accommodations must remove barriers in existing buildings where it is easy to do so without much difficulty or expense, given the public accommodation's resources. To be protected under the ADA, an individual must have a disability or have a relationship or association with an individual with a disability.          Does the ADA apply to me as a host?              The ADA does not apply to all hosts. In most cases, the ADA does not apply to residential housing. As a host, you\u2019re subject to the provisions of the ADA if your listing fits its criteria for a \"place of public accommodation.\" Federal regulations (28 C.F.R. \u00a7 36.104) define a place of public accommodation to include a place of lodging, except for an establishment located within a facility that contains not more than five rooms for rent or hire and that actually is occupied by the proprietor of the establishment as the residence of the proprietor.               This means that if you are a host renting out five or fewer rooms, the ADA does not likely apply to you. However, you should review the law and additional information regarding the definition of a \u201cplace of lodging\u201d at 28 C.F.R. \u00a7 36.104.                   Even if the ADA does not apply to you, we expect our hosts to conduct themselves in a respectful manner and work to bridge differences and make accommodations where possible. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe.          Back to Top          Improper Discriminatory Practices              Any of the following actions are discriminatory if they are based on a person's race, color, religion, sex, handicap, familial status, or national origin:                   Refusing to rent, or applying more burdensome criteria to certain guests         Misrepresenting the availability of a unit         Discriminating in choosing guests         Limiting the use of common facilities         Failing to provide the same level of service, or adding extra fees or payments         Denying a request for a reasonable accommodation         Threatening, coercing, intimidating or interfering with anyone exercising a fair housing right or assisting others who exercise that right                   Bear in mind this list is not exhaustive.          Back to Top          Service Animals     What is a service animal?              You must accept service animals if the ADA or FHA applies to your listing. A service animal, in short, is a guide dog, signal dog, or other animal individually trained to provide assistance to an individual with a disability. If they meet this definition, animals are considered service animals under the ADA regardless of whether they have been licensed or certified by a state or local government. Some, but not all, service animals wear special collars and harnesses. Some, but not all, are licensed or certified and have identification papers.                   Remember that even if the ADA or FHA do not apply to you, there may be additional (broader) state laws that do.          I have a clear \"no pets\" policy. Do I still have to allow service animals?              If the ADA or FHA applies to you, yes. A service animal is not a pet. The ADA requires you to modify your no-pets policy to allow the use of a service animal by a person with a disability.          May I charge a special maintenance or cleaning fee for guests who bring service animals?              If the ADA or FHA applies to you, no. You may charge guests with disabilities if a service animal causes damage, so long as it is the regular practice to charge non-disabled customers for the same types of damages.          Am I responsible for the service animal while the person with a disability is my guest? What if the animal is threatening?              No. The care or supervision of a service animal is solely the responsibility of his or her owner. You\u2019re not required to provide care or food or a special location for the animal. You may exclude any animal, including a service animal, when that animal's behavior poses a direct threat to the health or safety of others.          Do I have to accept guests with service animals even if I am allergic, or animals are prohibited in my building, etc.?              If you\u2019re covered by the ADA or the FHA, you may be required to accept service animals or assistance animals, no matter your building\u2019s policy or your allergies.          Back to Top              State and Local Laws              While the FHA and ADA\u2014which are federal laws\u2014provide for minimum requirements, you may also be subject to additional and more stringent local laws that prohibit discrimination. Many states and local communities have passed anti-discrimination ordinances and statutes, and renters\u2019 rights vary greatly from state to state. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing(s).          Back to Top", "question": "ADA and FHA Compliance Policy"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.    Related Articles              Where can I find my VAT invoice?      What are the service fees?", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "To verify your phone number:    Go to Profile on airbnb.com.   Next to Phone Number, click Add a phone number.   Use the drop-down menu to select your country, and we\u2019ll automatically insert the right country code.   Enter your area code and phone number.   Click Verify via SMS or Verify via Call. We'll send you a 4-digit code via text message (SMS) or an automated phone call.   Enter your code and click Verify  If you don\u2019t see a confirmation message, try refreshing the page. If the method you chose isn't working, try the other one.  After verifying your phone number, you can manage text message notifications by going to Account and choosing Notifications on the left. As always, standard message and data rates may apply for any calls or messages sent or received. For questions about these rates, get in touch with your phone provider.   Why verify? Having a verified phone number gives your hosts, guests, and Airbnb a way to contact you about your reservations or your account. Hosts are required to verify their phone numbers before listing their homes, and guests must have a verified phone number before booking a reservation. You also need a verified phone number to complete Verified ID.", "question": "How do I verify my phone number?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "As a US company processing payments, we're required by US law to collect taxpayer information from hosts who appear to have US-sourced income. To add your taxpayer information, go to your Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form. It only takes a minute or two!  Even if you're not a US person and have no US listings, we may be required to collect certain documentation from you to find out if your earnings through Airbnb are subject to US tax.  Depending on your tax status, total earnings for the year, and number of reservations, we may provide you with a tax form showing your earnings.  Whether or not you receive a form from us, it remains your responsibility to determine what amount to report as taxable income on your US income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax professional if you need advice on reporting your income. One resource for an overview of your US income tax responsibilities and information on how to complete your US income tax return is Ernst and Young\u2019s \"General guidance on the taxation of rental income.\"    Related Content              Where do I find my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?      Should I expect to receive a tax form from Airbnb?", "question": "Why is Airbnb requesting my taxpayer information?"},
{"answer": "Since we\u2019re just getting started in Cuba, we want to offer some extra tips and guidelines to make sure your trip goes as smoothly as possible.         Call us if you need us         If you need anything related to your Cuba trip, call us at one of these numbers:                        888-404-6895 (US toll-free)             305-203-0879 (Miami)             437-888-3133 (Toronto)                    Don\u2019t rely on Internet access          Internet access in Cuba can be sporadic. Consider printing your itinerary, contact numbers and addresses, and any maps you\u2019ll need before leaving.         Enroll in the STEP program         If you\u2019re a US citizen, consider enrolling in the Smart Traveler Enrollment Program (STEP). This will help local embassies and US citizen services provide assistance faster in the unlikely event of a problem.         Know the local emergency numbers         If you have an emergency while in Cuba, dial 106 to get in touch with the local police, fire department, or medical services.         Keep track of currency options and exchange rates         Cuba has two currencies: the CUC, or \"convertible peso\", which is valued similar to the US dollar, and the \"national peso,\u201d or CUP, which is the local currency and is valued much lower. Change money only at banks or at the airport, and make sure you know which currency you\u2019re exchanging to avoid any misunderstandings.         Help your host register your visit         Bed and breakfasts in Cuba are legally required to record every tourist's passport details at check in. Your host won\u2019t need to hold your passport, they\u2019ll only need to copy down a few details. Then they'll need to bring those details to their local immigration office.         Stay in touch with your host         We're new to Cuba, but your host isn't\u2014don't be afraid to ask questions, get directions, or share expectations. Also, be sure to check with your host before bringing visitors to your listing. Many hosts don't accept visitors and, if they do, will need to take down your visitors' passport details as well.", "question": "What are some helpful tips for traveling to Cuba?"},
{"answer": "The Host Guarantee and Host Protection Insurance program are two separate programs that Airbnb offers to help cover hosts in the event of damage or injury. Learn more about the differences between the two below. Host Guarantee     Airbnb's Host Guarantee is designed to protect hosts in rare instance of property damage to their own possessions, unit, or home by a guest staying in the space. The Host Guarantee is not insurance and doesn\u2019t replace your homeowner\u2019s or renter\u2019s insurance.        Learn more about our Host Guarantee.       Host Protection Insurance      The Host Protection Insurance program is insurance, and is designed to cover hosts in the event of third-party claims of bodily injury or property damage. The Host Protection Insurance program is available to hosts regardless their other insurance arrangements, but will only act as primary insurance coverage for incidents related to an Airbnb stay.      Learn more about Host Protection Insurance. Examples of coverage Here's an example to help show how the coverages offered by the Host Guarantee and Host Protection Insurance program differ:  During a stay in a covered country, a guest accidentally breaks the toilet and the host\u2019s bathroom floods. The living room of the neighbor\u2019s apartment also floods. The neighbor or landlord brings a claim against the host for damages to the living room. In this example, damage to the host\u2019s bathroom could be covered by the Host Guarantee, since the property belonged to the host. Damage to the neighbor\u2019s living room could be covered by the Host Protection Insurance program, since a claim is being brought against the host by the neighbor or landlord for liability.    Related Articles   What is Host Protection Insurance? What is the Airbnb Host Guarantee?", "question": "What\u2019s the difference between Airbnb's Host Guarantee and Host Protection Insurance?"},
{"answer": "The Host Protection Insurance program provides primary liability coverage for up to $1,000,000 per occurrence in the event of a third-party claim of bodily injury or property damage related to an Airbnb stay.          This coverage is subject to a $1,000,000 cap per listing location, and certain conditions, limitations, and exclusions may apply. Review the list of the covered countries. The Host Protection Insurance program will only act as the primary insurance coverage for incidents related to an Airbnb stay, but it's available to hosts regardless of their other insurance arrangements. Here are some examples of what the Host Protection Insurance program should cover:  A guest breaks their wrist after slipping on the rug and brings a claim for the injury against the host. A guest is working out on the treadmill in the gym of the apartment building. The treadmill breaks and the guest is injured when they fall off. They bring a claim for the injury against the host and the landlord. A guest accidentally drops their suitcase on a third party's foot in the building lobby. The third party brings a claim for the injury against the host and the landlord of the host\u2019s building. Some examples of what the Host Protection Insurance program doesn\u2019t cover:  Intentional acts where liability isn\u2019t the result of an accident. Accusations of slander or defamation of character. Property issues (ex: mold, bed bugs, asbestos, pollution). Auto accidents (ex: vehicle collisions).  For now, this policy only applies to hosts in covered countries. We\u2019re working hard to expand this and other programs to hosts around the world. You can find the list of the covered countries at www.airbnb.com/host-protection-insurance. Download a summary of the program.                        Related Articles   What\u2019s the difference between Host Protection Insurance and the Host Guarantee? How does homeowner's insurance work with Airbnb?", "question": "What is Host Protection Insurance?"},
{"answer": "Being a host comes with certain responsibilities. Here are some resources to help support you along the way.         Interact smartly         Always pay and communicate on Airbnb. Use Airbnb\u2019s messaging system to get to know your guests and share expectations about the trip or your space.                  Read profiles and reviews of your potential guests, and look for verified phone numbers, connected social networks, and references. If potential guests don\u2019t have any profile verifications, you can ask them to complete some.         Trust your intuition: If you don\u2019t feel right about a reservation, don\u2019t accept it!         Fill out your House Rules, Home Safety Card, and House Manual         Completing your house rules and house manual helps guests know what to expect. Include anything you\u2019d like people to know before they book\u2014for example, whether (or where) smoking is allowed, whether certain areas are off-limits, your Wi-Fi password, or if guests should take off their shoes before coming inside.                  If a guest encounters an urgent or emergency situation, it's important they know who to call, what, and where to go. To help make this information clear and easy to display, all hosts will see the option to fill out a safety card online in the Home Safety tab of their listings. This card includes important information that hosts can provide guests, like emergency phone numbers, locations of fire extinguishers and fire alarms, and emergency exit routes. If a disaster affects your area and you\u2019d like to help, you can list your space for free.         Make sure you're insured         Airbnb's Host Protection Insurance program provides primary liability coverage for up to $1,000,000 per occurrence in the event of a third-party claim of bodily injury or property damage related to an Airbnb stay. Learn more.                  You may also want to talk to your insurance provider about adding an extra layer of protection with your own renter\u2019s or homeowner\u2019s insurance.         Set requirements for your listing         You can require guests to complete certain verifications before they book, such as Verified ID.                  Adding a security deposit to your listing can also help protect you in the event of an accident, like spilled wine on a rug.                  Read Airbnb\u2019s Responsible Hosting page         We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. Hosting offers rich experiences, but it requires commitment.                                  Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "I'm a host. What are some safety tips I can follow?"},
{"answer": "To submit a Host Guarantee payment request, read through the terms and conditions of the Host Guarantee (www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee), then contact your guest to notify them of your complaint\u2014often hosts and guests resolve issues on their own via our Resolution Center.  If you and your guest aren't able to come to an agreement, update your case in the Resolution Center accordingly. Gather as much documentation as possible to submit to Airbnb, including photos, receipts, a police report, and any other documentation that proves ownership, damage, or estimates the fair market value of items damaged.  In the very rare occasion of malicious damages or damages involving any kind of illegal activity, please also file a police report with your local authorities. We'll ask you to provide Airbnb with an official copy of the report, so please be sure to ask for a paper copy for your records.  You must submit the request either 14 days from the guests check out or before the next guest checks in, whichever is earlier. For payment requests submitted on time, well send a confirmation email and follow-up emails to discuss next steps. Once we receive sufficient information from both the host and the guest, well review all documentation and evaluate the payment request. The length of the process will vary depending on the severity of the case, the quality of documentation, and the cooperation of the host and guest.                          Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "How do I submit a Host Guarantee payment request?"},
{"answer": "The Airbnb Host Guarantee provides protection for up to $1,000,000 to a host for damages to covered property in the rare event of guest damages above the security deposit\u2014or if no security deposit is in place. The Host Guarantee Program doesn't cover cash and securities, collectibles, rare artwork, jewelry, pets or personal liability. We recommend that hosts secure or remove valuables when renting their place. The program also doesn't cover loss or damage to property due to wear and tear. For these types of incidents, hosts can add a security deposit in their pricing settings. The Host Guarantee Program isn't insurance and doesn't replace your homeowners or renters insurance. Make sure you review and understand the terms of your insurance policy and what it covers and doesn't cover. Not all insurance will cover damage or loss to property caused by a guest renting your space. Filing a host guarantee request doesn't preclude a guest from financial responsibility for the damages claimed if Airbnb determines a guest was at fault. Learn more about the Host Guarantee at: www.airbnb.com/guarantee.  View the Host Guarantee terms and conditions at: www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee. If you can't view this page, the country you're accessing Airbnb from doesn't have Host Guarantee coverage right now.", "question": "What is the Airbnb Host Guarantee?"},
{"answer": "Business Travel Ready hosts must provide 24-hour access to the listing for the duration of a guest\u2019s stay\u2014this starts with check-in. 24-hour check-in means that your guest should be able to check in at any time after the check-in time you set for your listing on their arrival date. 24-hour check-in could be something like a lockbox, a doorman, a buzzer, or keyless entry.", "question": "What is 24-hour check-in?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "Business Travel Ready listings must be an Entire Home/Apt and an eligible property type (house, apartment, bed &amp; breakfast, townhouse, loft, or condo). The listing must be no smoking, and can\u2019t have pets on the property. The space Many business travelers are new to traveling on Airbnb, so we\u2019ve limited Business Travel Ready listings to certain property types to help make sure guests know what to expect when they arrive. As a part of this, and because of the potential for allergies and other sensitivities, we also ask that Business Travel Ready listings are smoke-free properties and don\u2019t have pets living in the space while the guest is there. If a pet lives in your space, but won\u2019t be there during your guest\u2019s stay we ask that you\u2019re aware of traveler\u2019s potential allergens and make sure your listing is cleaned before your guest\u2019s arrival. Amenities The listing must also have the following Business Travel Ready amenities:   Wireless Internet A laptop-friendly workspace 24-hour check-in (this could be a lockbox, doorman, keyless entry or similar 24-hour access) A smoke detector A carbon monoxide detector Essentials (toilet paper, clean towels, and fresh linens) An iron Hangers A hair dryer Shampoo  Smoke and carbon monoxide detectors are an important part of making Airbnb a trusted travel option for companies. As part of our commitment to guest safety, Airbnb offers free smoke and carbon monoxide detectors for hosts: www.airbnb.com/home-safety. Reviews and response rate Listings must have at least 3 star rated reviews before they can be eligible for Business Travel Ready status. For listings with 3 or more star rated reviews, at least 60% of both the listing\u2019s primary reviews, and the listing\u2019s reviews for cleanliness and accuracy must be 5 star reviews. Hosts of Business Travel Ready listings also must have responded to 90% of booking requests within 24 hours over the last year. Cancellations Hosts of Business Travel Ready listings must provide a 7-day cancellation commitment to reservations. If a listing has a cancellation within 7 days of a confirmed check-in date, it can't be considered for Business Travel Ready for 1 year from the cancellation date. Eligibility Listings and their hosts are evaluated for business travel readiness on a rolling basis. Keep in mind that you and your listing need to continue to qualify after the initial evaluation in order to maintain Business Travel Ready status. If you\u2019re a host, learn more or get started now. Questions? Review the Business Travel Ready Terms &amp; Conditions.", "question": "What makes a listing Business Travel Ready?"},
{"answer": "No. We\u2019ve made it easy to manage your company\u2019s business travel by adding a specialized dashboard that you can access from your personal Airbnb account. From the dashboard, you can view active or upcoming trips, itinerary details, and financial reporting. To access the dashboard:    Hover over your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com. Select Business Travel You\u2019ll need to link your work email address to your account and be added as a travel manager before you can access this dashboard. If your company isn\u2019t enrolled in Airbnb for Business yet, learn how to enroll.  Related Articles   I'm a travel manager. How do I get started with Airbnb for Business? How do I use my travel manager account?", "question": "Do I need to create a new Airbnb account to manage my company's travel?"},
{"answer": "Business guests can identify a reservation as a business trip by selecting Business travel on the checkout page. Any notes you add in the What\u2019s the purpose of this trip? box will be sent your company\u2019s travel manager. Choosing Business travel won\u2019t tell your host that you\u2019re traveling for work, but sharing information about your trip in a message to your host is a great way to help them understand your business travel needs. Already booked your trip? You can identify your reservation as a business trip at any time from your itinerary. Scroll down and select the checkbox next to This is a business trip in the Business Travel section.", "question": "How do I identify a reservation as a business trip?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb for Business makes it easy to travel for work without sacrificing the comforts of home. If you manage your company's travel read on to learn more about:           How do I enroll my company?        How do I set up my company's account?        I already have a personal Airbnb account, do I need to set up a new one to manage my company's travel?        How do I add or remove an employee from my company's account?        How do I add another travel manager?                     How do I enroll my company? To enroll your company, go to airbnb.com/business/signup. After filling out the necessary information, you\u2019ll be asked to verify your email address before setting up your company\u2019s account.   How do I set up my company's account? We\u2019ll walk you through the steps to set up your company\u2019s account after you confirm your email address. You'll start by:      Inviting your employees to the program. You can add individual email addresses or upload them in bulk.   Adding your company\u2019s credit card. This gives your employees an easy way to pay for their Airbnb trip.  I already have a personal Airbnb account, do I need to set up a new one to manage my company's travel? No. We\u2019ve made it easy to manage your company\u2019s travel by adding a specialized travel manager dashboard\u2014which you'll be able to use from your existing Airbnb account. From this dashboard, you can invite employees, view active or upcoming trips, see itinerary details, and more. To access your travel manager dashboard, go to airbnb.com/business/dashboard How do I add or remove an employee from my company's account? To add a traveler, go to People  and click Invite New Travelers. To remove a traveler:   Go to the People section of your dashboard   In the Travelers tab, click X next to the traveler you'd like to remove  How do I add a travel manager or booker? To add a travel manager or booker:  Go to the People section of your dashboard   Click Add People   Choose a role under Select a role, then add the person's email address below   Click Add People to save", "question": "I'm a travel manager. How do I get started with Airbnb for Business?"},
{"answer": "Viewing your dashboard   Once you\u2019re logged in, visit your travel manager dashboard at airbnb.com/business/dashboard. This dashboard split up into 4 main sections: Activity, Reporting, People, and Settings.        Activity: Use the Activity section to see an overview of employee\u2019s active and upcoming trips. For each trip you\u2019ll see traveler name, destination, booking and trip dates, and number of guests.     Reporting: Use the Reporting section to see details about number of nights booked, total amount spent, and average daily rate across your company. You can also export CSV reports from this page.     People: Use the People section to view and manage the employee accounts that are linked to your company. You can also view, add, or remove travel managers from this page.     Settings: Use the  Settings section of your dashboard to edit your company\u2019s info, update your payment settings, change who can join your company\u2019s account, and add or update your email alert settings.", "question": "How do I use my travel manager account?"},
{"answer": "Travel managers can create groups of travelers (ex: departments, office locations) and assign a name and payment method to each group from the travel manager dashboard. Travelers will then have the option to \"Charge to\" that group when they book a business trip through Airbnb. Adding or editing a group   To create a new group:            Go to your Business Travel dashboard       Click People &gt; Groups       Click Create Group       Add a group name and select a payment method for the group       Click Save           Travelers will see the group name you choose when they bill business travel to the company (ex: Charge to Sales, Charge to North America Office).   To add employees to a group:            Go to Groups and click the group you want to edit       Click Add Members and select or search for employees by name       Click Save       To edit an existing group\u2019s payment info:            Go to Groups and click the group you want to edit      Click Change Payment Method      Under Payment Method select an existing credit card or choose Add Credit Card      Add payments details and click Save       You won't be able to switch from payment by credit card to monthly invoicing or vice versa. If you want to switch a group's payment type from credit card to monthly invoicing, you'll need to delete and re-create the group. Deleting a group   To delete a group:            Go to Groups and click the group you want to edit       Click Edit Group       Click Delete This Group, then click Save", "question": "How do I set up payment groups for my company?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb for Business makes it easy to travel for work without sacrificing the comforts of home.  Business travelers If your company is already enrolled in Airbnb for Business, join their account by visiting airbnb.com/business-travel. Business Travel Ready listings Some homes have a badge to indicate that they\u2019re Business Travel Ready. These listings meet certain requirements for home type, amenities, check-in, reviews, responsiveness, and host commitment\u2014you\u2019ll see them identified with a briefcase . Travel managers For travel managers, the Airbnb for Business program provides better transparency and more accurate reporting for their company. If you manage your company's travel arrangements, sign your company up for Airbnb for Business by visiting airbnb.com/business/signup. Once you\u2019re enrolled, learn more about using your travel manager account and dashboard.  Related Articles   I'm a travel manager. How do I get started with Airbnb for Business? How do I join my company's business travel account?", "question": "What is Airbnb for Business?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb\u2019s Host Protection Insurance will act as primary insurance and provides liability coverage to hosts and, where applicable, their landlords, subject to certain conditions, limitations, and exclusions.  If you have questions about how this policy interacts with any homeowner\u2019s or renter\u2019s insurance, you should discuss your coverage with your insurance provider. Some policies protect homeowners and renters from certain lawsuits that result from injury to a visitor, while others do not.  It\u2019s always a good idea to let your insurance carrier know about rental activity in your space even though liability arising during an Airbnb stay should be covered by the Host Protection Insurance policy.   For further guidance, refer to our Responsible Hosting page.", "question": "How does homeowner's insurance work with Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We strongly encourage all hosts to install smoke and CO detectors in their listings, but we don't require hosts to show proof that they have these devices in their space right now. If you don't have a smoke or CO detector installed, you should mention this in your listing\u2019s description.           If you're a host and already have these devices installed, update your listing description to let your guests know you have this important amenity installed.             Having working smoke and carbon monoxide (CO) detectors in your home can make a big difference. To help you get started, we're giving away one free combination smoke and carbon monoxide detector to the first 25,000 eligible hosts who request one through December 31, 2016. Read more about this offer.        Be sure to check you local regulations, which may require that you have more than one working smoke and carbon monoxide detector installed in your listing\u2014for example, some cities require one in every room.", "question": "I'm a host. Am I required to have a smoke and CO detector installed?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Your safety and comfort are always a priority. If you find that a guest isn't a fit for your space or hosting style, you can decline their reservation request or cancel the reservation.          Before you've accepted a reservation          We encourage you to take advantage of the safety features we've built to help give you peace of mind and help you get to know potential guests.          Declining an individual reservation request won't negatively impact your listing's placement in search results\u2014however, if you decline many or most reservation requests, your search result placement may be negatively impacted.     After you've accepted a reservation          If you've already accepted the reservation, you can cancel it. You may be subject to cancellation penalties.          You won't be eligible for Superhost status if you cancel a confirmed reservation\u2014unless it\u2019s under extenuating circumstances.          Flagging inappropriate messages                  If a message from a guest makes you uncomfortable, let us know by flagging it. To flag a message, open the message thread and click the flag icon  next to the message you want to flag to Airbnb for review.                              Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "What should I do if I'm uncomfortable hosting someone?"},
{"answer": "Through awareness and a few simple tools, we'd like to help hosts make their homes safer and put guests more at ease.  Emergency safety cards If a guest encounters an urgent or emergency situation, it's important they know who to call, what, and where to go. To help make this information clear and easy to display, all hosts will see the option to fill out a safety card online in the Home Safety tab of each listing. This card includes important information that hosts can provide guests, like emergency phone numbers, locations of fire extinguishers and fire alarms, and emergency exit routes. After you fill out the card online, guests will be able to see it after they book a reservation at your listing. You\u2019ll also be able to easily print the card and display it in your space. Smoke and carbon monoxide detectors We\u2019re encouraging all Airbnb hosts to install working smoke and carbon monoxide detectors in their homes. To help achieve this goal, the first 25,000 eligible hosts who request a detector through December 31, 2016 will get one for free. Terms, Conditions and Restrictions apply. Please check your local laws for any applicable requirements for where to put the detector(s) in your space. While we encourage hosts to install smoke and carbon monoxide detectors in their space, at this time, we don't require confirmation that they've been installed. If you don't indicate you have these devices by selecting the \u201csmoke detector\u201d and/or \u201ccarbon monoxide detector\u201d amenities in your listing description, guests will see those amenities crossed-out when they view your listing. For more information, visit our Home Safety page: www.airbnb.com/home-safety", "question": "What is Airbnb doing to help hosts make their homes safer for guests?"},
{"answer": "Here are some tips to help you travel with confidence.         Read carefully             Look at the profiles and reviews of potential hosts before you book, and check for verified phone numbers, connected social networks, and references. If you'd like to see more, you can always ask them to complete profile verifications before booking with them, or look for hosts who already have a strong reputation on Airbnb.             It's also a good idea to read everything the host has posted about their listing in the description, the amenities, and the house rules so there won\u2019t be any surprises. Make sure you understand the host's cancellation policy before submitting a reservation request, too.         Pay and communicate on Airbnb                          Paying or communicating outside Airbnb makes it harder for us to protect your information and puts you at greater risk of fraud and other security issues. That's why we prohibit paying for a reservation outside our website in our Terms of Service and strongly encourage you to communicate using our messaging system.         Use our messaging system before a booking to confirm details about specific amenities, ask whether other people share the same space, discuss house rules, and talk about the neighborhood. After booking, use it to discuss check-in details.         Set clear expectations             After learning more about your host\u2019s Airbnb history, start a conversation with them about your plans and what you can expect. Your host will likely know all the great (and not so great) spots. Trust your intuition: if you don\u2019t feel right about a reservation, don\u2019t book it! If a message makes you feel uncomfortable or you need help during your reservation, let us know.         Prepare for the unexpected         Research the neighborhood where you\u2019ll be staying, familiarize yourself with major roads and landmarks, and have a plan for where you\u2019d go in an emergency. If you\u2019re covering long distances in your travels, make sure to tell your friends and family where you\u2019ll be.             For any trip, think about signing up for traveler's insurance. Airbnb doesn't offer traveler\u2019s insurance for guests, but traveler's insurance is a relatively affordable option that can protect you in case of an injury or emergency on a trip. Some policies even cover lost baggage and travel delays. Check with your local insurance provider for details on your options.                         Before booking international travel or traveling internationally, also be sure toconsult the relevant agencies in your government (for example the State Department for US citizens) for any travel warnings or travel advisories that may apply to countries or regions included in your travel plans.          Be a considerate guest             Whether you're still looking for the perfect listing or are already on your way, being a considerate guest matters.                                                 Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "I\u2019m a guest. What are some safety tips I can follow?"},
{"answer": "To ensure a listing has what you\u2019ll need for kids, you can always message the host directly with questions before you book.         Safe Kids Worldwide, a global organization dedicated to preventing child injuries, provides an array of resources on child safety on its website.          This includes a series of simple tips on how to make a home safer for children. Below is a full list of the various home risks Safe Kids Worldwide identifies:                      Batteries             Burns and Scalds             Carbon Monoxide             Choking and Strangulation             Falls             Fire             Guns             Liquid Laundry Packets             Medication             Poison             Sleep Safety and Suffocation             Toy Safety             TV and Furniture Tip-Overs             Water and Drowning                  The safety of our hosts, guests, and any accompanying children is our highest priority. Whether you\u2019re a seasoned traveler or a first time guest, our safety tips will help you along the way.", "question": "I\u2019m traveling with children. What are some safety tips I should consider?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method  Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method    New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:    Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How long does it take a payout method to become ready?       How do I change my taxpayer information?", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "To update your taxpayer information:   Log into airbnb.com from your desktop computer  Go to your Payout Preferences  To the right of your Taxpayer Information, click Options  Select Edit  Don't forget to click Submit after making any changes, and you're all set!    Some fields aren't editable, so if you're trying to change your tax ID number, tax classification, or enter a different taxpayer entirely, please add a new taxpayer. If you\u2019ve added more than one taxpayer, you\u2019ll be able to remove any record that is not your default by clicking Options &gt; Delete.    Related Content               How do I split income between multiple people?", "question": "How do I change my taxpayer information?"},
{"answer": "Whether you\u2019re looking for detailed information on a specific transaction or a static report, you can view your earnings at any time from your Airbnb account.  It's your responsibility to determine what, from your total amount earned, to report as taxable income on your tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance deducting any non-taxable income. Transaction history  You can filter transactions by payout method, listing, and date from your Transaction History. Your transaction history includes completed and future transactions, along with an option to view gross earnings.  Learn more about how to use your transaction history. 2015 earnings summary (US-only) All transactions paid out in the 2015 calendar year are included in your Transaction History &gt; Earnings Summary. All transactions paid out in the 2015 calendar year are a part of the report, including both net and gross earnings. Gross earnings include any withholdings or adjustments that may have reduced payouts throughout the year. These amounts can be useful for income tax reporting purposes.  At this time, your earnings summary is only available for display in USD. If you received payouts in other currencies, your earnings summary will display the exchange rate that was locked in on the date that the transaction took place.     Related Articles              What expenses are deductible from my Airbnb income?           Should I expect to receive a tax form from Airbnb?      How do I split income between multiple people?", "question": "Where do I find my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?"},
{"answer": "It's possible that not all of your income is taxable. Deductible items may include rent, mortgage, cleaning fees, rental commissions, insurance, and other expenses. Other factors you might consider when assessing taxable income include renting vs. owning the space, number of nights hosted, tax status, and total net amount earned (any tax forms issued to you display your total gross earnings).   We encourage you to consult a tax advisor for more details, as there are many special rules in this area and we aren't able to provide tax advice. One resource for an overview of your US income tax responsibilities and information on how to complete your US income tax return is Ernst and Young\u2019s \"General guidance on the taxation of rental income.\"    Disclaimer: Airbnb's presentation of EY is not an endorsement. Tax advice is complicated, and you should do your own diligence when receiving advice. Airbnb is not responsible for any tax or other advice provided by any outside entity.", "question": "What expenses are deductible from my Airbnb income?"},
{"answer": "As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area, and encourage you to consult a tax professional if you need advice on reporting your income. H&amp;R Block will provide a $20 discount on in-person tax preparation services and a 35% discount on online tax preparation services for Airbnb hosts who use the service between January 1, 2016 and April 18, 2016. Visit  hrblock.com/Partner/airbnb to learn more.  Ernst and Young (\u201cEY\u201d) has prepared an overview of tax considerations for Airbnb hosts relating to the US taxation of rental income. This information provides an overview of how to complete your US income tax return as well as some of your tax responsibilities as an Airbnb host. Access EY\u2019s \u201cGeneral guidance on the taxation of rental income\u201d here.   Disclaimer: Airbnb's presentation of EY and H&amp;R Block is not an endorsement. Tax advice is complicated, and you should do your own diligence when receiving advice. Airbnb is not responsible for any tax or other advice provided by any outside entity.     Related Articles              Where do I find my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?      Should I expect to receive a tax form from Airbnb?", "question": "Resources for the 2015 US Tax Season"},
{"answer": "Depending on your account status, forms submitted to Airbnb, and other factors, you may receive a tax form from Airbnb.  As always, we encourage you to consult a tax professional for assistance reporting your income. If you think you've submitted the wrong information, you can make changes to taxpayer information you've already submitted.  Airbnb expects to issue tax forms to the following categories of persons:  US persons who have earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations  The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) requires that all US companies processing payments, including Airbnb, report the gross earnings of US customers that earn over $20,000 and have 200+ transactions in the calendar year. If you cross both IRS thresholds in a calendar year, Airbnb will provide you with a Form 1099-K. Delivery of Form 1099-K   Any Form 1099-K issued to you will be available in your Payout Preferences. You'll receive an email notification when your form is ready, typically in late January of each year. We also mail a copy to the address you provided along with your taxpayer information, unless you opted for electronic delivery only. You may receive more than one Form 1099-K if your taxpayer information is listed on multiple Airbnb accounts.  Non-US persons who have submitted a Form W-8  Hosts with US sourced earnings who have filled out a Form W-8 will be provided a Form 1042-S. Delivery of Form 1042-S You'll receive a Form 1042-S in the mail at the address you entered when you submitted your tax information, typically in late February of each year. The IRS requires that we mail Form 1042-S by the end of March.   Hosts that had funds withheld from their payouts for taxes  If taxes were withheld from your payouts during the calendar year, you\u2019ll be provided with the appropriate tax form so that you may account for the withholdings on your income tax return. Read more about withheld taxes.  Airbnb service providers (photographers, translators, others)  Airbnb service providers, including photographers, translators, and additional service providers, will receive a Form 1099-MISC.  Delivery of Form 1099-MISC Any Form 1099-MISC issued to you will be available in your Payout Preferences. You'll receive an email notification when your form is ready, typically in late January of each year. We also mail a copy to the address you provided along with your taxpayer information, unless you opted for electronic delivery only.     Related Content              Where do I find my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Should I expect to receive a tax form from Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages  Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.  Related Articles   What are profile verifications? What is Verified ID?", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "To see a list of recent logins to your Airbnb account:            Go to Account on airbnb.com       Select Security on the left       Scroll down and look for Login History section          Under Login History, you\u2019ll find a list of logins to your Airbnb account, including information on the type of browser used to access your account, when your account was accessed, and where we believe it was accessed from. You can hover over the  icon in the Recent Activity column to get more information, such as the precise time or IP address of the device used to access your account.     Trusted browsers are included in your login history.", "question": "Can I see a list of recent logins to my Airbnb account?"},
{"answer": "We'll send you an email or text (SMS) alert whenever certain changes are made to your account (ex: updates to your password, email address, payout method). When you receive one of these alerts, make sure it was you who made the change. If you didn't make the change, reset your password and let our team know here.", "question": "My account details changed, but I didn\u2019t update them. What should I do?"},
{"answer": "Using a strong password for your Airbnb account makes it harder for people to gain access your account without your permission. The password you choose should be easy for you to remember, but hard for someone else to figure out.          Create a unique password         Make sure your Airbnb password is different than the passwords you use for other websites, like your email or bank account. That way, if someone figures out your Airbnb password, they won\u2019t be able to use it to access your other accounts (or vice versa).         Change your password often          If someone knows your password, they might be accessing your Airbnb account without you knowing. Changing your password often helps prevent this kind of unauthorized access.         Use at least 8 characters and avoid common phrases         Make sure your password is at least 8 characters long, and try to use a mix of special characters (#, $, &amp;, !, etc.). You should also avoid using common words or phrases in your password, and never include personal information.                   Related Articles   How do I reset my password?", "question": "How can I make my password strong?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb will never ask you to pay off-site or through email. If someone messages you on Airbnb and asks you to contact them off-site to arrange payment details, don't respond, report it to us instead.      Report requests for off-site payment   If a host on the Airbnb site asks you to pay off-site, report it to us by flagging the message\u2014just look for the flag icon  in your message thread.   If you receive a personal email from anyone (including an automated@airbnb.com or any other username@airbnb.com email address) asking you to pay or accept payment off-site, let us know immediately.      You won't receive a paper or PDF invoice from a host or from Airbnb asking you for payment. Any of the following key words and similar terms should be immediately flagged or avoided: Western Union, MoneyGram, cashier's check, money order, Liberty Reserve.      Types of scams Never share your email address before a booking is accepted or transfer funds outside the Airbnb system, and always carefully examine emails claiming to be from Airbnb. Examples of common scams include:  Advance Fee Scam: A type of scam in which an individual offers money or another reward in exchange for you transferring money through various payment services outside of Airbnb.  Phishing Scam: A type of scam in which someone will send an email or link that is made to look like it's from Airbnb or another trusted site. These messages are designed to trick you into providing confidential information\u2014such as passwords or other email addresses\u2014and may contain malware, which is malicious software that gains access to your computer to gather your personal information, including passwords.  Travel Scam: A type of scam in which someone will encourage you to secure your \"too good to be true\" listing by sending payment via wire transfer or with an advanced deposit in order to collect the money without providing the advertised accommodation.  Overpayment Scam: A type of scam in which someone will offer more than what your listing may be worth, and ask you to repay them in cash.  Related Articles   Why should I pay and communicate through Airbnb directly? How can I keep my account secure?", "question": "What should I do if someone asks me to pay outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "We don't share your personal email address even after you have a confirmed reservation. Instead, we create a unique, temporary Airbnb address for you, and share that with your host or guest. Keeping your real personal email address hidden helps protect your privacy, and prevent unwanted communication from people who may abuse our system. Any emails sent to your temporary Airbnb address are forwarded to your personal email address. This lets you use your email provider to send or reply to messages, attach files (up to 15 MB), and include links. A host's anonymized email address might look like: Personal email address: john.lastname@exampleemail.com Temporary Airbnb address: john-abc123xyz@host.airbnb.com A guest's anonymized email address might look like: Personal email address: jane.lastname@exampleemail.com Temporary Airbnb address: jane-def456@guest.airbnb.com  We recommend communicating using the Airbnb messaging system, but we recognize that sometimes you'll need to attach photos, directions, or other information in an email. These addresses let you send emails like your normally would\u2014with an extra layer of security.", "question": "How will my email address look to other people?"},
{"answer": "We remove text from messages when our system detects words or numbers that might include contact information. Communicating or paying outside Airbnb can put you at risk, so we do this to help protect you from potential online fraud.        We ask that you communicate only through the Airbnb message thread until you have a confirmed Airbnb reservation. After a reservation is accepted, the phone number, listing address, and an anonymized version of your email address are automatically shared.        By communicating and booking directly through Airbnb, you\u2019ll have access to our secure payments platform, 24/7 customer support, the Host Guarantee, and the Host Protection Insurance program.", "question": "Why was text removed from my Airbnb message thread?"},
{"answer": "Occasionally, people create fake emails or websites designed to look like Airbnb. These sites can be used to try steal personal information, like your password or bank account info. This is often called phishing or spoofing.         If you receive an email or are directed to a website that looks like Airbnb but asks for confidential information, be cautious. When in doubt, always start at the Airbnb home page. Type https://www.airbnb.com in your browser and go from there.         Check the email address         You can tell if an email is really from Airbnb by looking at what comes after the @ symbol. All official Airbnb emails will come from an address that ends in:                      @airbnb.com                          @airbnbmail.com                          @e.airbnb.com                          @host.airbnb.com                          @guest.airbnb.com                          @airbnb.zendesk.com                          @airbnbaction.com                          @express.medallia.com (learn more about Medallia)                               It's possible for fraudsters to \"spoof\" an email address, so these tips aren't failsafe. If you receive an email that looks like it's from Airbnb, but wasn't sent from one of these addresses, it's very likely fake. Don't click any of its links and delete the email.         Learn to identify fraudulent emails         Fraudulent emails often include the Airbnb logo and a fake Airbnb address in the \"From\" line.         Fraudulent emails might also contain text from real Airbnb emails, such as a reservation confirmation message, payout confirmation, reservation reminder, or a request to update your profile. By making an email seem real, fraudsters hope to trick you into providing personal information that we would never ask for. Here are some signs to help you tell the difference:                                                            Fake Email                     Real Airbnb Email                                                                                                                                       They\u2019re sent from fraudulent email addresses. Examples include john@bnb.com or automated@reservation-airbnb.com.                                                                                                                         They're sent from an address that ends in @airbnb.com, @airbnbmail.com, @e.airbnb.com, @host.airbnb.com, @guest.airbnb.com, @airbnb.zendesk.com, @airbnbaction.com, or @express.medallia.com. If it's not sent from one of these addresses, it\u2019s not from Airbnb.                                                                                                                                                           They often contain links to fake Airbnb web pages that try to steal your information. Don\u2019t click links in any email you\u2019re not sure about.                                                                                                                         They begin with https://www.airbnb.com (or a country-specific URL like https://es.airbnb.com or https://it.airbnb.com). If you click a link that takes you to a page that looks like Airbnb but doesn\u2019t start with this address, it\u2019s a fraudulent page and you should close it.                                                                                                                                                           They often have an urgent tone and threaten account suspension, loss of a reservation or booking, or a delayed payout if you don't click a link or reply with certain information immediately.                                                                                                                         If it\u2019s truly important, you\u2019ll usually find more information in your Airbnb dashboard. If you have any doubt about an email\u2019s authenticity, log in to your account at www.airbnb.com and go from there.                                                                                             Report fake emails to Airbnb       If you think you've received a fake email, forward it to report.phishing@airbnb.com. If possible, forward or send the email as an attachment\u2014this gives us important information that will help us investigate.       This inbox is strictly for reporting suspicious emails or websites, and isn't monitored for urgent issues. If you made a payment outside of Airbnb or are concerned about the security of your account, contact us instead.", "question": "How do I know if an email is really from Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Paying and communicating through Airbnb helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program and other safeguards. It also makes it easy to find and reference important reservation details like a listing's address, your itinerary, check-in details, and other useful information. We can\u2019t provide these benefits if your reservation isn\u2019t booked and paid for directly through Airbnb.       Paying or communicating outside of Airbnb also makes it harder for us to protect your information and puts you at greater risk of fraud and other security issues, such as phishing.     Flag suspicious messages       Never pay for your reservation outside of Airbnb. If someone asks you to pay for a reservation outside our on-site payment system\u2014or you think someone might be sending you links to a fake Airbnb site\u2014let us know and click the flag icon  in your message thread with that person.", "question": "Why should I pay and communicate through Airbnb directly?"},
{"answer": "Review the tips below to learn more about how you can help keep your account and information secure.      If you make a change to sensitive account information, we may send you an account alert or ask you to confirm the change by entering a security code sent to your verified phone number. Password strength Create a password that's at least 8 characters, and contains a unique combination of letters, numbers, and symbols. Don't use the password you create for your Airbnb account for other accounts (ex: your email account). Learn how to update your password. Online security A few general guidelines to help you stay safe online: Always log in at https://www.airbnb.com: Check any page's URL before you enter your login info\u2014when in doubt, you can always type https://www.airbnb.com directly into your browser. Turn browser security alerts on: Many newer browsers have built-in security protection that might be able to warn you if you're about to visit an unsecure website. Install a pop-up blocker and antivirus software: Install a pop-up blocker or antivirus software from a trustworthy source. Remember to run scans for viruses and malware frequently, and keep your antivirus software up-to-date. Check the sender: Don't click any links or download any attachments unless you know and trust the source.  Off-site payments and messages Airbnb will never ask you to pay elsewhere\u2014and we ask that you keep all payment and communication on the Airbnb platform. Don't share your email address before a booking is accepted or transfer funds outside the Airbnb system, and always carefully examine emails claiming to be from Airbnb. If you encounter a suspicious profile, listing, or message thread, flag it for review. If someone emails you asking you to pay or accept payment off-site, let us know right away. Related Articles     What should I do if someone asks me to pay outside of the Airbnb website? Why should I pay and communicate through Airbnb directly?", "question": "How can I keep my account secure?"},
{"answer": "Related article: How does Occupancy Tax Collection and Remittance by Airbnb work?  Currently, Airbnb is collecting and remitting taxes on behalf of the host in the following locations: France Chamonix- Mont-Blanc Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Chamonix-Mont-Blanc will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Tourist Tax: 0.75\u20ac per person per night for the category \"meubl\u00e9s touristiques non class\u00e9s\".  Exemptions may apply to some guests. For detailed information, visit your local city hall's website. If a guest believes they are subject to an exemption, they may reach out to the Municipality.  Paris Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Paris will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Tourist Tax: 0.83 \u20ac per person per night for the category \"meubl\u00e9s touristiques non class\u00e9s\". This amount includes the city-imposed tourist tax and the administrative district tax. Exemptions may apply to some guests. If guests believe they are subject to an exemption, they may reach out to the Municipality. You can find more information here, here and here.  Other cities As of August 1, 2016, guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Ajaccio, Annecy, Antibes, Avignon, Biarritz, Bordeaux, Cannes, La Rochelle, Lille, Lyon, Marseille, Montpellier, Nantes, Nice, Saint-Malo, Strasbourg, or Toulouse will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Tourist Tax: 0.83 \u20ac per person per night for the category \"meubl\u00e9s touristiques non class\u00e9s\". This amount includes the city-imposed tourist tax and the administrative district tax. Exemptions may apply to some guests. If guests believe they are subject to an exemption, they may reach out to the Municipality. You can find more information here, here and here.  India Country of India Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the Country of India will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  India Service Tax: 14.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee, less a 40% abatement. Airbnb is required, as an aggregator, to collect and remit service tax on behalf of Airbnb hosts.For detailed information, visit India\u2019s government website.  Netherlands Amsterdam Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the City of Amsterdam, NL will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Amsterdam Tourist Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee. For detailed information, visit Amsterdam\u2019s government website.  Portugal Lisbon Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Lisbon will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:   Tourist Tax: 1.00 \u20ac per person per night, up to a maximum of 7.00 \u20ac per person. For detailed information, visit the City of Lisbon website.       United States Alabama State of Alabama  Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Alabama will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Alabama State Lodging Tax: 4-5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 179 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Sales and Use Tax at the Alabama Department of Revenue website. County Lodging and Rental Tax collected by the State: 1-6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 179 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Local Sales, Use, Lodgings &amp; Rental Tax Rates at the Alabama Department of Revenue website. Municipality Local Lodging Tax collected by the State: 2-12% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 179 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Local Sales, Use, Lodgings &amp; Rental Tax Rates at the Alabama Department of Revenue website.  Hosts are responsible for collecting any city and county taxes that are not collected by the state. Arizona Phoenix Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Phoenix, AZ will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Phoenix Hotel/Motel Tax: 3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. Phoenix Transaction Privilege (Sales) Tax: 2.3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for all reservations. For detailed information, visit Phoenix.gov.  California    Humboldt County Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in unincorporated Humboldt County, CA (does not include the incorporated cities of Arcata, Blue Lake, Eureka, Ferndale, Fortuna, Rio Dell and Trinidad) will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation  Humboldt County Transient Occupancy Tax: 10% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Humboldt County Tax Collector  website.     Santa Cruz County Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in unincorporated Santa Cruz County, CA (does not include the incorporated cities of Capitola, Santa Cruz, Scotts Valley or Watsonville) will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Transient Occupancy Tax: 11% of the listing price including any cleaning fees for 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, please visit the Santa Cruz County Treasurer website.  Tuolumne County Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Tuolumne County, CA (does not include the incorporated city of Sonora) will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:    Transient Occupancy Tax: 10% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Tuolumne County Transient Occupancy Tax site. Malibu Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Malibu, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Malibu Transient Occupancy Tax: 12% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit MalibuCity.org.   Oakland Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Oakland, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:    Oakland Transient Occupancy Tax: 14% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Oakland's FAQ page.  Palo Alto Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Palo Alto, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Palo Alto Transient Occupancy Tax: 14% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter.  For detailed information, visit CityofPaloAlto.org.  San Diego Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in San Diego, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  San Diego Transient Occupancy Tax: 10.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter.  San Diego Tourism Marketing District Assessment: 0.55% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit SanDiego.gov.  San Francisco Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in San Francisco, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  San Francisco Transient Occupancy Tax: 14% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. 14% is the tax rate imposed by the City and County of San Francisco (the tax jurisdictions are one and the same). For detailed information, visit SFtreasurer.org.    San Jose Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in San Jose, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  San Jose Transient Occupancy Tax: 10% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit SanJoseCa.gov.   Santa Clara Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Santa Clara, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:    Santa Clara Transient Occupancy Tax: 9.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit SantaClara.gov.    Santa Monica Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Santa Monica, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Santa Monica Transient Occupancy Tax: 14% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Santa Monica's website.  Connecticut State of Connecticut Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Connecticut will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Connecticut State Room Occupancy Tax: 15% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for the first 30 nights of any reservation. For detailed information, visit the Connecticut Department of Revenue website.  District of Columbia District of Columbia Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the District of Columbia will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  DC Sales Tax on Hotels (transient accommodations): 14.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 90 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit DC.gov.  Florida State of Florida   Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Florida will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:    Florida Transient Rental Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Florida Dept. of Revenue website. Florida Discretionary Sales Surtax: 0.5%-1.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. The State imposes both a statewide 6% tax and a local 0.5-1.5% tax, which varies by county. For detailed information, visit the Florida Dept. of Revenue website. County Tourist Development Taxes collected by the State: 2-5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter.  The state administers 22 county taxes, including: Bradford, Citrus, Columbia, Desoto, Dixie, Flagler, Franklin, Gadsden, Gilchrist, Glades, Hamilton, Hendry, Holmes, Jackson, Jefferson, Levy, Madison, Okeechobee, Pasco, Sumter, Wakulla, and Washington. Brevard County Tourist Development Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Brevard Tax Collector website.  Hernando County Tourist Development Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Hernando County Comptroller site. Lee County Tourist Development Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Lee Clerk website.  Orange County Tourist Development Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Orange County Comptroller website. Pinellas County Tourist Development Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Pinellas County Tax Collector website. Putnam County Tourist Development Tax: 4% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Putnam County Tax Collector website. Taylor County Tourism Development Tax: 3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Taylor County Tax Collector website.  Illinois Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Illinois, Cook County, and Chicago will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Illinois Hotel Operators Occupation Tax: 5.98-6.17% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit tax.Illinois.gov. Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Cook County, IL will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:   Cook County Hotel Accommodations Tax: 1% of the listing price including any cleaning fee. For detailed information, visit the  Cook County Department of Revenue website. Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Chicago, IL will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Chicago Hotel Accommodation Tax: 4.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit CityofChicago.org.   Other Taxes administered by the State of Illinois: 5.73% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit tax.Illinois.gov.  Louisiana State of Louisiana Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Louisiana will pay the following taxes administered by the State as part of their reservation:  Louisiana Sales and Use Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for all reservations. For detailed information, visit the Louisiana Department of Revenue website.  Maryland Montgomery County Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Montgomery County, MD will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Montgomery County Room Rental and Transient Tax: 7% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Room Rental-Transient Tax Information page.  Nevada Washoe County, Sparks and Reno Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Washoe County, the City of Sparks or the City of Reno, NV will pay the following tax as part of their reservation:  City or County Transient Lodging Tax: of either 13.5% or 13% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for 27 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the   RSCVA Finance and Accounting Department website.  New Jersey Jersey City Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Jersey City, NJ will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:   Hotel and Motel Use and Occupancy Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 89 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Article V of Jersey City's Code of Ordinances at municode.com.  New York Tompkins County Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Tompkins County, NY will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation: Tompkins County Hotel Room Occupancy Tax: 3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Tompkins County's website.  North Carolina State of North Carolina Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of North Carolina will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  North Carolina Sales Tax: 6.75-7.5% of the listing price including any cleaning and guest fees for reservations less than 90 nights. The State imposes both a statewide 4.75% tax and a local 2-2.75% tax, which varies by county. For detailed information, visit North Carolina's website. City and/or County Occupancy Tax: All locally imposed occupancy taxes will be collected on reservations in North Carolina. The tax varies by city and county. It is typically 1-8% of the listing price including any cleaning and guest fees for reservations less than 90 nights.  Ohio Cleveland, OH USA Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Cleveland, OH will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Cleveland Transient Occupancy Tax: 3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the City of Cleveland website. Cuyahoga County, OH USA Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Cuyahoga County, OH will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  County Bed Tax: 5.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fees for 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, please visit Cuyahoga County's FAQ page.  Oregon State of Oregon Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Oregon, Multnomah County and/or the City of Portland will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Oregon Transient Lodging Tax: 1.8% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. 1.8% is the State imposed tax rate only. For detailed information, visit Oregon.gov.  Multnomah County Transient Lodging Tax: 11.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. 11.5% is the maximum Transient Lodging Tax for listings in Multnomah County (excluding the State level tax). For example, for Portland listings that are also located in Multnomah County, the Portland Transient Lodging Tax is 6% and the Multnomah County Transient Lodging Tax is 5.5%. For detailed information, visit  PortlandOregon.gov.  Portland Transient Lodging Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter  Washington County Transient Room Tax: Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Washington County, OR will pay 9% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Washington County Finance Department website.  Pennsylvania State of Pennsylvania Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Pennsylvania will pay the following taxes administered by the State as part of their reservation:  Pennsylvania Hotel Occupancy Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter that are in the State of Pennsylvania. For detailed information, visit the Pennsylvania Department of Revenue website.  Local Sales Tax Collected by the State: 1% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. The State administers 2 Local Sales Taxes: Allegheny County and Philadelphia County. For detailed information, visit the Pennsylvania Department of Revenue website. Allegheny County Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Allegheny County will pay the following tax as part of their reservation:   Allegheny County Hotel Room Rental Tax: 7% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter.  For detailed information visit the Allegheny County Treasurer website. Philadelphia Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Philadelphia, PA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Philadelphia Hotel Room Rental Tax: 8.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. 8.5% is the tax rate imposed by the City and County of Philadelphia (the tax jurisdictions are one and the same). For detailed information, visit Phila.gov.  Rhode Island State of Rhode Island Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Rhode Island will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:    Rhode Island Sales Tax: 7% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit  RI.gov.   Rhode Island Local Hotel Tax: 1% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter.   Rhode Island Statewide Hotel Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter on rentals of private rooms or shared rooms only.  Rentals of an entire home or apartment are excluded from this tax.  South Carolina   State of South Carolina Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of South Carolina will pay the following taxes administered by the State as part of their reservation:  South Carolina State Sales and Use Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 89 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the South Carolina Department of Revenue website. South Carolina State Accommodations Tax: 2% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 89 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the South Carolina Department of Revenue website. Local Taxes collected by the State: 0.5-8%, per Local Tax type, of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 89 nights and shorter.  One or more of the following Local Taxes may apply:  Capital Project Tax, Catawba Tribal Tax, School District Tax, Education Capital Improvement Tax, Transportation Tax, Local Option Tax, Tourism Development Tax.  Note that Airbnb is only collecting the Local Taxes that are administered or collected by the State at this time.  For detailed information, visit the South Carolina Department of Revenue website and the Sales and Use Tax Manual.  Washington State of Washington Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Washington will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:  Washington Combined Sales Tax: 7.0-9.6% of the listing price including any cleaning fees for reservations 29 nights and shorter.  Washington's combined sales tax is a combination of the state retail sales tax of 6.5% and the local retail sales tax, which varies by county and city. For detailed information, visit WA.gov. Special Hotel/Motel Tax, Convention and Trade Center Tax, Regional Transit Authority Tax, and Tourism Promotion Area Charges: All locally imposed taxes on transient lodging will be collected on reservations in Washington. The Special Hotel/Motel Tax is typically 1-5% of the listing price including any cleaning fees for reservations 29 nights and shorter. Other local taxes vary and are only applicable in certain cities and counties.   Hosts located in these areas are responsible for assessing all other tax obligations, including state and city jurisdictions. Hosts with listings in these areas should also review their agreement with Airbnb under the Terms of Service and familiarize themselves with the Occupancy Tax provisions which allow us to collect and remit taxes on their behalf and explains how the process works. Under those provisions, hosts instruct and authorize Airbnb to collect and remit Occupancy Taxes on their behalf in jurisdictions where Airbnb decides to facilitate such collection. If a hosts believes applicable laws exempt the host from collecting a tax that Airbnb collects and remits on the host's behalf, the host has agreed that, by accepting the reservation, the host is waiving that exemption. If a host does not want to waive an exemption the host believes exists, the host should not accept the reservation.", "question": "In what areas is Occupancy Tax Collection and Remittance by Airbnb available?"},
{"answer": "In areas that Airbnb has made agreements with governments to collect and remit local taxes on behalf of hosts, Airbnb calculates applicable local taxes and collects those taxes from guests at the time of booking. Airbnb then takes care of remitting collected taxes to the applicable tax authority on the hosts' behalf.   This doesn\u2019t change which taxes are due, but automating the process makes tax collection easier for all parties involved.  If occupancy tax is being collected for your area, it appears as a line item on your listing\u2019s public page. You can also confirm what taxes are being collected and remitted by looking for occupancy tax details in Manage Listing &gt; Location, underneath the Address section.  Taxes collected on reservations do not affect the amount of host payouts. Hosts continue to get their payout of accommodation fees minus Airbnb service fees.  Collected Occupancy Taxes are listed in the Gross Earnings section of hosts\u2019 transaction history, and appear as a line item on all guest receipts.    Related Content              In what areas is Occupancy Tax Collection and Remittance by Airbnb available?      Where do I find information about my payouts?", "question": "How does Occupancy Tax Collection and Remittance by Airbnb work?"},
{"answer": "We created the Verified ID process to build trust in our community and help give you more information when you're deciding who to host or stay with.              How Verified ID works         Verified ID connects your Airbnb profile with other information about you. As part of Verified ID, you might be asked to:                                   Take a photo or upload an image of your government-issued ID, such as your driver's license or passport             Depending on where you live, you may have the option of answering a few questions about yourself instead             Connect another online profile to your Airbnb account, such as a Facebook, Google, or LinkedIn account             Upload an Airbnb profile photo and provide a phone number and email address                      Visit airbnb.com/verify to get started at any time.       When you'll need to complete it         Under certain circumstances, you might be required to complete Verified ID. For example, hosts can require that guests complete Verified ID before booking their place.                  If your host requires you to complete Verified ID, you'll be directed to complete the process right after you send your reservation request, and will have 12 hours to complete it. If you need to come back later, go to airbnb.com/verify and pick up where you left off.                           The Verified ID badge              When you complete Verified ID, you'll earn a badge on your profile. Many hosts and guests look for this badge when deciding whether to host or stay with someone\u2014but it's not an endorsement or guarantee of someone's identity.                    Privacy and encryption         We take privacy seriously. The information you provide during this process is encrypted and governed by our Privacy Policy.                      We won't share the government ID or personal details you provide during Verified ID with your host or guest\u2014they'll only know that you\u2019ve successfully completed the process. And we\u2019ll never post to your Facebook, Google, LinkedIn, or other connected accounts without your permission.                  Other ways your ID info is used     Where permitted by applicable law, we may also provide information from your government ID, such as your full name and date of birth, to our service providers to run checks against public records for criminal convictions and sex offender registrations. For now, these checks are limited to users in the United States about whom we have adequate identifying information, such as the user\u2019s full name and date of birth. While we believe these checks help us deter fraud and misuse of our services, they don\u2019t guarantee that interactions with people who book through Airbnb will be safe or problem-free. Please carefully review our notice about the limitations of background and registered sex offender checks.", "question": "What is Verified ID?"},
{"answer": "What is Occupancy Tax? Occupancy tax is a tax on the rental of rooms that your state or locality may require. In many places this is known as an occupancy tax, but may also be known as a lodging tax, a room tax, a sales tax, a tourist tax, or a hotel tax. Occupancy tax rates and rules vary by city, county, state, and country. They\u2019re generally owed on the accommodations price plus any fees for other items, like cleanings or extra guests. In some places, occupancy tax is required on a per person, per night basis. There are typically long-term stay exceptions that exempt reservations over a certain number of nights. Occupancy tax is generally paid by the guest, but the obligation to remit the taxes to the government usually falls on the host. We expect all hosts to familiarize themselves with and follow their local laws and regulations. What are my options to collect and pay occupancy tax? As an Airbnb host, if you determine that you need to collect occupancy tax, you can collect Occupancy Taxes by either incorporating it into your nightly price, adding it within a Special Offer, or asking your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect Occupancy Taxes in person, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we\u2019re unable to assist with collection. In some locations, like Amsterdam, Portland and San Francisco, Airbnb automatically collects occupancy tax from guests and sends it to the tax authority on hosts\u2019 behalf. For these areas, Occupancy Tax amounts will appear as a line item on your listing\u2019s public page, and you should not collect taxes separately for those jurisdictions. Learn more. To confirm if you listing is included in a collection area:  Go to Your Listings Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you'd like to view Select Location on the left If occupancy taxes are being collected and remitted on your behalf, they'll be listed at the bottom of the page. When will Airbnb start collecting occupancy tax in my area? We\u2019ll let you know if an occupancy tax related feature becomes available for your listing. We want to help hosts follow the laws relevant to them, and we understand that many of these rules are complex and difficult to follow. We're continuing to work with governments across the world to explore ways to help facilitate occupancy tax collection in as many locations as possible.", "question": "What is occupancy tax? Do I need to collect or pay it?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "We ask everyone who uses Airbnb for a few pieces of information before they travel on Airbnb. Guests need to have this info completely filled out before they can make a reservation request. This info helps make sure hosts know who to expect, and how to contact the guest. Airbnb\u2019s requirements for guests include:   Full name   Confirmed email address   Confirmed phone number   Profile photo that shows their face   Introductory message   Agreement to house rules   Payment information  Hosts won\u2019t see guest\u2019s real email addresses, even after they book. Instead, hosts will see a temporary Airbnb email address that forwards their messages to the guest. Some hosts may also ask guests to complete Verified ID before booking their space.", "question": "What are the requirements to book on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices Select Guest Invoice  For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation.    Related Article              How do I provide my VAT ID number?         .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "If your host canceled your reservation, you can transfer your payment to a new Airbnb reservation or request a refund.   If you experience a travel issue that prevents you from being able to complete a trip with Airbnb, and you\u2019re unable to resolve with your host, our Guest Refund Policy may be applied in certain circumstances.      Eligible travel issues Situations that may be eligible for a refund under this policy generally fall into one of three categories:  The host fails to provide reasonable access to the booked listing. The listing booked is misrepresented (ex: number of bedrooms, location, lacks promised amenities). The listing isn't generally clean, is unsafe, or there's an animal in the listing that wasn't disclosed prior to booking.    Airbnb will either provide you with a refund or use reasonable efforts to find and book you at another comparable accommodation for any unused nights left in your reservation. The amount of any refund will depend on the nature of the travel Issue suffered. Submit a valid claim for refund To submit a valid claim for your reservation, you are required to: Contact us within 24 hours of check-in to document the issue and place a hold on the host's payment. Include photographs or other evidence of the issue as part of your claim. Be responsive to our requests for additional information and cooperation. Not have directly or indirectly caused the Travel Issue. Have used reasonable efforts to remedy the circumstances of the Travel Issue with the host prior to making a claim, including messaging your host on Airbnb to notify them of the issue. We'll verify this in your account. Review the Guest Refund Policy Terms for more details, including more information about the minimum quality standards for accommodations, and what qualifies as a travel issue.", "question": "Guest Refund Policy"},
{"answer": "The Airbnb Host Guarantee provides protection for up to $1,000,000 to a host for damages to covered property in the rare event of guest damages above the security deposit\u2014or if no security deposit is in place. The Host Guarantee Program doesn't cover cash and securities, collectibles, rare artwork, jewelry, pets or personal liability. We recommend that hosts secure or remove valuables when renting their place. The program also doesn't cover loss or damage to property due to wear and tear. For these types of incidents, hosts can add a security deposit in their pricing settings. The Host Guarantee Program isn't insurance and doesn't replace your homeowners or renters insurance. Make sure you review and understand the terms of your insurance policy and what it covers and doesn't cover. Not all insurance will cover damage or loss to property caused by a guest renting your space. Filing a host guarantee request doesn't preclude a guest from financial responsibility for the damages claimed if Airbnb determines a guest was at fault. Learn more about the Host Guarantee at: www.airbnb.com/guarantee.  View the Host Guarantee terms and conditions at: www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee. If you can't view this page, the country you're accessing Airbnb from doesn't have Host Guarantee coverage right now.", "question": "What is the Airbnb Host Guarantee?"},
{"answer": "The following information is provided for law enforcement entities seeking information about users of the Airbnb platform.         All other requests for information regarding the Airbnb platform, including user questions regarding reservations and user information, should be directed to our Customer Experience team.                                        We reserve the right to make changes to the information on this page at any given time without notice. You should check this page each time you're making a request.                               Emergency Requests                          Cross-Border Information Requests                          Requests from US Law Enforcement                          Requests from Non-US Law Enforcment                          Form of Requests                                                 Emergency Requests         In the event of an emergency involving the danger of death or serious physical injury to a person, law enforcement agents may make an emergency disclosure request by emailing leoinfo@airbnb.com with the subject: Emergency Disclosure Request.         Users or non-law-enforcement third parties aware of an emergency situation should not contact us at this email address, but instead should immediately and directly contact local law enforcement officials. Other urgent communications may be directed to Airbnb's Customer Experience team.         Back to Top                                    Cross-Border Information Requests         If Airbnb Ireland\u2019s initial research shows that the concerned data subject is likely a US resident, the guidelines that apply for requests from US law enforcement will be followed. Non-US law enforcement seeking information about US users needs to serve the request on the registered agent in the US, and Airbnb, Inc. may require the requesting law enforcement authority to follow the MLAT processes.         Also, if Airbnb, Inc.\u2019s initial research shows that the concerned data subject is likely a non-US resident, the guidelines that apply for requests from non-US law enforcement are to be followed. US law enforcement seeking information about non-US users needs to serve the request on Airbnb Ireland, and Airbnb Ireland may require the requesting law enforcement Authority to follow the MLAT processes.         Back to Top                                    Requests from US Law Enforcement         All law enforcement requests for user information should be directed to Airbnb, Inc., located in San Francisco, California. Airbnb will respond to valid, properly served legal process to the extent permitted by our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, and US law, through service on its Registered Agent for Service of Process in Delaware and California: Corporation Service Company, 2711 Centerville Road, Suite 400, Wilmington, DE 19808, 866-403-5272, 302-636-5454 (fax), www.cscglobal.com, and/or at 888 Brannan Street, San Francisco, CA 94103 Attn: Legal. To expedite review of a request, in addition to serving Airbnb\u2019s Registered Agent, please fax a copy of the legal process to 1-888-927-3493.         The following materials are required for non-emergency information requests from US law enforcement:                      A valid trial, grand jury or administrative subpoena is required to compel the disclosure of basic subscriber records (defined in 18 USC \u00a7 2703(c)(2)).             A court order issued pursuant to 18 USC \u00a7 2703(d) is required to compel the disclosure of certain other records pertaining to an account, not including contents of communications.             For content of communications, a search warrant issued under the procedures described in the US Federal Rules of Criminal Procedure (or equivalent state warrant procedures) is required.                  Notification         Please note that Airbnb, Inc. has a policy of using commercially reasonable efforts to notify users in the United States when we receive legal process from a third party requesting user data. Generally, except where a court order (and not just the request for information itself) requires delayed notification or no notification, or except where notification is otherwise prohibited by law or where we, in our sole discretion, believe that providing notice would be futile, ineffective or would create a risk of injury or bodily harm to an individual or group, or to our property, we will endeavor to provide reasonable prior notice to the relevant user of the request for user data in the event the user wishes to seek appropriate protective relief.         Back to Top                                    Requests from Non-US Law Enforcement         All law enforcement requests for user information from non-US law enforcement should be directed to Airbnb Ireland, located in Dublin, Ireland. Generally, Airbnb Ireland will respond to a valid and properly notified legal request to the extent permitted by our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy and applicable law. Requests should be directed to:                                                Airbnb Ireland                 Law Enforcement Liaison                 The Watermarque Building                 South Lotts Road                 Ringsend                 Dublin 4                 Ireland                               To expedite review of a request, in addition to notifying Airbnb Ireland by mail, please fax a copy of your request to 35316971830.         Specifically the following is required for requests from non-US law enforcement:                      In case of alleged crimes against a person, a person\u2019s property or alleged fraud, a valid police request on Police Department letterhead is required for the disclosure of basic subscriber records, transactional information or basic payments-related data (not including contents of communications) to be considered by Airbnb Ireland.             For all other alleged crimes, a valid request on your law enforcement agency\u2019s letterhead is required for the disclosure of basic subscriber records to be considered by Airbnb Ireland and a valid order (\u201cordonnance judiciaire\u201d, \u201cDecreto del Giudice per le Indagini Preliminari\u201d, subpoena, \u201cAuskunftsersuchen\u201d, \u201crichterlicher Beschluss/formelles Auskunftsersuchen\u201d) is required for the disclosure of transactional information pertaining to an account or payments-related data (not including contents of communications) to be considered by Airbnb Ireland.             For content of communications, an appropriate and binding court order (or equivalent local warrant procedure) is required for the disclosure to be considered by Airbnb Ireland.                  The above notwithstanding, we explicitly reserve the right to require the use of diplomatic processes such as an applicable Mutual Legal Assistance Treaty.         Notification         Please note that Airbnb Ireland has a policy of using commercially reasonable efforts to notify users when we receive legal process from a third party requesting their user data. Generally, we will notify the relevant user of your request except where a court order (not a request) expressly requires us to delay or withhold notification, or where notification is otherwise prohibited by applicable law, or where based upon the information supplied by law enforcement we, in our sole discretion, believe that providing notice would be futile or ineffective or would create a risk of injury or great bodily harm to our rights or property or to an individual or group of individuals, including minors.         Back to Top                                    Form of Requests         Airbnb is unable to process overly broad or vague requests. We will only consider law enforcement requests that are:                      Typed             Duly signed and stamped by the appropriate law enforcement officer who is empowered by local law to represent the law enforcement unit that is making the request             In compliance with local, international, and United States law             Addressed to Airbnb, Inc. or Airbnb Ireland (as appropriate) and sent to Airbnb, Inc. or Airbnb Ireland (as appropriate) directly             Translated into English                  Requests should explicitly mention the following elements:                      All known email addresses, names, and aliases of data subject or all known physical addresses and telephone numbers of the data subject.             Your name, department, street address, telephone number, fax number, and email address. If your specific fax number is not supplied, our answer may be sent to your general department fax. Please note that for law enforcement communications by email, Airbnb will only respond to emails from law enforcement email domains.             Exactly what information you're requesting, why you're requesting it, and how it pertains to your investigation.             The applicable act or law under which the law enforcement agency is requesting the data.                  Back to Top", "question": "How does Airbnb respond to data requests from law enforcement?"},
{"answer": "Being a responsible host means being a considerate tenant, neighbor, and community member. Here are a few things you should consider when talking with others about hosting on Airbnb. Know the rules and regulations Before you start hosting, know what contracts and rules affect you, such as leases, condo board or co-op rules, HOA rules, or rules established by tenant organizations. Make sure you understand and comply with these rules before listing your space. Other laws in your city or state may also affect you, so be sure to review them as well. Talk with your landlord or HOA Talk to your homeowner\u2019s association or landlord about how often you plan to have guests, and how Airbnb builds trust in its community. You can share information about Airbnb\u2019s trust and safety resources, including community reviews and Verified ID. Remind them that you only host people you feel comfortable with. If applicable in your country, you can also explain that Airbnb offers a US$1M Host Guarantee. Talk with your neighbors Neighbors may want to know about many of the same things as your landlord or HOA, as well as more specifics about upcoming bookings, such as names, dates, and other information about your guests. Making sure your neighbors are comfortable might help address some of your landlord\u2019s concerns.  Be a responsible host Here are some things you can do to show your landlord, HOA, and neighbors that you care about the property and your neighbors as much as they do: Set an occupancy limit to only allow groups of a certain size  Share your home and building rules with each guest Provide your guests with phone numbers for emergency responders and a map of emergency exits and evacuation routes Make sure you have a working smoke and carbon monoxide detector Inform neighbors when a guest will be staying in your home With your guests\u2019 permission, share names or Airbnb profile pages", "question": "How should I talk to my neighbors, homeowners association, or landlord about Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb empowers hosts to set and manage their cancellation policies. If a host or guest needs to cancel a reservation, it\u2019s their responsibility to cancel as soon as possible. At times, certain circumstances outside of a host or guest\u2019s control can impact their ability to meet the terms of a reservation. In rare instances, if Airbnb determines that a Guest\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, Airbnb may override the Host's cancellation policy (ex: flexible, moderate, strict) and make refund decisions.  If Airbnb determines that a Host\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances policy, Airbnb may waive the host cancellation penalties outlined in Airbnb\u2019s Terms of Service and Airbnb\u2019s Payments Terms of Service. What might be covered? Valid extenuating circumstances include:  Unexpected death or serious illness of a host, guest or immediate family member  Serious injury that directly restricts a guest\u2019s ability to travel or a host\u2019s ability to host Significant natural disasters or severe weather incidents impacting the location of destination or location of departure Urgent travel restrictions or severe security advisories issued after the time of booking, by an appropriate national or international authority (such as a government office or department) Endemic disease declared by a credible national or international authority (such as the US Center for Disease Control or the World Health Organization) Severe property damage or unforeseen maintenance issues that directly impact the ability to host safely Government-mandated obligations issued after the time of booking  If you need to make a claim Claims can only be considered after a reservation has been canceled. Once you have informed your host or guest and canceled a reservation, if you feel that your reason for cancellation is covered by Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, contact Airbnb for consideration. We generally require claims to be submitted no later than 14 days from the original check-in date and we may require valid supporting documentation.", "question": "Extenuating Circumstances Policy"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "Whether you want to get to know hosts and guests in your home city, or you\u2019re looking to meet other people who use Airbnb while you travel, meetups are a great way to connect with our global community, swap tips, and share experiences. Events include things like volunteering at a local garden, taking a neighborhood architectural tour, exchanging hosting tips, or just throwing a party to celebrate the Airbnb community in your city.   Check out our Meetup page to see what's going in your city, or other cities around the world. To sign up for an Airbnb meetup, you must:        Have your own Airbnb account    RSVP on the event's invitation page             RSVPs are only good for one person per Airbnb account. When you RSVP, you'll receive a confirmation email, and your name and Airbnb profile photo will appear on the confirmed list of attendees. If a meetup's guest list is full, you'll see the option to add yourself to the waitlist. If a spot opens up, you'll receive a notification.  You can also connect with other hosts and guests at any time through our online community platform, the Airbnb Community Center. Interested in a specific city? Check out our Cities boards.", "question": "What are Airbnb meetups?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "If you notice that something is missing, not working, or otherwise not what you expected when you check in, contact your host right away. Your host is often in the best position to help you\u2014giving them the chance to fix an issue can be the fastest way to make sure you get what you need, and can continue on with your reservation as planned. In the event that you experience a travel issue, and you and your host aren't able to resolve the issue on your own, please take the following required steps within 24 hours of your check-in to make sure you're covered by our Guest Refund Policy:      Contact us to document the issue and place a hold on the host's payment.   Message your host on Airbnb to notify them of the issue. We'll need to verify this in your account.     Take photographs to document the situation. It's important that your photos show what's happening and where (in relation to the rest of the room or space) so we can verify what's going on.    If your host is unreachable or unresponsive, we'll work on issuing you an adequate partial refund if you decide to stay, or a full refund if you decide to leave, as we deem appropriate. You can see a complete explanation of coverage in our Guest Refund Policy.  The Guest Refund Policy doesn't apply beyond 24 hours after check-in, but we can always help you mediate with your host if you've tried reaching out with no response.                          Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "What should I do if something's missing or not as expected when I check in?"},
{"answer": "Even if you\u2019ve already booked your reservation, it\u2019s your choice whether to accept or decline a host\u2019s offer to book an alternate listing.     Before paying for a reservation     If you don\u2019t yet have a confirmed reservation and the host offers you a different listing from the one you discussed, you can book your reservation at this listing or simply look for a new place. You have no obligation to accept the new listing and you should make sure that it would work for your trip before booking.     After you\u2019ve paid for your reservation     If your host is asking you to stay in a different listing than you originally booked and you\u2019re okay with a switch, either you or your host can change your reservation. Make sure to check the details of the new listing before accepting a change.     If you\u2019re not okay with a switch or your host is asking you to switch without officially changing the reservation on Airbnb, ask the host to cancel your reservation so you can get a full refund or find another home that better accommodates your stay.     After you\u2019ve checked in     If you\u2019ve already checked in and you feel the listing is not what you booked on the site, follow the steps to document the issue and our Guest Refund Policy will make sure you either get the listing you booked or receive a refund. Related articles   How do I change my reservation as a guest? What should I do if something's not missing or not as expected when I check in? How do I check if a reservation is confirmed? How can I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "What if a host informs me that the listing I already paid for is now unavailable but they have an alternative?"},
{"answer": "If you\u2019re having trouble getting in touch with your host after you\u2019ve made a reservation, consider a few things:   Most hosts respond within a few hours.     We recommend giving the host a few days to respond. Sometimes things come up or your host might be on a different schedule from you.   Try contacting your host using a different form of communication. For example, you can try reaching them through:        Airbnb message: Find your host in your Messages and send them a note.   Email or phone: Go to Your Trips, click View Itinerary next to your reservation, and use the email address or phone number listed.                         If your trip is starting or about to start, contact us.  Related Content     How do I contact a host? How do I view and send messages? How do I contact Airbnb?", "question": "What if I can't get in touch with my host?"},
{"answer": "Inviting people to Airbnb can earn you\u2014and the people you invite\u2014travel credit to use toward a new reservation.     Invite friends to use Airbnb                     To begin earning credit, visit the invitation page and send the link to your friends. When a friend clicks the link, they will receive credit that will automatically apply towards their first reservation with Airbnb. The credit will show up automatically on the checkout page of any qualifying reservation.                                When your friend completes their first qualifying reservation, you'll earn travel credit to use for your own Airbnb reservations. You'll receive your travel credit after the departure date of your friend's trip. For each person you refer, there are two opportunities to earn travel credit. You earn credit when your friend completes a qualifying reservation as a guest and also when they complete a qualifying reservation as a host. You can earn up to $5,000 USD in travel credit overall.                       To see all of your current referral details, click Invite Friends on your Airbnb Dashboard. Terms apply.         Qualifying reservations         A qualifying reservation usually has a total value of $75 USD or more, excluding guest fees and any taxes. These amounts may vary during promotional periods.         Use your travel credit         Your available travel credits automatically appear as a coupon on the checkout page of your reservation request. If the travel credits aren't automatically added, it means the reservation doesn\u2019t qualify.         Travel credits can't apply to a trip that has already been paid for, but they will be available and applied to your next qualifying reservation. They expire one year from the date they're issued and can only be used once. They\u2019re also not reusable if you cancel a reservation where the credits were applied.", "question": "How do referrals and travel credits work?"},
{"answer": "Amex Express Checkout  With Amex Express Checkout, eligible American Express Card Members who have an americanexpress.com account can complete bookings quickly and send information securely to Airbnb. On the payment page, select Amex Express Checkout as your Payment type and enter your americanexpress.com User ID and Password in the Amex Express Checkout pop-up window. After you confirm your card information with Airbnb, American Express will share your card and billing information with Airbnb in order to process the booking. If you have an eligible card to use American Express Membership Rewards points for your booking, you\u2019ll see the option to use points. When you\u2019re ready, submit your reservation request.   American Express Membership Rewards points  To use points for all or a portion of your Airbnb reservation, you need an American Express Card enrolled in the US Membership Rewards program that\u2019s active, in good standing and authorized to use points.  View eligible American Express Cards here. When you choose to pay with an eligible card, the maximum dollar value in points available for the booking will display. You can choose to apply the entire dollar value of points available, or enter the amount you prefer to use. To confirm your use of points, click Apply to Booking. Whether you use Membership Rewards points to for all or a portion of your booking, your American Express Card will be charged for the total amount of the reservation, and the dollar amount used in Membership Rewards points will appear as a statement credit on your card account in 2-4 business days. If you\u2019re issued a refund on a booking that used Membership Rewards points, we\u2019ll credit the dollar amount of the refund to the American Express Card that you used. Please allow 2-4 days for the refund to post to your American Express Card billing statement. If you\u2019d like to have points reinstated instead, please contact Amex Membership Rewards program Customer Care at 1-800-297-3276. For questions about Amex Express Checkout and American Express Membership Rewards eligibility, or for more information about this program, visit amex.co/AirbnbFAQs.", "question": "Amex Express Checkout and American Express Membership Rewards\u00ae points"},
{"answer": "If you want to use a coupon on a new Airbnb reservation, you can add it on the same page where you submit payment. Find your coupon code If you received a coupon from Airbnb, you will find the coupon in your email. At the moment, these coupons don\u2019t automatically show up on airbnb.com.  Use a coupon on a reservation  On the checkout page for a reservation, click Coupon code near your subtotal.  Enter your code. Click Apply.  There are a few things to know about using coupons:    Only one coupon can be used for a reservation.     If your coupon has expired, there is no way to re-activate it.     Coupons can only be used once. If you cancel a reservation that used a coupon, the coupon is also no longer valid.   We only accept coupons issued by Airbnb.   If you don\u2019t use the full amount of a coupon, you won\u2019t receive the difference.   Coupons can't be applied retroactively. Use travel credits You can receive travel credits for referring people to travel or host on Airbnb. Unlike with coupons, these credits are automatically applied when you book a space. There are a few things to know about using travel credits:    Travel credits can\u2019t be combined with any other coupons.     Travel credits can only be used on qualifying reservations (usually $75 or more, before any guest fees or taxes).   You won\u2019t receive any travel credits until the person you referred has completed a qualifying reservation on Airbnb.  Related Content       How do referrals and travel credits work? How do Airbnb gift cards work?", "question": "How do I use a coupon code?"},
{"answer": "If you contact a host about their space before requesting to book it, the host has the option to invite you to book a couple of ways:    Pre-approval: The host invites you to book for the dates and prices shown when you contacted the host     Special offer: The host chooses a custom price (or other details) and invites you to book with the new details Note: A special offer will not include the guest service fee or relevant taxes charged for each reservation. Find your pre-approval or special offer You'll get an email notification when you receive a pre-approval or special offer. You can also check your reservation status by looking in the message thread where you're talking with the host.  Book a pre-approval or special offer You won\u2019t automatically be booked when you receive a pre-approval or a special offer. You still need to add your payment details and confirm the reservation.      On airbnb.com, go to your Inbox         Click the conversation with the host to open the message thread     Find the box that shows the details of your pre-approval or special offer     Click Book It!     Add your payment details, and click Book now     You\u2019ll receive a confirmation email with your itinerary and a billing receipt     You have 24 hours to book a pre-approval or special offer before it expires. If 24 hours have passed, you can still accept the pre-approval but your host will have to approve your request before your reservation is confirmed. Change your dates If you've already been pre-approved or given a special offer, you can still change your dates. On the listing page, click Contact Host  to send the host a new message and change the dates before sending the message. The host will then have the ability to pre-approve or give a special offer for your new dates. The option to book isn\u2019t available A host has the ability to pre-approve or extend a special offer to multiple people at once for a set of dates. If someone else booked the space before you, you won\u2019t see the option to accept the reservation. Related Content   What is a pre-approval? How do I send a guest a special offer? How do I pre-approve a guest?", "question": "How do I book a pre-approval or special offer?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "No, Airbnb can't split your reservation cost across multiple payment methods. To make a reservation, you'll need to make your payment with a single payment method.  If you need to update your payment method for a long-term reservation or an unsuccessful charge, please contact us for assistance.  If you have a confirmed reservation that isn't long-term, remember that you've already paid in full through our payment system\u2014so you won't need to change or update your payment method to enjoy your trip.", "question": "Can I use more than one payment method to pay for a reservation?"},
{"answer": "Transparency and trust are vital to the Airbnb experience. People rely on information in Airbnb profiles, reviews, and other verifications when deciding whether to host or stay with someone.  We require Airbnb reservations booked for personal travel to be booked by the person who's going to stay at the listing. Instead of making a reservation for someone else, consider referring them to Airbnb. You can refer them to Airbnb directly from your dashboard by clicking the Invite Friends button. When a referred friend or family member successfully completes a qualifying reservation, you\u2019ll earn travel credit.      For business trips, Airbnb allows designated bookers at companies enrolled in Airbnb for Business to book trips on behalf of others. If you book travel for a company, read more.", "question": "Can I book on behalf of a friend or family member?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb gift cards are a great way to give the gift of travel! Visit airbnb.com/gift to get started. If you have a gift card to redeem, click Redeem a Gift Card and enter your code. Once a gift card has been added to an Airbnb account, the funds on it will not expire. Gift card balances are visible from your payment methods page. The balance from gift cards will be automatically applied when a trip is booked, but cannot be applied to long-term reservations (28 nights or longer). To send a digital gift card to anyone in the United States, select Send a Gift Card. We\u2019ll send the gift card by email, and the recipient can easily add it to their Airbnb account. The recipient of a digital gift card has 90 days to claim it and link it to their Airbnb account. If the gift card is not claimed within that time, we'll send the gift card balance back to the purchaser on the same payment method they used to pay. Right now, gift cards can only be purchased in US dollars, but we\u2019ll be expanding on the program in additional currencies in the future. Gift Card Terms of Service", "question": "How do Airbnb gift cards work?"},
{"answer": "If you want to see the status of your reservation, you can find your status in your Inbox on the right side of the message thread with the guest or host. Once you\u2019ve found your status, you can see the details of the status below. Reservation statuses Inquiry: A guest sent a message to a host about certain dates, but hasn't submitted a reservation request. In response, the host can send a message, pre-approve, send a Special Offer, or decline the dates of the inquiry. Reservation Request: A guest sent a message to a host by submitting a booking request for specific dates. In response, the host will need to either accept or decline the request within 24 hours before it expires. Pending: A guest is waiting for a host to respond to a reservation request. The host has 24 hours to respond before the request expires. Confirmed: A host accepted a guest's reservation request or the request was accepted automatically with Instant Book. Airbnb has collected full payment from the guest and the booking is complete. Declined: A host declined a guest's reservation request. No charge is made to the guest. Expired: A host took more than 24 hours to respond to a pending reservation request. If the host wants to accommodate the expired request, the host will have to send a pre-approval or Special Offer, or the guest will need to send another reservation request. Canceled: A host or guest canceled a confirmed reservation. Pre-Approval: A guest has contacted the host about specific dates and the host has responded by inviting them to book the dates. If the guest accepts the pre-approval request within 24 hours, their reservation will be confirmed. Special Offer: A guest has contacted the host about specific dates and the host has responded by inviting them to book the dates with a different price than what is listed on their calendar. If the guest accepts the special offer within 24 hours, their reservation will be confirmed. Awaiting Payment: A host chose to accept a guest's reservation request, but the guest's payment didn\u2019t go through. The guest has 24 hours to successfully update their payment information for the reservation to be accepted. Otherwise, the reservation will be canceled without penalty. Action Required: A guest submitted a reservation request to a host who requires they complete Verified ID, and they haven't completed the process yet. The request is on hold until Verified ID has been confirmed. Closed: The guest is no longer looking for a place to stay for the dates they requested. Not Possible: A guest contacted a host about specific dates and the host responded with a Special Offer or pre-approval, but some or all of the dates are no longer available on the host's calendar.", "question": "What does each reservation status mean?"},
{"answer": "Depending on when your guest canceled a reservation, you can refund them from their reservation on airbnb.com, or through the Resolution Center.     Guest canceled before check-in date If your guest canceled the reservation before the check-in date, you can give them an additional refund beyond what the cancellation policy provides by going to Your reservations and clicking the Issue Refund button.  Guest canceled after check-in date If your guest canceled the reservation after the check-in date, you can issue a refund to your guest in our Resolution Center: Go to the Resolution Center on airbnb.com Choose the reservation you want to refund Under Select a Reason, choose Offer Partial Reimbursement  Enter the desired amount, currency, and a message to your guest  After you send the details, your guest will be notified and can choose to accept or decline the offer. If the offer has been accepted, we\u2019ll process your transaction within 48 hours. You\u2019ll be notified once the transaction is complete. Once you submit the refund amount, the transaction is considered final. To ask your guest for any money back, you will need to submit a new request using the Resolution Center. Service fees Airbnb service fees are non-refundable for guests. However, your 3% host fee will be adjusted according to your final reservation total after the refund.", "question": "How do I refund my guest?"},
{"answer": "Messaging on Airbnb starts when a guest makes an inquiry or reservation request. Afterward, all messages related to that inquiry or reservation request will appear in your inbox. View or send a message                      On airbnb.com, go to your Messages             In your inbox, you'll see a message thread for each inquiry or reservation.              Click on a message thread to view old messages or send a new one.                  You must be logged in to your Airbnb account to view or send messages, and you can only send 30 messages within any 24-hour period.                To remove a message from your inbox                                 Go to your Messages             In your inbox, you'll see a message thread for each inquiry or reservation.              Hover over the message thread you'd like to remove and select Archive.          If a message makes you feel uncomfortable or someone tries to get you to pay outside Airbnb, click the  next to it to let us know. Message Threads When you click on a message, you can view the conversation and also the following information:   Host or guest profiles including number of reviews, verifications, and description.   Reservation and payment details such as date of inquiry, number of guests, and price breakdown.   Events such as reservation confirmation, pre-approvals, and special offers are notated in the timeline of the conversations.   If any actions are needed from you, you\u2019ll see the prompt at the top of the page, above the conversation. Guests can make booking inquiries or reservation requests, and hosts will be able to accept or decline requests.     Hosts will see what the guest pays and what they will earn. They will also be able to see a snapshot of their calendar.", "question": "How do I view and send messages?"},
{"answer": "Our Guest Refund Policy and Hospitality Standards help protect guests from things from things like last-minute host cancellations, lock-outs, and listings that are misrepresented, unsanitary, or lacking in promised amenities or items. If you don\u2019t meet one or more of our Hospitality Standards, Airbnb may require you to refund a guest.", "question": "Do I have to refund my guests when they make a complaint?"},
{"answer": "We've heard from hosts around the world that sometimes they'd like a little extra help with their listing. There are times when they'd love to have someone they trust, like a family member or friend, help out with messaging, check in, and more. Following extensive research into a number of ways we can help, we\u2019ll be introducing a new feature that allows current hosts to add an additional host to their account. This is a simple and secure way to allow a family member or trusted friend to help with some of the hosting responsibilities.    This feature will be available soon.", "question": "What can my additional hosts do?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:      New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable          Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable          Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable          Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method  In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How do I split income between multiple people?", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "When a host payout is ready to be paid to you, it will be released to your payout method for processing. You can check the status of your payouts at any time from your Transaction History. To add a new payout method: Go to Account on airbnb.com Select Payout Preferences on the left  Click Add Payout Method and enter your address to see the payout options available to you. Available payout methods and currencies differ by country.   Here are tips for adding specific payout method types: ACH/Direct deposit: Use information from a check to enter your ACH/direct deposit routing number and account number. For Further Credit accounts (FFC) are not supported. Wait for a small deposit to confirm your account is ready. International wire: Depending on your location, you\u2019ll need to enter your account number or IBAN, which your bank can provide. Fees may apply. Read more about international wire transfers. Payoneer Bank transfer/debit card: Enter your name as it appears on your official ID. Payoneer needs to approve your details before you can receive payouts. Read more about Payoneer. PayPal: Make sure that your account, which is an email address, is activated on PayPal before adding it as a payout method. Read more about PayPal. Western Union: Enter your name as it appears on your official ID. Fees apply. Read more about Western Union.  In order to protect your privacy, please do not include specific payout or bank account details in any written correspondence with Airbnb. Managing more than one payout method If you\u2019ve added more than one payout method, you can specify a default or add payout routing rules.  Your default payout method is noted next to your payout method type. To choose a different payout method as your default, first add the new payout method, then click Options and select  Make Default. To remove a payout method (and any settings associated with that payout method), click  Options and select  Remove Payout Method.  Payout routing rules let you split your payouts among different payout methods or set a different payout method for each listing in your account. To add a payout routing rule: Go to Account on airbnb.com Select Payout Preferences on the left Click Add Payout Routing Rule. When you add a new payout routing rule, it won\u2019t affect reservations that have already begun\u2014only payouts for reservations that begin after the change will be affected.", "question": "How do I add or change my payout method?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is support. Whether or not you're sharing a space with your guests, it's important to remain available and responsive throughout their stay. If they can't find the toaster or if the faucet starts leaking, your guests should know they can get help. Availability Make sure your guests have your contact information, and respond to their questions or requests quickly. If you won't be greeting your guests when they arrive, send them a message at their check-in time to make sure everything went smoothly. If you won't be in the area during their stay, give your guests a local point of contact. Expectations and resources Provide detailed House Rules, so your guests know how you'd like for them to treat your space. In the listing, itself, anticipate their needs and provide items and resources that will help them feel at home. Leave a list of phone numbers for taxi companies, restaurants you recommend, and emergency contacts. Each guest will be different\u2014some will prefer privacy, while others will want to interact with you more often. Living like a local Sometimes guests and hosts make plans together. For other trips, you may not be available, or your guests may prefer to explore the area on their own. To help them feel comfortable, create a host guidebook that highlights your favorite local sights and activities. In some cities, you can also point them to a city guidebook with further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Departure Make sure your guests' departure is just as easy as their arrival. The process for returning keys and checking out should be clear and simple. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I make my guests feel supported?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is amenities. Amenities are the useful or fun features your space provides, and the set of amenities a listing offers can be one of the main things that helps it stand out. While all Airbnb hosts should consider providing basic amenities like soap, toilet paper, sheets, and towels, many travelers are also interested in specific amenities like a hair dryer, Wi-Fi, or a hot tub\u2014or are specifically looking for things like family-friendliness. Even knowing small details, like whether or not you provide shampoo and conditioner in your space, can help guests plan for their trip. Accurately listing the amenities your space offers may be the reason a guest decides to stay in your space\u2014and ensuring that every single one is available and operational during your guest's stay will help make it a great one. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "What are amenities and why are they important to guests?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is commitment. When you confirm you'll host someone, they're trusting you to take care of their needs. That's why it's important to make sure you are able to commit to a guest, before accepting a reservation. If the unexpected happens and you can't avoid cancelling a confirmed booking, here are some things to keep in mind:   As soon as you understand that you have to cancel, let your guest know right away. This will give them as much time as possible to find new accommodations.   Be empathetic when you tell your guest that you need to cancel, and do it with a kind, thoughtful tone. You'll need to cancel the reservation within Airbnb to initiate the refund process.   If you know other hosts in your area, consider asking them if they can accommodate this guest\u2019s trip and offer to make an introduction.  Of course, hosts always decide who stays in their space. When there is an extenuating circumstance or a safety concern, we may make an exception to host cancellation penalties. In such cases, hosts should select the Extenuating Circumstance option when canceling the reservation. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "What does commitment mean for hosts?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is cleanliness. Providing a clean and tidy space will make your guests feel comfortable from the moment they arrive\u2014and show your commitment to making your guests feel welcome. To make your listing shine, consider starting with these steps before each guest's arrival:   Clean every room that your guests can access during their stay and pay special attention to the bathroom and kitchen.   If you provide towels and sheets, make sure they're freshly-washed.   To show extra consideration, think about the small things, like dusting the bookshelves, wiping the mirrors, and emptying the wastebasket.   Make room in the closet or dresser so that guests can store their belongings.  We know that cleaning is one of the more challenging aspects of preparing your listing, particularly if you're traveling yourself. If you can't do the cleaning, you can always add a cleaning fee to your listing price and hire a professional cleaning service. It's important to give yourself enough time to clean your space, particularly when you have back-to-back bookings. Giving your guests the ability to tidy up after themselves will be a big help, so consider leaving cleaning supplies in your space, so they can take care of spills and accidental messes.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I provide a clean space for my guests?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.  Related Articles   How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar? How do I set reservation requirements? Why are reviews important?", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is communication. It's important to respond to booking inquiries and reservation requests within 24 hours in order maintain your response rate. Before you confirm a booking, get to know your prospective guest to see if you're a good fit for one another. If their plans don't match your hosting style or what your listing has to offer, just decline the reservation promptly. Responding to guests Every time a guest reaches out\u2014whether you have a booking with them or not\u2014it's important that you respond quickly. Timely responses show travelers that you\u2019re an attentive and considerate host, but it's not the only thing that matters. Make sure you maintain a helpful and polite tone, and find opportunities to personalize your communication so that you can build trusting relationships with other members of the Airbnb community.   Before your guest arrives  When you have a confirmed booking that's about to begin, you should communicate with your guest shortly before their arrival. Ensure they know how to reach you, and see if there\u2019s anything you can do to help make their arrival more comfortable. Unexpected changes If something about your listing has changed since the time you confirmed a booking, communicate it in advance. If your roommate moved out and took all the pots and pans with them, your guest deserves to know.    Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How should I communicate with my guests?"},
{"answer": "If you\u2019ve added more than one payout method, you can specify a default or add payout routing rule. Your default payout method is noted next to your payout method type. To choose a different payout method as your default, first add the new payout method, then click Options and select Make Default. To remove a payout method (and any settings associated with that payout method), click  Options and select  Remove Payout Method. Payout routing rules let you split your payouts among different payout methods or set a different payout method for each listing in your account. To add a payout routing rule: Go to Account on airbnb.com Select Payout Preferences on the left Click Add Payout Routing Rule. When you add a new payout routing rule, it won\u2019t affect reservations that have already begun\u2014only payouts for reservations that begin after the change will be affected.", "question": "Managing more than one payout method"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is accuracy. Giving travelers a sense of who you are and what your listing has to offer can help them feel more comfortable requesting a reservation. Creating a detailed profile and accurate listing will help attract guests and set their expectations. Your personal profile Your Airbnb profile is the first opportunity you have to introduce yourself to travelers and get them excited about staying with you. Use a photo that clearly shows your face, share some details about your hosting style, and add a fun fact about yourself. Your listing An accurate and informative listing lets potential guests know what to expect from you space:   Use high-quality photos, write a detailed description of the space, select the correct room type, and highlight the amenities you have.   Make clear what isn\u2019t available to guests\u2014if you don\u2019t have reliable hot water, say so.   Let guests know if there are parts of the listing that are off-limits, like a shared backyard or the attic.   Provide detailed House Rules that address the situations that will matter to your guests. If you don't want your guests bringing other people into the space, tell them in advance.   Be honest and candid about the unexpected factors that will impact your guests' stay. If your neighbors just started a noisy construction project, your guests deserve to know. Pricing Guests will evaluate the value of your listing, so it's important to set a price that balances expectations with what your listing has to offer. When you're setting your price, you may want to start with Airbnb's tips and make adjustments based on similar spaces nearby. You can always set weekend rates, or adjust your prices to match seasonal trends. If you're a first-time host, consider lowering your rate so that you can get a few bookings and reviews, gain some experience, and start developing your hosting style.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "What does it mean to have an accurate profile and listing?"},
{"answer": "Payoneer is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If the option appears for your selected country, you'll be able to sign up for Payoneer\u2014if you already have a Payoneer card, contact them to connect Airbnb payouts to your existing account. Signing up with Payoneer When you sign up for Payoneer as a new customer with Airbnb, be sure that you enter the same address that you provided on the Airbnb payout method page. After signing up, Payoneer will approve your details or ask for additional information (like a copy of your government issued ID or Social Security card) by email within 2 days. When approved by Payoneer, a card will be mailed to you within 4-15 business days. You need to activate the card to receive funds. If you don't receive the card, please contact Payoneer customer service. Receiving payouts  Payoneer allows you to receive payouts directly to a Payoneer Prepaid Debit MasterCard. Once activated, Airbnb will load your payouts in USD or EUR, depending on your country, and you can view your balance on Payoneer's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and Payoneer typically delivers the funds to your account within 1-3 hours. Additional fees  Payoneer applies fees for certain transactions, some of which are listed below. Additionally, there are fees for transactions originated outside of the Payoneer country of issuance. Please visit Payoneer's Help Center for more information.  Annual Card Account Maintenance: Free - Payoneer's regular $29.95 fee is waived for Airbnb customers Purchase Transaction: Free, except when  transaction is made in a different currency (3% foreign transaction fee) Cash Withdrawal Fee in the US (ATM and in-branch): $1.75 per withdrawal - ATM surcharges may also apply Cash Withdrawal Fee outside the US (ATM and in-branch): $3.15 per withdrawal - ATM surcharges may also apply ATM Withdrawal Decline Fee: $1 per decline ATM Balance Inquiry Fee: $1 per inquiry Card Replacement: $12.95 per replacement card", "question": "How do I use Payoneer to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Never pay for a reservation outside Airbnb's secure, on-site payment system. If a host or guest asks to pay for a reservation outside our on-site payment system, report the message by clicking  in the message thread with that person.   Airbnb host payouts are available through Western Union in some countries. To see if Western Union is available to you as a payout method:    Go to Account on airbnb.com. Select Payout Preferences on the left. Click Add Payout Method. After entering your address, you'll see a list of your payout and currency options.  If Western Union isn\u2019t listed, it's not available as a payout method for your country. If Western Union is available and you choose it as your payout method, enter your name as it appears on your government ID, including your first, middle, and last names. To collect your payouts, your official ID will need to match your account information. Collecting Western Union host payouts If you choose Western Union as your payout method, you'll receive a unique confirmation number (called an MTCN) in an email from Airbnb 1-2 business days after each reservation begins. You need this number to pick up your money from a Western Union Quick Cash agent location. Western Union payouts expire after 30 days. Fees and conditions  Western Union processing fee: A $10 USD fee is deducted from each Western Union transaction to cover processing costs. Minimum payout amount: A minimum payout of $60 USD is required before your payout will be sent. Maximum payout amount: The maximum Western Union transaction amount is $2000 USD. If your payout is more than $2000 USD, it\u2019s divided into several smaller transactions. Western Union can\u2019t process identical sums on the same day, so if you have a payout of $4000 or more, only $2000 can be processed per day. Currency and exchange rate: Western Union payouts are sent in USD. Western Union sets any exchange rates between USD and your local currency. Additional fees: Additional fees may be required by the local government. These are not set or charged by Airbnb.", "question": "I'm a host. Will Airbnb send payouts through Western Union?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Never pay for your reservation outside of Airbnb. If someone asks you to pay for a reservation outside our on-site payment system, report it to us\u2014just look for the flag icon  in your message thread. Learn more.                      If you're a host, Airbnb can send you your payouts through international wire transfer. An international wire (or international wire transfer) is an electronic payment service for transferring funds. A wire transfer is considered international when Airbnb sends funds in a currency different from your local currency from a bank outside your country.         Your bank may charge a fee to receive a foreign currency. If the funds are transferred using an intermediate bank, the intermediate bank may also deduct fees from the payout. Airbnb can't inform you on how much you'll be charged to receive an international wire. In addition, Airbnb is not responsible for any fees deducted during the international wire, by your bank, or by the intermediary bank.                      If you're a host and want to receive your payouts via international wire, please enter your local banking information in your payout preferences, even if your bank works with a specific intermediary bank. Airbnb's bank will take care of processing the international wire without the intermediary bank information.", "question": "I'm a host. Can Airbnb send my payouts by international wire transfer?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Once you\u2019ve found a listing for your trip, we recommend messaging the host to doublecheck the availability of the space for your dates. Message the host before requesting Unless you have found an Instant Book listing, you\u2019ll have to request that the host accept your stay. It\u2019s a good idea to message the host before requesting, since they can answer questions about their home, as well as let you know it\u2019s available. To contact a host from the listing page, click Contact Host and ask the host any questions you have. Most hosts respond within a few hours. Keep in mind that you may be in different time zones or the host may not have Internet access at the moment. The host isn\u2019t responding If a host hasn't responded, consider reaching out to other hosts in the area. You can message as many hosts as you'd like, so it's up to them to respond to you in a timely fashion or risk losing their chance at having you as a guest.  Sending multiple requests Unless you're planning on renting multiple locations for the same dates, make sure you don\u2019t submit more than one reservation request at a time, as you may end up booking multiple reservations during the same time period. Related articles   How do I submit a reservation request? How do I cancel a reservation request? How do I view and send messages?", "question": "Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?"},
{"answer": "We've heard from hosts around the world that sometimes they'd like a little extra help with their listing. There are times when they'd love to have someone they trust, like a family member or friend, help out with messaging, check in, and more. Following extensive research into a number of ways we can help, we\u2019ll be introducing a new feature that allows current hosts to add an additional host to their account. This is a simple way to allow a family member or trusted friend to help with some of the hosting responsibilities, without giving someone access to their personal account.    This feature will be available soon.", "question": "What are additional hosts?"},
{"answer": "Yes. Some hosts require guests to sign contracts or rental agreements prior to check-in. For hosts If you require guests to sign a contract, you must disclose the actual contract terms to them prior to booking. The easiest way to do this is to mention the contract in your listing's description, and include the terms in your message thread with the guest. Airbnb can't help enforce any special policies in your contract. For guests Hosts may ask you to sign a contract, but they must disclose this requirement and its terms prior to booking. If you\u2019re not comfortable with the contract, you may want to discuss your concerns with the host or look for another place to stay. If your host asks you to sign a contract that you weren\u2019t notified about before you made the reservation, you can decline to sign the contract and ask your host to cancel your reservation instead.", "question": "Can hosts ask guests to sign a contract?"},
{"answer": "If you\u2019re having trouble getting in touch with your host after you\u2019ve made a reservation, consider a few things:   Most hosts respond within a few hours.     We recommend giving the host a few days to respond. Sometimes things come up or your host might be on a different schedule from you.   Try contacting your host using a different form of communication. For example, you can try reaching them through:        Airbnb message: Find your host in your Messages and send them a note.   Email or phone: Go to Your Trips, click View Itinerary next to your reservation, and use the email address or phone number listed.                         If your trip is starting or about to start, contact us.  Related Content     How do I contact a host? How do I view and send messages? How do I contact Airbnb?", "question": "What if I can't get in touch with my host?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are experienced hosts who provide a shining example for other hosts, and extraordinary experiences for their guests. Once a host reaches Superhost status, a badge will automatically appear on their listing and profile to help you identify them.  We check Superhosts\u2019 activity four times a year, to ensure that the program highlights the people who are most dedicated to providing outstanding hospitality. The Superhost Terms &amp; Conditions apply. Airbnb doesn't endorse or sponsor any host, including Superhosts, or their listings.  Related Articles     How do I become a Superhost?   What benefits do Superhosts receive?", "question": "What is a Superhost?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "If you want to contact a host before booking a reservation or after a trip, send them a message on Airbnb. Once a trip is confirmed, you can message, email, or call the host to communicate until the trip has ended. Before booking a reservation If you want to find out more about a listing or host before booking a reservation, you can message the host on Airbnb. Make sure to review the listing page (for example, reviews and amenities) to clarify anything you need from the host. To send a message:   On airbnb.com, go to the listing for the host you want to contact.     Click Contact Host on the listing page.   Enter the dates and number of guests for your trip. You can adjust this information before booking.   Write your message and click Send Message.  For your safety and privacy, you can\u2019t call or email hosts before your reservation is accepted. Learn more about why it\u2019s good to keep communication and transactions on Airbnb. Once a trip is confirmed If you have an accepted reservation, you can call or email the host, or message them on the site to communicate about your trip. You can find the host\u2019s email and phone number in the message thread for your trip, where you can also send the host a message. After a trip After a trip, you can send a message to your host in your Inbox if you have anything you need to follow up with them about. If you have any issues that you need to resolve, you can work through payment issues in the Resolution Center on the site.  Related Content     What if I can't get in touch with my host? How do I view and send messages? What is the Resolution Center?", "question": "How do I contact a host?"},
{"answer": "When you book a place on Airbnb, you\u2019re making arrangements to stay in someone\u2019s home. Each host has their own style of hospitality, starting with how they like to get to know their guests. Some hosts want to approve reservations, while others are comfortable letting you book their place instantly without waiting for approval. 1. Complete Your Profile In either case, it\u2019s important to know that Airbnb is a community that relies on trust. Complete your profile before you request a reservation with a host, so they can know a little bit about you when they confirm. Your profile should include photos and verifications, especially because some hosts require guests to have a profile photo or Verified ID in order to book. 2. Find the Right Place With over 800,000 unique listings around the world, you\u2019ll want to make sure the place you choose has everything you need for a comfortable and memorable trip. When searching for a place, make sure to include your dates and number of guests to get the most accurate pricing. Read reviews, descriptions, house rules, and amenities for each place to see if it\u2019s the right fit for your trip. You can always contact the host if you have any questions about their home. 3. Book It! You\u2019ve found the perfect place, and now it\u2019s time to make it official. This is where the host\u2019s preferred way of booking will determine how you\u2019ll confirm your reservation. Instant Book For hosts who don\u2019t want to approve each reservation, you\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Instant Book. Like the name suggests, you can confirm a reservation at these places right away. Learn more about Instant Book. Request to Book Many hosts prefer to approve reservations before they\u2019re final. In this case, you\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Request to Book. To submit a reservation request, you\u2019ll need to enter your payment details. Hosts have 24 hours to accept your request, and your reservation is automatically confirmed once they do. Learn more about submitting a reservation request. Pre-approvals and Special Offers If you decide to contact the host to ask questions before attempting to book, the host may respond to your message by inviting you to make a reservation with either a pre-approval or Special Offer. A pre-approval is an invitation to finish booking for the dates and number of guests you noted in your message. A Special Offer gives the host the opportunity to provide special pricing, dates, and other reservation details before you book. Learn more about booking a pre-approval or Special Offer.", "question": "How do I book a place on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Guidebooks let hosts suggest local spots, like restaurants, grocery stores, parks, and attractions. If you add a Guidebook to your listing, your recommended places will appear on the map on your public listing page.  Some cities also have city guidebooks, which are combined lists of recommendations that hosts have added to their own guidebooks. Add a host guidebook to a listing To create your guidebook:   Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com. Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit. Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu. Click Guidebook. Under a category, enter a business name or address of a favorites place. Write a short recommendation and any tags that apply. Click Add. You'll need to create a separate host guidebook for each of your listings. You can only create a host guidebook once you've completed the steps to list your space. Since these guidebooks are public, you\u2019ll have to remove your recommendations if you don\u2019t want them to appear for all guests. Edit or delete a host guidebook You can edit or remove recommendations from your guidebook, or delete your guidebook altogether.   Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Guidebook Next to the business you want to edit, click Edit If you want to remove the business, click Delete. Otherwise, you can edit your recommendation. To delete your guidebook, you need to remove each recommendation individually. Host recommendations in city guidebooks With city guidebooks, recommendations from host guidebooks are used to provide a detailed picture of what guests can do in that city. Three recommendations will be featured and will include a link to the host\u2019s guidebook and listing. These featured recommendations will change over time. To determine which recommendations to use, our algorithms look at the most interesting content created around each location, based on informativeness, uniqueness, and representation of the place. We then show the most helpful recommendations which seem to provide the most compelling information for guests. The best way to be featured in city guidebooks is to continue expanding your own host guidebook with your favorite places in the area. Can\u2019t find a city guidebook  At this time, not all cities have a city guidebook but we\u2019re actively looking to add more. The best way to help your city get a guidebook is to expand your own host guidebook with your recommendations. Once enough hosts create robust guidebooks, this information can be gathered together in a city guidebook. Leave feedback about guidebooks If you have any thoughts or concerns about guidebooks, you can provide us direct feedback. While not all feedback will make it to the site or receive a response, we encourage you to share your knowledge and opinions.", "question": "What's a Guidebook?"},
{"answer": "To help you decide where to stay, you can search by neighborhood for a number of cities. To search by neighborhood:   Search for a city on airbnb.com.     Under the price range slider, click More Filters.   Next to the Neighborhoods section, choose a neighborhood you want to search. If you don\u2019t see this section, that city doesn\u2019t have any neighborhoods recorded on Airbnb. You can also browse neighborhoods by clicking different locations on the map. How do I know which neighborhood to choose? If you\u2019re not sure which neighborhood is the best fit for your trip, you can use the Neighborhoods page for your destination to get a description of each neighborhood based on research with locals and city experts. In the Airbnb app, you can also provide extra information about your trip to see more personalized homes and neighborhoods. You can choose filters such as property type (for example, apartment or castle) and neighborhood type (for example, \u201chip\u201d or \u201cquiet\u201d). You can also indicate if you\u2019re traveling with any children or pets. Using this information, along with a number of other search and ranking factors, we\u2019ll display neighborhoods and homes for your specific trip, as well as \u201cPopular\u201d listings based on our existing ranking factors.  Related articles   What are Neighborhoods? How can I edit my neighborhood?", "question": "How do I search by neighborhood?"},
{"answer": "Neighborhoods are a way to help travelers make informed decisions about where to stay when planning a trip. When visiting a new city, it can be helpful to know which neighborhoods may fit your interests and the purpose of your trip. How neighborhoods are determined On Airbnb, neighborhoods boundaries are based on research with locals and city experts. A cartographer helps make sure these boundaries are accurate and up-to-date. This research also informs the detailed descriptions, photos, and stories about each neighborhood. Search by neighborhood You can search by neighborhood to narrow your options when looking for a listing. You can also get additional information about neighborhoods, such as location, access to transportation, and map, by  browsing all available neighborhoods for the city you're interested in. Give direct feedback or suggest changes Neighborhood information is updated partly by using feedback from the community. If you feel that neighborhood information is incorrect, you can give us direct feedback. While we can\u2019t respond to everything, we encourage you to share your knowledge and opinions because the Neighborhoods team uses feedback to improve our platform. Can\u2019t find a neighborhood While we\u2019ve recently updated neighborhood information for popular travel destinations worldwide, not all locations have neighborhoods on Airbnb.  Related articles   How do I search by neighborhood? How do I edit my neighborhood?", "question": "What are Neighborhoods?"},
{"answer": "If you want to see if a space would allow you to bring a pet on your trip, you can check the Amenities section of the listing description or contact the host. Check the amenities Each listing on the site includes a section for amenities. Under the Amenities section below the listing description, check to see if  Pets Allowed is listed. If you don\u2019t see it, or it\u2019s crossed out, it means the host doesn\u2019t allow guests to bring their pets along on their trip. This includes service animals. Contact the host Whether or not the listing says that pets are allowed, you should contact the host to double check. In some situations, they may be willing to make exceptions. But sometimes allergies are an issue, so many hosts can\u2019t accept pets. Pets already at the listing If you want to know if the hosts have a pet at the listing, you can also check In the  Amenities section of the listing. If you see  Pet Owner  listed, that means the host has a pet on the premises, although it doesn\u2019t necessarily mean that a guest can bring a pet. Contact the host with any questions about pets at the listing.", "question": "How can I tell if a listing is pet-friendly?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about. Related Content   How do I book a place on Airbnb? How do I search for listings? How do I view and send messages? What is Instant Book?", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "Hosts on Airbnb offer a wide variety of spaces, ranging from shared rooms to private islands. While you can filter searches to look for something more specific (like boats or castles), all listings are grouped into the following three room types:    Shared rooms     Private rooms   Entire homes/apartments  Shared rooms Shared rooms are for when you\u2019d like a comfy, communal experience, and don't mind sharing a space with others. When you book a shared room, you'll be sharing your bedroom and the entire space with other people. These rooms work best for the flexible traveler looking for new friends and a budget-friendly stay. Private rooms Private rooms are great for when you prefer a little privacy, but still value a local connection. When you book a private room, you'll have a bedroom to yourself, but will share some spaces with others. With a private room, you'll be able to wake up to greet your new friends in the kitchen and have the freedom to bid them adieu at bedtime. Entire homes/apartments Entire homes/apartments are best if you're seeking a home away from home with complete privacy and the freedom to cook breakfast in your pajamas. With an entire home/apartment, you'll have the whole space to yourself. You can be your own host, make your own dinner, and remember to treat your listing with the respect and courtesy you would at your own home.", "question": "What does the room type of a listing mean?"},
{"answer": "When you search for a place to stay on Airbnb, you can narrow your options by using filters and reading the descriptions of places to check if they\u2019d be a good fit for your trip.   To search for a place to stay:        On airbnb.com, enter your destination, travel dates, and number of guests.         Click Search.     If you want, use the filters (for example, price range) to narrow your options. Click More Filters to see all available filters.     Scroll through the listings or use the map to find listings in the location you want.     Click on a listing to open it. To learn more about it, read the description, check the available amenities, review the House Rules, and see reviews that other guests have left for the host.     If you have any questions, send the host a message. Or, if you\u2019re ready to book, request to book the listing (or use Instant Book if the host has it turned on).         You can also save your favorite places to a Wish List, which you can save for later or share with your friends. Related articles   How do I use search filters? What are house rules? How do reviews work? How do I view and send messages? What is Instant Book?", "question": "How do I search for listings?"},
{"answer": "To keep track of listings you\u2019re thinking of booking, or simply find fun and inspiring spaces, you can create a wish list. Create a wish list From a listing page: On a listing you want to add to a wishlist, click Save to Wish List under the pricing details Click the drop-down menu &gt; Create new Give your new wish list a name (for example, \u201cLos Angeles Trip\u201d or \u201cRomantic Getaway\u201d) and choose whether to keep the wish list private or public Click Save To add more listings to this wish list, click Save to Wish List on a listing page and choose your wish list. Note: New wish lists may take a couple minutes to show up on the website.  Related articles   How do I manage my wish list? How do I search for listings?", "question": "How do I create a wish list?"},
{"answer": "The Community Center is a place to connect with other hosts, share stories, ask for advice, and get updates from the Airbnb team. You can also plan or join meetups. Getting started Here are a few of the features the Community Center offers:    Conversations: Ask a question, share a story, or connect with other hosts by starting a conversation\u2014or joining in on an existing one. Tags: Add topic tags to your conversations to help people find and follow them. We\u2019ll show trending topics on the Community Center homepage. You can also follow a topic to get updates whenever new content is posted. Top contributors: We\u2019re so lucky to have a vibrant and active community of hosts, and we want to make sure your amazing contributions to the community get recognized\u2014that\u2019s why you\u2019ll see a Top Contributors section on the homepage. New to hosting? Use this section to find a community expert. Direct messaging: Want to ask another host a private question? You can now direct message other community members right from the Community Center. Meetups: Meetups are a great way to meet other hosts, share best practices, and get advice from people like you. Over 12,000 meetups have been organized by hosts in 85 cities around the world.    Available languages The Community Center is available in English, French, Italian, German, Spanish, Brazilian Portuguese, Korean, Dutch, and Japanese. We plan to offer support more languages soon.   Cities Cities boards are location-specific boards you can use to connect with other hosts in your area. You can view any Cities board to connect with hosts in that area. Don\u2019t see your city yet? Use the Where in the world? board to start a location-specific conversation. You can use tags to help other community members find your post. Managing the Community Center This is your community. You own the discussions, and the Community Center will ultimately rely heavily on your level of engagement.  The Community Center will be largely self-moderated, but you may also see a faces from the Airbnb team around from time to time to to share updates, answer tricky questions, and help keep things clean and safe.  Related Content   Visit the Community Center", "question": "What is the Airbnb Community Center?"},
{"answer": "Once you've created a wish list to keep track of listings you like, you can share it with others, add and remove listings, or delete the wish list altogether. Share a wish list You can share a wish list with the people you want to travel with and allow them to add listings and notes to the list. On airbnb.com, go to Wish Lists. At the top of the page, choose My Wish Lists. Open your wish list. At the top of the list, click the plus button. Add the email addresses for the people you want to plan with and add a note. Click Send Invites. To remove someone from the wish list, hover over their profile picture in the wish list and click Remove.   The people you\u2019ve shared with can now add and remove listings on the wish list and make comments on the existing listings.  Remove a listing from a wish list On airbnb.com, go to Wish Lists At the top of the page, choose My Wish Lists Open your wish list Hover over the listing you want to remove and click Remove  Delete a wish list On airbnb.com, go to Wish Lists At the top of the page, choose My Wish Lists Open the wish list you want to delete Next to the name of the wish list at the top, click Edit On the right, click Delete Wish List &gt; OK   Related articles   How do I create a wish list? How do I search for listings?", "question": "How do I manage my wish list?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "No\u2014if your reservation request isn\u2019t accepted by the host or expires without a response, there\u2019s no cost for the reservation or any Airbnb service fees. Depending on your payment method, you may see a temporary authorization or a refunded charge after a reservation request is declined or expires. Temporary authorizations and refunded charges Before you submit a reservation request, you'll see whether your chosen payment method will place a hold (called an authorization) or charge on your account for the amount of the reservation. If your payment method is authorized Some payment methods or locations require that the full amount of the reservation is authorized at the time of your request. If your reservation is accepted, the authorization will turn into a real charge and the amount will be deducted from your payment account. If the reservation request is declined or expires, you\u2019ll either see the authorization disappear altogether or appear as a refund in your payment account. Depending on the processing time of your bank, the release of the authorization may take up to 7 business days. If your payment method is charged Some payment methods or locations require that the full amount of the reservation is charged at the time of your request. If your reservation request is accepted, the charge remains and your reservation is confirmed. If the reservation request is declined or expires, you\u2019ll be refunded immediately and automatically. Depending on the processing time of your bank, the refund may take up to 10 calendar days to process.  Related articles   When do I pay for a reservation? How do I pay for my reservation?", "question": "Do I have to pay if my reservation request isn't accepted by the host?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "If you\u2019ve submitted a reservation request with a host on Airbnb, a couple of things are required to confirm your reservation:            You\u2019ve added your payment information       The host accepts your request (unless you sent a reservation request for a place with Instant Book turned on, which will automatically accept the request)          When a host accepts your request, you'll receive an email and, depending on your account notification settings, a text (SMS) and push notification from Airbnb. Your reservation request status will also change to Accepted.     Check your reservation status     To check your reservation status from your computer:                    Your Trips: Pending and declined reservations show their status, and you can see if a reservation is accepted if you see the option to \u201cChange Reservation\u201d             Your Inbox: Look for the status next to each message thread              Read more about what each reservation status means or how to make reservation requests. Related articles   How do I submit a reservation request? What does each reservation status mean?", "question": "How do I check if my reservation is confirmed?"},
{"answer": "If your reservation request is declined by the host or expires, meaning the host didn\u2019t respond within 24 hours, no charge is made for the reservation and you\u2019re free to book with another host. We urge our hosts to keep their calendars up to date and respond to requests in a timely manner. But, sometimes situations come up that prevent this from happening. We recommend messaging several hosts before submitting a reservation request to ask about their availability and ask any other questions you have. Temporary authorizations Your payment method may be temporarily authorized for a charge when you request a reservation, but this authorization is voided and released back to the payment method if your request is declined or expires. We complete a charge only when a reservation request is confirmed. Related articles   Should I book if I have not heard back from the host? How do I check if my reservation is confirmed? How do I view and send messages? What does my reservation status mean?", "question": "What happens if my reservation request is declined or expires?"},
{"answer": "Yes. If the request hasn\u2019t been accepted by the host, you can cancel the request and send a new one with the updated reservation details.             To change a reservation request:   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com   Find your reservation request under Pending Trips   Click Cancel Request and then OK to confirm   If you want, send a new request with your changed dates or number of guests   Related articles   Change a confirmed reservation as a guest Change a confirmed reservation as a host", "question": "Can I make changes to a pending reservation request?"},
{"answer": "When you book a place on Airbnb, you\u2019re making arrangements to stay in someone\u2019s home. Each host has their own style of hospitality, starting with how they like to get to know their guests. Some hosts want to approve reservations, while others are comfortable letting you book their place instantly without waiting for approval. 1. Complete Your Profile In either case, it\u2019s important to know that Airbnb is a community that relies on trust. Complete your profile before you request a reservation with a host, so they can know a little bit about you when they confirm. Your profile should include photos and verifications, especially because some hosts require guests to have a profile photo or Verified ID in order to book. 2. Find the Right Place With over 800,000 unique listings around the world, you\u2019ll want to make sure the place you choose has everything you need for a comfortable and memorable trip. When searching for a place, make sure to include your dates and number of guests to get the most accurate pricing. Read reviews, descriptions, house rules, and amenities for each place to see if it\u2019s the right fit for your trip. You can always contact the host if you have any questions about their home. 3. Book It! You\u2019ve found the perfect place, and now it\u2019s time to make it official. This is where the host\u2019s preferred way of booking will determine how you\u2019ll confirm your reservation. Instant Book For hosts who don\u2019t want to approve each reservation, you\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Instant Book. Like the name suggests, you can confirm a reservation at these places right away. Learn more about Instant Book. Request to Book Many hosts prefer to approve reservations before they\u2019re final. In this case, you\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Request to Book. To submit a reservation request, you\u2019ll need to enter your payment details. Hosts have 24 hours to accept your request, and your reservation is automatically confirmed once they do. Learn more about submitting a reservation request. Pre-approvals and Special Offers If you decide to contact the host to ask questions before attempting to book, the host may respond to your message by inviting you to make a reservation with either a pre-approval or Special Offer. A pre-approval is an invitation to finish booking for the dates and number of guests you noted in your message. A Special Offer gives the host the opportunity to provide special pricing, dates, and other reservation details before you book. Learn more about booking a pre-approval or Special Offer.", "question": "How do I book a place on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment. Related articles   How do I check if my reservation is confirmed? Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Once you\u2019ve found a listing for your trip, we recommend messaging the host to doublecheck the availability of the space for your dates. Message the host before requesting Unless you have found an Instant Book listing, you\u2019ll have to request that the host accept your stay. It\u2019s a good idea to message the host before requesting, since they can answer questions about their home, as well as let you know it\u2019s available. To contact a host from the listing page, click Contact Host and ask the host any questions you have. Most hosts respond within a few hours. Keep in mind that you may be in different time zones or the host may not have Internet access at the moment. The host isn\u2019t responding If a host hasn't responded, consider reaching out to other hosts in the area. You can message as many hosts as you'd like, so it's up to them to respond to you in a timely fashion or risk losing their chance at having you as a guest.  Sending multiple requests Unless you're planning on renting multiple locations for the same dates, make sure you don\u2019t submit more than one reservation request at a time, as you may end up booking multiple reservations during the same time period. Related articles   How do I submit a reservation request? How do I cancel a reservation request? How do I view and send messages?", "question": "Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?"},
{"answer": "As long as your reservation hasn\u2019t been accepted by the host, you can cancel the reservation. You won\u2019t be charged for the reservation or Airbnb service fees.   But, if you cancel after the reservation has been accepted, your reservation will be subject to the terms of the cancellation policy selected by the host. See how to check the status of a reservation request. Cancel a pending reservation request     Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com     On the reservation request you\u2019d like to cancel, click Cancel Request    Related articles   How do I check if a reservation is confirmed? What is a cancellation policy? How do I cancel a reservation as a guest?", "question": "How do I cancel a reservation request?"},
{"answer": "You\u2019ll be charged for the total cost of your reservation when it's confirmed, which happens as soon as:    You\u2019ve added your payment information     Your host accepts your request (or the request is accepted immediately with Instant Book)  Regardless of how far in advance your reservation is booked, we hold the payment for the host until 24 hours after check-in to make sure everything goes smoothly. Long term reservations For reservations that are 28 nights or longer, you\u2019ll be charged the first month\u2019s payment when the host confirms the reservation. You\u2019ll then be charged a recurring monthly payment during your reservation. In other words, you won't make a second payment until one month after you check in. Security deposits If you make a reservation with a host who asks for a security deposit, you won\u2019t be charged on the deposit unless a host makes a successful claim against the deposit after your trip.  Related Content   How do I check if a reservation is confirmed? How do I pay for my reservation? How do I pay for my long term reservation? How does Airbnb handle security deposits? What is a payment authorization?", "question": "When will I be charged?"},
{"answer": "If you\u2019re ready to book a place on Airbnb, you can send a request to the host to book a reservation. If you\u2019re unsure about the listing or its availability, you can also send a message to the host. To send a reservation request:   On a listing, click Request to Book.    If you see Instant Book, the host is allowing you to book their place instantly. Your reservation will be automatically confirmed after step 4.     Review your reservation details to make sure everything is correct.   Add your payment information, including any coupon code you may have.   Agree to the policies and terms, including the host\u2019s cancellation policy and house rules.   Wait for the host\u2019s response. The host has 24 hours to reply, but most reply within a few hours. Some hosts require that you complete the Verified ID process before confirming a reservation, which allows the host to get more information about who they\u2019re hosting in their home. If your request is accepted, you\u2019ll be charged in full for the reservation. If the host declines the request or doesn\u2019t respond within 24 hours, no charge is made and you can try booking those dates with someone else. Related articles   How do I view and send messages? How do I use a coupon code? When do I pay for a reservation? How do I check if my reservation is confirmed? What happens if my reservation request is declined or expires? What is Instant Book?", "question": "How do I submit a reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "All pricing information is included when you book a reservation using Airbnb. After paying, there are a few situations where you may owe more money.  Know when to pay more  You may owe more money if:      You change your reservation \u2014 for example, you need to add another guest       Your host makes a claim on your security deposit    Your host require taxes to be paid at check-in\u2014this needs to be clearly stated on the listing prior to booking    If a host asks you for more money than what you paid on the site and the extra charge wasn\u2019t stated in the listing or in the message thread, you can dispute the charges in the Resolution Center. Never pay a host directly for these charges.  How to pay after booking the reservation  If you need to pay the host more money, use the Resolution Center on the site. You should keep all payment transactions on Airbnb because Airbnb can\u2019t help with any issues related to off-site or cash payments. Related Content   Why should I only pay and communicate through Airbnb? What is the Resolution Center? How do I change a reservation as a guest? What happens if a host makes a claim on my security deposit? What is occupancy tax?", "question": "What if a host asks for more money?"},
{"answer": "If you book a long term reservation that lasts 28 nights or more, you\u2019ll be charged a first month down payment and the rest will be collected in monthly installments. At the moment, you can only pay for a long term reservation on a computer. First month down payment Once you\u2019ve booked a long term reservation, you\u2019ll be charged for the first month of your stay upfront. We\u2019ll hold this payment until 24 hours after check-in before giving it to the host. Payment for future months After check-in, we\u2019ll charge you monthly, using the same payment method, for the duration of your reservation. In other words, you won\u2019t make a second payment until approximately one month after you check in. The monthly price you pay is locked at the beginning of the reservation.  You can see your total reservation cost and successful payments made on your billing receipt. Cancellation policy The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice of lease termination.", "question": "How do I pay for my long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of running Airbnb, we charge guests a service fee every time a reservation is confirmed. The amount of this service fee varies and is based on a percentage of the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). The exact amount of the service fee is displayed before guests confirm a booking. Guest service fees are typically 6-12% but can be higher or lower depending on the specifics of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. We also charge hosts a host service fee to cover the cost of processing payments. Find the service fee After entering the exact dates and number of guests for a reservation, you\u2019ll see the service fee included as part of the booking details. The exact amount of the service fee is also located on:   The checkout page before submitting a reservation request   Any guest billing receipt VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT). Trip cancellations and reservation changes See the effect on service fees for the following situations:   If a reservation request is retracted, expires or is declined, we don\u2019t charge the guest a service fee   If a guest cancels a reservation, the service fee charged to the guest is non-refundable   If a guest chooses to be refunded after a host cancellation, the service fee charged to the guest is refunded    If a reservation is changed, the service fee charged to the guest adjusts with to the new subtotal", "question": "What are guest service fees?"},
{"answer": "No\u2014if your reservation request isn\u2019t accepted by the host or expires without a response, there\u2019s no cost for the reservation or any Airbnb service fees. Depending on your payment method, you may see a temporary authorization or a refunded charge after a reservation request is declined or expires. Temporary authorizations and refunded charges Before you submit a reservation request, you'll see whether your chosen payment method will place a hold (called an authorization) or charge on your account for the amount of the reservation. If your payment method is authorized Some payment methods or locations require that the full amount of the reservation is authorized at the time of your request. If your reservation is accepted, the authorization will turn into a real charge and the amount will be deducted from your payment account. If the reservation request is declined or expires, you\u2019ll either see the authorization disappear altogether or appear as a refund in your payment account. Depending on the processing time of your bank, the release of the authorization may take up to 7 business days. If your payment method is charged Some payment methods or locations require that the full amount of the reservation is charged at the time of your request. If your reservation request is accepted, the charge remains and your reservation is confirmed. If the reservation request is declined or expires, you\u2019ll be refunded immediately and automatically. Depending on the processing time of your bank, the refund may take up to 10 calendar days to process.  Related articles   When do I pay for a reservation? How do I pay for my reservation?", "question": "Do I have to pay if my reservation request isn't accepted by the host?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb\u2019s payment system is designed to make transferring money between guests and hosts as simple and reliable as possible. Here\u2019s how it works:   Guests pay Airbnb when they book a place   Airbnb releases the money to hosts 24 hours after the guest checks in Using Airbnb\u2019s payment system is required to make a reservation, and it helps ensure that both parties are protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation policies, Guest Refund Policy, and other safeguards. Airbnb automatically includes service fees in each transaction, and some government-required taxes where applicable.  Related topics for guests: Prices &amp; Fees Payment Methods Related topics for hosts: How Payouts Work Payout Preferences", "question": "How does Airbnb process payments?"},
{"answer": "You\u2019ll be charged for the total cost of your reservation when it's confirmed, which happens as soon as:    You\u2019ve added your payment information     Your host accepts your request (or the request is accepted immediately with Instant Book)  Regardless of how far in advance your reservation is booked, we hold the payment for the host until 24 hours after check-in to make sure everything goes smoothly. Long term reservations For reservations that are 28 nights or longer, you\u2019ll be charged the first month\u2019s payment when the host confirms the reservation. You\u2019ll then be charged a recurring monthly payment during your reservation. In other words, you won't make a second payment until one month after you check in. Security deposits If you make a reservation with a host who asks for a security deposit, you won\u2019t be charged on the deposit unless a host makes a successful claim against the deposit after your trip.  Related Content   How do I check if a reservation is confirmed? How do I pay for my reservation? How do I pay for my long term reservation? How does Airbnb handle security deposits? What is a payment authorization?", "question": "When will I be charged?"},
{"answer": "The total price of a reservation on Airbnb is based on a few factors. Note that the price is charged in full once a host accepts your reservation request (or if you use Instant Book).    Costs determined by the host:          Nightly price: Nightly rate decided by the host           Cleaning fee: One-time fee charged by some hosts to cover the cost of cleaning their space      Extra guest fees: One-time fee charged by some hosts to cover other costs related to using their space     Costs determined by Airbnb:   Airbnb service fee: Guest service fee charged for all reservations to help Airbnb run smoothly and offer 24/7 customer support Other costs that may be included:   Currency exchange fee   Value Added Tax (VAT): Tax charged to guests who live in the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan (charged as JCT).   Local taxes\u2014Any taxes charged based on the location of the host's listing    Note: Security deposits are only charged if the host needs to make a claim. Related Content   When do I pay for a reservation? How does Airbnb handle security deposits? Can I use more than one payment method to pay for a reservation? How do I pay for my long-term reservation?", "question": "How is the price determined for my reservation?"},
{"answer": "No. The currency you pay in is controlled by your payment method and, in some cases, by your country. It\u2019s not possible to manually choose what currency you'll use to pay. When you select your country and payment method on the checkout page, the currency in which you'd be charged will be clearly displayed before you confirm your reservation request. Exchange rates and currency conversion  When the currency you\u2019re paying with is different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we convert your payment automatically. The base exchange rate uses data from one or more third parties, such as OANDA. It\u2019s updated regularly, but may not be identical to the real-time market rate. If you\u2019re paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we also charge a 3% conversion fee on your total cost; the conversion fee accounts for Airbnb\u2019s holding costs and foreign currency risks. The exchange rate used will display on the checkout page before you confirm your booking. Third-party fees  If you pay in a currency that\u2019s different from the designated currency of your payment method, your provider or third-party payment processor may apply a currency conversion rate or fees to your payment. Contact your provider (for example, your credit or bank card issuer) for information on what fees may apply, since they\u2019re not controlled by Airbnb. Currency view You can view Airbnb listings in many currencies, but this won\u2019t affect what currency you\u2019ll be asked to pay in. To change your currency view, scroll to the bottom of any page on airbnb.com and click on the currency field to select what currency you want to view listing prices in.", "question": "Can I pay with any currency?"},
{"answer": "Your payment information is collected when you submit a reservation request. Once the host accepts your request, or if you book a reservation with Instant Book, your payment method will be charged for the entire amount at that time. Whether the reservation is two days or two months away, we hold the payment until 24 hours after check-in before giving it to the host. This hold gives both parties time to make sure that everything is as expected. Changing your payment method If you've requested to book a listing but the host hasn't responded yet, you can cancel your reservation request and make another request with a different payment method. Once your reservation is confirmed, there isn't a way to change your payment method at this time. Long term reservations If you book a reservation for 28 nights or more, you\u2019ll be charged a first month down payment when the reservation is confirmed. Then, the rest of the nights will be charged on a monthly basis. Security deposits If your listing requires a security deposit, you won\u2019t be charged unless the host files a successful claim within 48 hours of your checkout.   Related articles   How do I submit a reservation request? How does Airbnb process payments? What methods of payment does Airbnb accept? Can I pay with any currency? How do I pay for my long term reservation? How does Airbnb handle security deposits?", "question": "When do I pay for a reservation?"},
{"answer": "When you book a place on Airbnb, you\u2019re making arrangements to stay in someone\u2019s home. Each host has their own style of hospitality, starting with how they like to get to know their guests. Some hosts want to approve reservations, while others are comfortable letting you book their place instantly without waiting for approval. 1. Complete Your Profile In either case, it\u2019s important to know that Airbnb is a community that relies on trust. Complete your profile before you request a reservation with a host, so they can know a little bit about you when they confirm. Your profile should include photos and verifications, especially because some hosts require guests to have a profile photo or Verified ID in order to book. 2. Find the Right Place With over 800,000 unique listings around the world, you\u2019ll want to make sure the place you choose has everything you need for a comfortable and memorable trip. When searching for a place, make sure to include your dates and number of guests to get the most accurate pricing. Read reviews, descriptions, house rules, and amenities for each place to see if it\u2019s the right fit for your trip. You can always contact the host if you have any questions about their home. 3. Book It! You\u2019ve found the perfect place, and now it\u2019s time to make it official. This is where the host\u2019s preferred way of booking will determine how you\u2019ll confirm your reservation. Instant Book For hosts who don\u2019t want to approve each reservation, you\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Instant Book. Like the name suggests, you can confirm a reservation at these places right away. Learn more about Instant Book. Request to Book Many hosts prefer to approve reservations before they\u2019re final. In this case, you\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Request to Book. To submit a reservation request, you\u2019ll need to enter your payment details. Hosts have 24 hours to accept your request, and your reservation is automatically confirmed once they do. Learn more about submitting a reservation request. Pre-approvals and Special Offers If you decide to contact the host to ask questions before attempting to book, the host may respond to your message by inviting you to make a reservation with either a pre-approval or Special Offer. A pre-approval is an invitation to finish booking for the dates and number of guests you noted in your message. A Special Offer gives the host the opportunity to provide special pricing, dates, and other reservation details before you book. Learn more about booking a pre-approval or Special Offer.", "question": "How do I book a place on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "A pre-approval is a way for host to let guests know that their listing is available when asked about a potential reservation. Once pre-approved, the guest can automatically confirm a booking for the specific dates provided. Hosts When you pre-approve a guest\u2019s inquiry, you give them permission to automatically confirm a booking for specific dates. The dates won\u2019t be blocked on your calendar, so you can pre-approve multiple guests at one time.   Guests have 24 hours to confirm a booking that has been pre-approved. After 24 hours, the guest can still request to book your listing with the price offered during the pre-approval, unless you remove the pre-approval. You can remove the pre-approval at any time in the message thread. Guests If a host has sent you a pre-approval, your booking isn\u2019t confirmed until you\u2019ve clicked Book It in the message thread with the host and added your payment information. Hosts can send pre-approvals to many potential guests, so if you\u2019ve found the perfect space, make sure to complete the booking process as soon as possible.  You have 24 hours to accept a pre-approval before it expires. If 24 hours have passed, you can still accept the pre-approval but your host will have to approve your request before your reservation is confirmed. Related articles   How do I pre-approve a guest\u2019s stay or remove a pre-approval? How do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest?", "question": "What is a pre-approval?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account. Related articles   How do I turn Instant Book on or off as a host? How does check-in work?", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Boleto payment is only available for guests in Brazil, and may not be available to all customers at all times. Additionally, Boleto cannot be used for Instant Book listings, for reservations that are longer than 28 nights, or for reservations that start in fewer than 7 days. When you submit a reservation request and select Brazil as your country of payment, you\u2019ll see Boleto Banc\u00e1rio as an option in the payment type menu. Choosing this option will present a form that you\u2019ll need to complete with your details. After the host accepts your reservation, Airbnb will issue a Boleto under your name. You can print it out and pay it through a bank branch, ATM or in a lottery store. Alternatively, you can copy the barcode number and pay via internet banking or through your bank's app on your smartphone. We\u2019ll email you a copy of the Boleto so you\u2019ll always have access to it. After the Boleto is issued to you, you\u2019ll have 24 hours to make the payment, and we\u2019ll confirm it within 96 hours. Your reservation may appear with the status Awaiting Payment for up to 96 hours. Please keep in mind that this method of payment can take longer if you submit a reservation request on the weekend or within holiday periods. In case of cancellation, Airbnb will issue a refund and our payment processing partner will send you an email with instructions for how to claim the refund.", "question": "How do I pay for a reservation with Boleto?"},
{"answer": "After you\u2019ve booked a reservation, you can add guest names and a business address to your billing receipt. Once the reservation ends, you won\u2019t be able to make any changes to the receipt.  Information like passport numbers, birthdates, and tax identification numbers can\u2019t be added to a receipt.  Add guest names  To add guest names to your receipt, you have to update the names on your itinerary.      Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com       Next to the trip you want to edit, click View Itinerary    Next to Guests, click Manage Guests    Add or remove names of the other guests staying at the listing    The names are automatically updated on the billing receipt      Add a business address         Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com       Next to the trip you want to edit, click View Itinerary    Next to Billing, click Detailed Receipt    On the receipt, click Add billing details    Add the business address and other relevant information    Click Save    Note: Adding VAT details to your business information is documentation only and won't affect VAT charged on your reservation. VAT invoices can't be changed. Learn more about how VAT may apply to you.   Related articles   How do I find my trip itinerary or receipt? What is Airbnb for Business?", "question": "How can I add a guest or business address to my receipt?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "If you choose to pay with a credit card when you make a reservation request, you can edit or remove the credit card information later from your Airbnb account, as long as a default payment method remains.  At this time, it's only possible to add credit cards from the Payment Methods section of your account, although you can choose to add other types of payment methods on the checkout page when you book. Removing or adding a payment method To view the credit card information on your Airbnb account: Go to Account on airbnb.com Select Payment Methods on the left  If you\u2019ve added more than one credit card as a payment method, you\u2019ll be able to remove any card that is not your default payment method by clicking Remove. You won\u2019t be able to remove a card that\u2019s currently being used on a pending or active reservation. To have a card appear first on your list of available payment methods the next time you make a reservation, click Set Default.  You can click Add Payment Method to add new credit card information to your account at any time.", "question": "How do I remove credit card information from my Airbnb account?"},
{"answer": "No, Airbnb can't split your reservation cost across multiple payment methods. To make a reservation, you'll need to make your payment with a single payment method.  If you need to update your payment method for a long-term reservation or an unsuccessful charge, please contact us for assistance.  If you have a confirmed reservation that isn't long-term, remember that you've already paid in full through our payment system\u2014so you won't need to change or update your payment method to enjoy your trip.", "question": "Can I use more than one payment method to pay for a reservation?"},
{"answer": "No. The currency you pay in is controlled by your payment method and, in some cases, by your country. It\u2019s not possible to manually choose what currency you'll use to pay. When you select your country and payment method on the checkout page, the currency in which you'd be charged will be clearly displayed before you confirm your reservation request. Exchange rates and currency conversion  When the currency you\u2019re paying with is different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we convert your payment automatically. The base exchange rate uses data from one or more third parties, such as OANDA. It\u2019s updated regularly, but may not be identical to the real-time market rate. If you\u2019re paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we also charge a 3% conversion fee on your total cost; the conversion fee accounts for Airbnb\u2019s holding costs and foreign currency risks. The exchange rate used will display on the checkout page before you confirm your booking. Third-party fees  If you pay in a currency that\u2019s different from the designated currency of your payment method, your provider or third-party payment processor may apply a currency conversion rate or fees to your payment. Contact your provider (for example, your credit or bank card issuer) for information on what fees may apply, since they\u2019re not controlled by Airbnb. Currency view You can view Airbnb listings in many currencies, but this won\u2019t affect what currency you\u2019ll be asked to pay in. To change your currency view, scroll to the bottom of any page on airbnb.com and click on the currency field to select what currency you want to view listing prices in.", "question": "Can I pay with any currency?"},
{"answer": "The Resolution Center lets you request or send money for things related to your Airbnb trip. To open a refund or payment request, go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions.      You have up to 60 days after your reservation's checkout date to submit a Resolution Center request. Asking for help from Airbnb     If you\u2019re unable to reach an agreement, you can ask Airbnb to make the final decision 72 hours after the request was opened. To involve Airbnb:                 Wait 72 hours after you open the request       Go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions        Select the correct reservation       Click Involve Airbnb      When you involve Airbnb, our team will be notified and a dedicated team member will be assigned to your case. They\u2019ll review the information provided by you and your host or guest, before making a final decision. In some cases, we may need to contact you to gather additional information, before we can make a decision.", "question": "What is the Resolution Center?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "When you book a listing with a security deposit, your payment details are stored but not charged or authorized for the deposit unless the host makes a claim. The host has 48 hours from your checkout date to make a claim on the deposit for damages to their property. What to expect if a host reports damages If your host makes a claim on your security deposit, here\u2019s the process that will be followed:   We'll ask for documentation from the host, and as soon as we receive it, we'll ask them to contact you through Airbnb\u2019s Resolution Center to discuss the claim. If your host sends you a request, you'll be notified by email and through an alert on your Dashboard.     Reply to your host's request in the Resolution Center within 48 hours. Your response will depend on whether or not you agree to the amount requested by the host:            Agree to the amount: Click Accept in the Resolution Center. We'll process your payment and send it to your host, which usually takes 5 to 7 business days.             Don't agree to the amount: Click Involve Airbnb in the Resolution Center and let us know why you think your host's claim is invalid. We'll contact you and give you 48 hours to respond to us so we can mediate.           In any case, we'll make sure you and your host are represented fairly and gather any details and documentation needed to reach a resolution. Most security deposit claims will be resolved within one week. Documentation from hosts Communication through email is required in order to collect needed documentation from the host, which will include photos and/or video along with receipts, invoices, written estimates, or links to comparable items denoting actual cash value for repair or replacement. If we determine money is owed based on documentation and communication from both parties, we will move forward with collecting from the deposit.\u00a0We reserve the right to collect payment from you using the payment details we have on file.", "question": "What happens if a host makes a claim on my security deposit?"},
{"answer": "We support several payment methods, which depend on what country your payment account is located in.    You'll see which payment methods are available to you on the checkout page, before you submit a reservation request. After you select your country, all of your payment details will be shown.  Offline or cash payments are a violation of our Terms of Service, and can result in removal from Airbnb. We prohibit off-site payments because paying outside of Airbnb makes it harder for us to protect your information and puts you at a greater risk of fraud and other security issues.                 Payment options may include:                                                   Major credit cards and pre-paid credit cards (Visa, MasterCard, Amex, Discover, JCB)                                      Many debit cards that can be processed as credit                                      PayPal for select countries                                      Alipay for China only                                      Postepay for Italy only                                      Sofort \u00dcberweisung for Germany only                                      iDEAL for the Netherlands only                                      Boleto Banc\u00e1rio, Hipercard, Elo, and Aura for Brazil only                                                       Google Wallet for US Android App only                                      Apple Pay for iOS App only                              Related Articles              When will I be charged?      Can I pay with any currency?", "question": "What methods of payment does Airbnb accept?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Guests and hosts work out details for checking in, exchanging keys, and checking out directly with each other. There is no online check-in or checkout process. Read below for some guidelines to help you have a smooth check-in. Communication is essential Before the start of the reservation, message your host to figure out check-in and checkout times, make plans for the key exchange, and ask any other questions. Keeping communication in your message thread gives you and Airbnb a clear reference if any issues come up. Also, confirm your contact information and arrival details so you can reach each other in case plans change. Make sure to let each other know if you'll be without access to a phone or the Internet. Know your reservation details After a reservation is confirmed, refer to your itinerary for useful information about your reservation, such as the check-in and checkout time, the listing's address, your host's contact information, and your billing receipt. If there's no check-in or check-out time specified within a listing's description, check-in is 3:00 PM local time and checkout is 12:00 PM local time. Stay tuned to flight information and weather forecasts Look up travel advisories to make sure there is nothing impacting your reservation. With road closures and flight delays, guests and hosts might need a little extra time to safely meet up to exchange keys. Key exchange Many hosts greet guests in person to exchange keys. Others send keys and instructions in the mail, leave them in a lockbox, or have a neighbor meet a guest. The host can decide whether or not to give a guest a key. But, our Guest Refund Policy states that guests need to have reasonable access to the listing they booked. If you decide not to provide keys, you should mention in your listing\u2019s description and house rules that keys will not be available to the guests so people are aware of the situation before booking.", "question": "How does check-in work?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "If you want to share your trip plans with the people traveling with you, add them to your reservation, which allows them to see your itinerary.     On airbnb.com, go to Your Trips   Next to the trip you want to share, click View itinerary   Next to Guests, choose Manage Guests   Add the name and email address of the person coming with you   Click Send Invites   An email will be sent to the traveler and they can see your full itinerary by signing in (or signing up) for Airbnb  If you want to share your itinerary with people not going on your trip, you can add their emails in the message that appears after you\u2019ve confirmed a reservation.", "question": "How do I share trip details with others?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Yes. If the request hasn\u2019t been accepted by the host, you can cancel the request and send a new one with the updated reservation details.             To change a reservation request:   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com   Find your reservation request under Pending Trips   Click Cancel Request and then OK to confirm   If you want, send a new request with your changed dates or number of guests   Related articles   Change a confirmed reservation as a guest Change a confirmed reservation as a host", "question": "Can I make changes to a pending reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Before canceling a reservation, you should check your host\u2019s cancellation policy to see if you\u2019re eligible refund.                                                                       Go to Your Trips.                                                    Next to the reservation you want to cancel, click View Itinerary.                                                  Under \u201cCancellation Policy\u201d, find the host\u2019s policy.                                                  See more information on the different cancellation policies.     Cancel a reservation                    Go to Your Trips.   Next to the reservation you want to cancel, click Change or Cancel.   Choose Cancel Reservation.                                    Related Content   Can I cancel my reservation request? What is a cancellation policy? Extenuating circumstances for guest cancellations", "question": "Cancel a reservation as a guest"},
{"answer": "It depends. Refunds for confirmed reservations can be issued for a variety of reasons, but are typically dependant on the cancellation policy a host has selected for their listing. Situations that are eligible for a possible refund outside of a host\u2019s cancellation policy include:     Host cancellations          Extenuating Circumstances          Cases covered by Airbnb\u2019s Guest Refund Policy       If you\u2019d like to request a refund from your host for another reason, you\u2019ll need to use Airbnb\u2019s Resolution Center. Our Resolution Center allows you to easily connect with your host, discuss a possible refund, and request mediation from an Airbnb team member if you\u2019re unable to reach an agreement. Please note that if you are granted a refund, it will take some time to arrive in your account, dependent on your payment method.", "question": "Can I get a refund?"},
{"answer": "If you need to make a change to a confirmed reservation, you can submit a change request to your guest. Change a reservation Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com. Click Change or Cancel next to the reservation you want to change. Choose Change Reservation. Click Submit Alteration.  If the guest accepts your request, the reservation will be updated and they'll be charged or refunded if necessary. If the request is declined or you don\u2019t receive a response, the reservation will stay the same.  There are a couple of other things to know about submitting change requests: Your chosen cancellation policy will apply based on the new dates. If the dates of the reservation have already passed, you can\u2019t make any changes to the reservation. If you want to change the details of your requested changes, you\u2019ll have to repeat the steps above and remove your request, and then submit a new one. If you changed your pricing, the new reservation will reflect this pricing if your change request is accepted. To request additional funds from your guest, you can do so directly from the Resolutions Center.", "question": "Can I change a reservation as a host?"},
{"answer": "If you need to make a change to a confirmed reservation, you can submit a change request to your host. Change your reservation     Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.     Next to the reservation you want to change, click Change or Cancel.     Choose Change Reservation.     Change the dates of your stay or the number of guests.     Click Submit Alteration.     If the host accepts your request, your reservation will be updated and you\u2019ll be charged or refunded if necessary. If the request is declined or you don\u2019t receive a response, your reservation will stay the same.            There are a couple of other things to know about submitting change requests:     If the dates of your reservation have already passed, you can\u2019t make any changes.   If you want to change the details of your requested changes, you\u2019ll have to repeat the steps above and remove your request, and then submit a new one.   If the host altered their pricing before you requested the change, your new reservation will reflect this pricing.", "question": "Can I change a reservation as a guest?"},
{"answer": "Hosts share their House Rules to set expectations with their guests, like limits on smoking, areas beyond the listing space that are off-limits, and permission to have visitors.  To add or edit House Rules after you\u2019ve listed your space: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Under Hosting, click on Booking Under House Rules, enter your expectations and rules for guests  If a guest breaks a house rule, either before or during their stay, you can cancel their reservation without penalty.  House rules appear on your listing page, and guests must review and agree to them before requesting a reservation. They\u2019re also sent directly to a guest once they\u2019ve a confirmed reservation.", "question": "What are house rules?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb empowers hosts to set and manage their cancellation policies. If a host or guest needs to cancel a reservation, it\u2019s their responsibility to cancel as soon as possible. At times, certain circumstances outside of a host or guest\u2019s control can impact their ability to meet the terms of a reservation. In rare instances, if Airbnb determines that a Guest\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, Airbnb may override the Host's cancellation policy (ex: flexible, moderate, strict) and make refund decisions.  If Airbnb determines that a Host\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances policy, Airbnb may waive the host cancellation penalties outlined in Airbnb\u2019s Terms of Service and Airbnb\u2019s Payments Terms of Service. What might be covered? Valid extenuating circumstances include:  Unexpected death or serious illness of a host, guest or immediate family member  Serious injury that directly restricts a guest\u2019s ability to travel or a host\u2019s ability to host Significant natural disasters or severe weather incidents impacting the location of destination or location of departure Urgent travel restrictions or severe security advisories issued after the time of booking, by an appropriate national or international authority (such as a government office or department) Endemic disease declared by a credible national or international authority (such as the US Center for Disease Control or the World Health Organization) Severe property damage or unforeseen maintenance issues that directly impact the ability to host safely Government-mandated obligations issued after the time of booking  If you need to make a claim Claims can only be considered after a reservation has been canceled. Once you have informed your host or guest and canceled a reservation, if you feel that your reason for cancellation is covered by Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, contact Airbnb for consideration. We generally require claims to be submitted no later than 14 days from the original check-in date and we may require valid supporting documentation.", "question": "Extenuating Circumstances Policy"},
{"answer": "If you\u2019re having trouble getting in touch with your host after you\u2019ve made a reservation, consider a few things:   Most hosts respond within a few hours.     We recommend giving the host a few days to respond. Sometimes things come up or your host might be on a different schedule from you.   Try contacting your host using a different form of communication. For example, you can try reaching them through:        Airbnb message: Find your host in your Messages and send them a note.   Email or phone: Go to Your Trips, click View Itinerary next to your reservation, and use the email address or phone number listed.                         If your trip is starting or about to start, contact us.  Related Content     How do I contact a host? How do I view and send messages? How do I contact Airbnb?", "question": "What if I can't get in touch with my host?"},
{"answer": "Even if you\u2019ve already booked your reservation, it\u2019s your choice whether to accept or decline a host\u2019s offer to book an alternate listing.     Before paying for a reservation     If you don\u2019t yet have a confirmed reservation and the host offers you a different listing from the one you discussed, you can book your reservation at this listing or simply look for a new place. You have no obligation to accept the new listing and you should make sure that it would work for your trip before booking.     After you\u2019ve paid for your reservation     If your host is asking you to stay in a different listing than you originally booked and you\u2019re okay with a switch, either you or your host can change your reservation. Make sure to check the details of the new listing before accepting a change.     If you\u2019re not okay with a switch or your host is asking you to switch without officially changing the reservation on Airbnb, ask the host to cancel your reservation so you can get a full refund or find another home that better accommodates your stay.     After you\u2019ve checked in     If you\u2019ve already checked in and you feel the listing is not what you booked on the site, follow the steps to document the issue and our Guest Refund Policy will make sure you either get the listing you booked or receive a refund. Related articles   How do I change my reservation as a guest? What should I do if something's not missing or not as expected when I check in? How do I check if a reservation is confirmed? How can I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "What if a host informs me that the listing I already paid for is now unavailable but they have an alternative?"},
{"answer": "If you notice that something is missing, not working, or otherwise not what you expected when you check in, contact your host right away. Your host is often in the best position to help you\u2014giving them the chance to fix an issue can be the fastest way to make sure you get what you need, and can continue on with your reservation as planned. In the event that you experience a travel issue, and you and your host aren't able to resolve the issue on your own, please take the following required steps within 24 hours of your check-in to make sure you're covered by our Guest Refund Policy:      Contact us to document the issue and place a hold on the host's payment.   Message your host on Airbnb to notify them of the issue. We'll need to verify this in your account.     Take photographs to document the situation. It's important that your photos show what's happening and where (in relation to the rest of the room or space) so we can verify what's going on.    If your host is unreachable or unresponsive, we'll work on issuing you an adequate partial refund if you decide to stay, or a full refund if you decide to leave, as we deem appropriate. You can see a complete explanation of coverage in our Guest Refund Policy.  The Guest Refund Policy doesn't apply beyond 24 hours after check-in, but we can always help you mediate with your host if you've tried reaching out with no response.                          Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "What should I do if something's missing or not as expected when I check in?"},
{"answer": "In the event that your reservation is canceled by a host, you have two options:   Transfer your payment to a new Airbnb reservation    Get a refund  Transfer your payment to a new Airbnb reservation Your money is immediately available to use towards a new reservation. Once you've found a new place, we'll automatically transfer your original payment to your new reservation request, along with any eligible credit from Airbnb.  Request a refund If you\u2019d prefer not to book another place on Airbnb, you can ask for a full refund online at any time. To get a refund:        Go to Your Trips from airbnb.com.     Find your canceled reservation.     Click Request a refund.      To ask for a refund, you\u2019ll need to log into your airbnb.com account on a computer. At the moment, refunds can't be requested using the Airbnb app or mobile website.", "question": "What to do if your host cancels"},
{"answer": "If your host already canceled your reservation, you can transfer your payment to a new Airbnb reservation or request a refund.  If your host let you know that they can\u2019t accommodate your stay anymore, don\u2019t cancel for them. If you cancel, you may not be eligible for a full refund depending on the host\u2019s cancellation policy. Instead, send your host a cancellation request to make sure you receive a full refund. To send a cancellation request:   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com     Next to the trip, click Change Reservation   Click Cancel Reservation   Choose My host needs to cancel   Click Send a Cancellation Request If your trip starts within a week, the host has 24 hours to respond to the request. Otherwise, they have 48 hours to respond. If your host accepts the request, or doesn\u2019t respond, you\u2019ll have the option to find a new space for your stay or request a full refund including service fees. If they decline the request, your host is letting you know that they can still host your stay.", "question": "What should I do if my host needs to cancel?"},
{"answer": "The Resolution Center lets you request or send money for things related to your Airbnb trip. To open a refund or payment request, go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions.      You have up to 60 days after your reservation's checkout date to submit a Resolution Center request. Asking for help from Airbnb     If you\u2019re unable to reach an agreement, you can ask Airbnb to make the final decision 72 hours after the request was opened. To involve Airbnb:                 Wait 72 hours after you open the request       Go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions        Select the correct reservation       Click Involve Airbnb      When you involve Airbnb, our team will be notified and a dedicated team member will be assigned to your case. They\u2019ll review the information provided by you and your host or guest, before making a final decision. In some cases, we may need to contact you to gather additional information, before we can make a decision.", "question": "What is the Resolution Center?"},
{"answer": "Business travelers can use their regular Airbnb accounts to book business travel\u2014all you need to do is link your work email address to your Airbnb account so we can confirm that you work for the company you say you work for.    If you need to switch the account your work email is linked to, or just no longer want your accounts to be linked, follow the steps below to unlink (or relink) your work email address and your personal Airbnb account:               Go to Profile on airbnb.com                          Scroll down to Business Travel             Click the X to unlink your accounts or the + Add work email to relink them  If you unlink your accounts, you won't be able to use your company's payment information to pay for your business travel reservations. Note: If you're the only travel manager for a company's account, we recommend you add another travel manager before unlinking your accounts.  Related Articles   How do I join my company's business travel account? What is Airbnb Business Travel?", "question": "How do I unlink or relink my work email address and Airbnb account?"},
{"answer": "If your company uses Concur\u2019s TripLink service, you\u2019ll need to link your Airbnb and Concur accounts to have your Airbnb reservation receipts automatically uploaded to your Concur account. Link your accounts  To link your Airbnb and Concur TripLink accounts: Go to Airbnb in the  Concur App Center, and click Connect Log in to your existing Airbnb account or, if you don\u2019t already have an account, create a new one  Once your accounts are linked, you can have the receipt for any Airbnb reservation appear in your Concur account by marking the box next to Send this booking to Concur on the reservation request checkout page.  Unlink your accounts To unlink your Airbnb and Concur TripLink accounts: Go to Account on airbnb.com Select Settings on the left side Under Unlink From Concur, click Unlink", "question": "How do I expense my business trip using Concur TripLink?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Business guests can identify a reservation as a business trip by selecting Business travel on the checkout page. Any notes you add in the What\u2019s the purpose of this trip? box will be sent your company\u2019s travel manager. Choosing Business travel won\u2019t tell your host that you\u2019re traveling for work, but sharing information about your trip in a message to your host is a great way to help them understand your business travel needs. Already booked your trip? You can identify your reservation as a business trip at any time from your itinerary. Scroll down and select the checkbox next to This is a business trip in the Business Travel section.", "question": "How do I identify a reservation as a business trip?"},
{"answer": "After you\u2019ve booked a reservation, you can add guest names and a business address to your billing receipt. Once the reservation ends, you won\u2019t be able to make any changes to the receipt.  Information like passport numbers, birthdates, and tax identification numbers can\u2019t be added to a receipt.  Add guest names  To add guest names to your receipt, you have to update the names on your itinerary.      Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com       Next to the trip you want to edit, click View Itinerary    Next to Guests, click Manage Guests    Add or remove names of the other guests staying at the listing    The names are automatically updated on the billing receipt      Add a business address         Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com       Next to the trip you want to edit, click View Itinerary    Next to Billing, click Detailed Receipt    On the receipt, click Add billing details    Add the business address and other relevant information    Click Save    Note: Adding VAT details to your business information is documentation only and won't affect VAT charged on your reservation. VAT invoices can't be changed. Learn more about how VAT may apply to you.   Related articles   How do I find my trip itinerary or receipt? What is Airbnb for Business?", "question": "How can I add a guest or business address to my receipt?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Once your company is enrolled in Airbnb for Business, you\u2019re ready to start planning your next work trip. Once you've verified your work email address, start a search on the Airbnb for Business homepage. From there you can easily filter by location, type of space, and the amenities each host offers. Business Travel Ready listings also have a badge to help travelers find them. Just look for the briefcase .  Related Articles     What makes a listing Business Travel Ready? How do I join my company's business travel account? How do I identify a reservation as a business trip?", "question": "How do I search for listings for my business trip?"},
{"answer": "Business Travel Ready listings must be an Entire Home/Apt and an eligible property type (house, apartment, bed &amp; breakfast, townhouse, loft, or condo). The listing must be no smoking, and can\u2019t have pets on the property. The space Many business travelers are new to traveling on Airbnb, so we\u2019ve limited Business Travel Ready listings to certain property types to help make sure guests know what to expect when they arrive. As a part of this, and because of the potential for allergies and other sensitivities, we also ask that Business Travel Ready listings are smoke-free properties and don\u2019t have pets living in the space while the guest is there. If a pet lives in your space, but won\u2019t be there during your guest\u2019s stay we ask that you\u2019re aware of traveler\u2019s potential allergens and make sure your listing is cleaned before your guest\u2019s arrival. Amenities The listing must also have the following Business Travel Ready amenities:   Wireless Internet A laptop-friendly workspace 24-hour check-in (this could be a lockbox, doorman, keyless entry or similar 24-hour access) A smoke detector A carbon monoxide detector Essentials (toilet paper, clean towels, and fresh linens) An iron Hangers A hair dryer Shampoo  Smoke and carbon monoxide detectors are an important part of making Airbnb a trusted travel option for companies. As part of our commitment to guest safety, Airbnb offers free smoke and carbon monoxide detectors for hosts: www.airbnb.com/home-safety. Reviews and response rate Listings must have at least 3 star rated reviews before they can be eligible for Business Travel Ready status. For listings with 3 or more star rated reviews, at least 60% of both the listing\u2019s primary reviews, and the listing\u2019s reviews for cleanliness and accuracy must be 5 star reviews. Hosts of Business Travel Ready listings also must have responded to 90% of booking requests within 24 hours over the last year. Cancellations Hosts of Business Travel Ready listings must provide a 7-day cancellation commitment to reservations. If a listing has a cancellation within 7 days of a confirmed check-in date, it can't be considered for Business Travel Ready for 1 year from the cancellation date. Eligibility Listings and their hosts are evaluated for business travel readiness on a rolling basis. Keep in mind that you and your listing need to continue to qualify after the initial evaluation in order to maintain Business Travel Ready status. If you\u2019re a host, learn more or get started now. Questions? Review the Business Travel Ready Terms &amp; Conditions.", "question": "What makes a listing Business Travel Ready?"},
{"answer": "To join your team's business travel account on Airbnb, you can link your work email address to your existing personal account, or, if you don't already have an Airbnb account, create a new account with your work details. Linking your work email address to your personal Airbnb account just lets us confirm that you work for your company\u2014you\u2019ll still use your personal email address and existing password to sign in to your account. Link your existing Airbnb account   If you already have an Airbnb account:     Go to airbnb.com/business     Log in to your Airbnb account     Enter your work email address and click Add Email  You should see a verification email in your work inbox soon. Once you've received it, click Verify Business Email, then follow the steps on screen to complete your verification. Create a new account If you need to create an Airbnb account:     Go to airbnb.com/business     Click Get Started     Choose a way to sign up and follow the steps on screen           Once you've created an account, you should see a verification email in your work inbox. Click Verify Business Email in that email and follow the steps on screen to complete your verification.  \"Please enter a valid company email\" error At this time, you can't join a company's business travel account or register your company using public domains (ex: gmail.com, hotmail.com). Even if you already have a personal Airbnb account, make sure you're entering the email address associated your company's domain (ex: name@companyname.com) on airbnb.com/business. We'll help you link your personal account and work email address from there.", "question": "How do I join my company's Airbnb for Business account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb for Business makes it easy to travel for work without sacrificing the comforts of home.  Business travelers If your company is already enrolled in Airbnb for Business, join their account by visiting airbnb.com/business-travel. Business Travel Ready listings Some homes have a badge to indicate that they\u2019re Business Travel Ready. These listings meet certain requirements for home type, amenities, check-in, reviews, responsiveness, and host commitment\u2014you\u2019ll see them identified with a briefcase . Travel managers For travel managers, the Airbnb for Business program provides better transparency and more accurate reporting for their company. If you manage your company's travel arrangements, sign your company up for Airbnb for Business by visiting airbnb.com/business/signup. Once you\u2019re enrolled, learn more about using your travel manager account and dashboard.  Related Articles   I'm a travel manager. How do I get started with Airbnb for Business? How do I join my company's business travel account?", "question": "What is Airbnb for Business?"},
{"answer": "When you complete your first business stay at an Airbnb listing, we\u2019ll give you a $50 coupon to use towards your next Airbnb trip.  How do I get the coupon code? You\u2019ll receive an email with your personalized $50 coupon code after you've checked in to your qualifying reservation. Promotion details   The coupon code will be sent to the email address you use to log in to your Airbnb account The $50 coupon is valid for one year The coupon can only be used towards one reservation There are no restrictions on destination or travel dates Once applied, the coupon can't be refunded, even if the reservation is canceled  Related Articles   How do I apply a coupon code? How do I identify a reservation as a business trip?", "question": "Airbnb for Business: $50 promotion"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.  Related articles   How do host cancellation penalties work?  Can I reply to a review? Extenuating Circumstances for Host Cancellations?", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "At this time, reviews can\u2019t be written for canceled reservations. If you\u2019d like to provide feedback for your host, you can send them a quick message using your Airbnb message thread.  Hosts: when you cancel a reservation, a review is automatically added to your listing\u2019s page indicating that a reservation was canceled. These reviews are one of the penalties for canceling and can\u2019t be removed. Learn more", "question": "Can I leave a review for a canceled reservation?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "We believe in free speech, transparency, and clear communication. When creating a review, we ask that you stick to the facts. The best reviews provide constructive information that helps the community make better decisions.           Airbnb's default position is not to censor, edit, or delete reviews. However, we reserve the right to remove reviews that violate our content policy.         We don't allow:                  Reviews that do not represent a user\u2019s personal experience            .         Reviews unrelated to the actual reservation (ex: political,             religious, or social commentary).         Content that endorses or promotes illegal or harmful activity or         violence, or is profane, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, threatening,          or discriminatory.         Content that violates another person\u2019s or entity\u2019s rights,              including intellectual property rights and privacy rights (ex:              publishing another person\u2019s full name, address or other identifying         information without permission).        Content that is proven to be used as extortion.       Content that refers to an Airbnb investigation.                Related Content   How do reviews work? Can I delete a review? Can I reply to a review?", "question": "What are Airbnb's review guidelines?"},
{"answer": "Yes, but only within 14 days of when you received the review\u2014we\u2019ll post it directly below the review you're responding to.   To write a response: Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com Click Reviews Select Reviews About You Find the review you\u2019d like to respond to and click Leave a Response  If you're a host and received a review related to a cancellation learn more.", "question": "Can I reply to a review?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "The payout you\u2019ll receive is your nightly rate minus the 3% host service fee. To view information about any of your payouts, visit your Transaction History. Guests pay a 6-12% service fee to Airbnb in addition to the cost of your listing, which is why the total price guests see is higher than your payout.  Here are some things that can impact your payout: Your weekly discount or monthly discount may have been applied to the reservation  Weekend pricing or custom pricing may have been applied to the reservation The Airbnb payment system rounds to the nearest whole amount Where applicable, Value-added tax (VAT) may be added on top of the Airbnb service fee If you receive a booking inquiry, but want to charge a different price, you can send the guest a Special Offer. If you want to change the price of an accepted reservation, you\u2019ll need to submit a request to your guest. Related articles   How do I set prices for long-term stays? How do I set up weekend pricing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? What is VAT and how does it apply to me?", "question": "How do I calculate my payout?"},
{"answer": "If you need to cancel a guest\u2019s reservation:    On your computer Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com Find the reservation you need to cancel Select Change or Cancel to start the cancellation process On the Airbnb app Go to Host Home section of the mobile app Select the reservation you need to cancel Tap Cancel Reservation to start the cancellation process  On mobile browser You can\u2019t currently cancel a reservation on Airbnb's mobile website. Use your desktop computer or download our iPhone or Android app to cancel a reservation.    Cancellation Penalties Canceling a guest's reservation can have serious implications on their trip, so penalties will be applied unless there is an extenuating circumstance.  Related Articles   How do the cancellation penalties work? What is the Guest Refund Policy? Extenuating Circumstances for Host Cancellations", "question": "Cancel a reservation as a host"},
{"answer": "If you need to make a change to a confirmed reservation, you can submit a change request to your guest. Change a reservation Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com. Click Change or Cancel next to the reservation you want to change. Choose Change Reservation. Click Submit Alteration.  If the guest accepts your request, the reservation will be updated and they'll be charged or refunded if necessary. If the request is declined or you don\u2019t receive a response, the reservation will stay the same.  There are a couple of other things to know about submitting change requests: Your chosen cancellation policy will apply based on the new dates. If the dates of the reservation have already passed, you can\u2019t make any changes to the reservation. If you want to change the details of your requested changes, you\u2019ll have to repeat the steps above and remove your request, and then submit a new one. If you changed your pricing, the new reservation will reflect this pricing if your change request is accepted. To request additional funds from your guest, you can do so directly from the Resolutions Center.", "question": "Can I change a reservation as a host?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can always see and update the cancellation policy for your listing. The cancellation policy is automatically set as Flexible when you list your space. View or change policy To view or change your cancellation policy:    On airbnb.com, go to Your Listings    Next to the listing you want information for, click Manage Listing and Calendar   On the left side of the screen, click Check-in and your policy will be listed  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space. If you update your cancellation policy, it only applies to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.  Available cancellation policies There are a few cancellation policies you can choose from:        Flexible: full refund up until 1 day prior to arrival, except fees.               Moderate: full refund up until 5 days prior to arrival, except fees. Strict: 50% refund up until 1 week prior to arrival, except fees.   There are additional policies that are only available to select hosts:  Super Strict: 50% refund up until 30 days prior to arrival, except fees.\u00a0Available by invitation only\u00a0and\u00a0requires an increased host fee of 5%. Super Strict 60 Days: 50% refund up until 60 days prior to arrival, except fees.\u00a0Available by invitation only and also requires an increased host fee of 5%.    For all long-term reservations (28 nights or more), the Long Term policy is automatically applied: Long Term: first month down payment, 30-day notice for lease termination. Automatically applied to all reservations of 28 nights or more.  If your guest cancels the reservation, your payout is determined by the cancellation policy you had in place at the time of booking. You can refund your guests more than the policy allows.", "question": "How can I see or change the cancellation policy for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Guests want high-quality, accurate listings with hosts that offer and good trip experiences. Here are a few things you can do to make your listing stand out. Complete each section of your listing A complete listing helps guests know what to expect from your space. Make sure you: Describe your space: Make your title and description attractive, detailed, and informative. Clearly explain what makes your space unique, including any amenities you offer or rules you have.  Upload high-quality photos: Your photos are the guest\u2019s first impression of your space on the search results page.  Set expectations: Lay out expectations for guests in the House Rules and House Manual sections of your listing.   Use your reviews to improve The quantity and quality of reviews from past guests can impact your search performance. Use your reviews and ratings to learn how you can improve your guest\u2019s experience.  Make it easier for guests to book Respond quickly to booking inquiries and reservation requests to show guests that you\u2019ll be an attentive, welcoming host. Turning on Instant Book can also help attract last-minute reservations. Set a competitive rates Take a look at what other hosts in your area are charging and use a similar price. Set seasonal pricing to help your listing stay competitive during the off-season.  Learn from other hosts Trade tips with other hosts\u2014Find a meetup in your area so that you can ask other hosts about how they stand out during slow months. Read more about how to optimize your listing for the off-season.", "question": "How do I make my listing more competitive?"},
{"answer": "What is Instant Book? Instant Book is a host setting which lets guests who meet your requirements automatically book your space. Instant Book will apply to all available dates on your calendar.  Benefits of Instant Book   Convenience: Book guests without having to respond to each request.   More guest interest: Guests can use filters to search for listings that can be booked instantly. Instant Book listings are more popular with guests since they\u2019re able to more easily plan their trip.    Search placement: Instant Book positively affects your response rate for your listing, which can improve your listing\u2019s placement in search results.   Superhost Status: Instant book can also help you reach Superhost status, which requires that you maintain a 90% response rate  Related Content   Instant Book settings Prepare to host What are house manuals and house rules?", "question": "Learn about Instant Book"},
{"answer": "If you want to see the status of your reservation, you can find your status in your Inbox on the right side of the message thread with the guest or host. Once you\u2019ve found your status, you can see the details of the status below. Reservation statuses Inquiry: A guest sent a message to a host about certain dates, but hasn't submitted a reservation request. In response, the host can send a message, pre-approve, send a Special Offer, or decline the dates of the inquiry. Reservation Request: A guest sent a message to a host by submitting a booking request for specific dates. In response, the host will need to either accept or decline the request within 24 hours before it expires. Pending: A guest is waiting for a host to respond to a reservation request. The host has 24 hours to respond before the request expires. Confirmed: A host accepted a guest's reservation request or the request was accepted automatically with Instant Book. Airbnb has collected full payment from the guest and the booking is complete. Declined: A host declined a guest's reservation request. No charge is made to the guest. Expired: A host took more than 24 hours to respond to a pending reservation request. If the host wants to accommodate the expired request, the host will have to send a pre-approval or Special Offer, or the guest will need to send another reservation request. Canceled: A host or guest canceled a confirmed reservation. Pre-Approval: A guest has contacted the host about specific dates and the host has responded by inviting them to book the dates. If the guest accepts the pre-approval request within 24 hours, their reservation will be confirmed. Special Offer: A guest has contacted the host about specific dates and the host has responded by inviting them to book the dates with a different price than what is listed on their calendar. If the guest accepts the special offer within 24 hours, their reservation will be confirmed. Awaiting Payment: A host chose to accept a guest's reservation request, but the guest's payment didn\u2019t go through. The guest has 24 hours to successfully update their payment information for the reservation to be accepted. Otherwise, the reservation will be canceled without penalty. Action Required: A guest submitted a reservation request to a host who requires they complete Verified ID, and they haven't completed the process yet. The request is on hold until Verified ID has been confirmed. Closed: The guest is no longer looking for a place to stay for the dates they requested. Not Possible: A guest contacted a host about specific dates and the host responded with a Special Offer or pre-approval, but some or all of the dates are no longer available on the host's calendar.", "question": "What does each reservation status mean?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book lets guests who meet your requirements and agree to your house rules to book your space without requesting approval.       Booking settings You can use Guest requirements and House rules to set requirements for guests that book your space.  In addition to Airbnb's requirements, you can also require guests to provide Airbnb with a government-issued ID and/or a 4.5 out of 5 star rating, including cleanliness and communication. Guests will need to agree to your House Rules before booking. If you feel like you are ever uncomfortable with your guests\u2019 behavior, you can cancel penalty-free. Availability settings You can use Reservation preferences and Calendar sync to help you manage when guests can book, how much advance notice you need, and whether you want time blocked before or between reservations.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Tips to get your listing ready Keep an updated calendar so that you\u2019ll only get bookings when you\u2019re available. Use your calendar settings to control when and for how long guests can book your space, when guests can arrive, and to add preparation time between reservations.  Import and sync other calendars you use for your space. Decide whether you\u2019d like all of your guests to have verified their ID before they\u2019re able to book your space. Write check-in instructions and include contact information, wifi passwords, your neighborhood guide, house rules, and any other vital information guests need to get situated and comfortable. Tips to get your home ready Provide a way for guests to access keys and check in even when you\u2019re not around.  Bulk-buy amenity items you offer guests. Soap, bottled water, or snacks are a good start.  A few sets of sheets and towels will help you ready your space quickly without having to deal with laundry. Consider getting professional help with cleaning and management. Many hosts include a small cleaning fee to offset the cost of hiring a professional.  Get to know your guests before they arrive by checking out profiles or starting a conversation to set the tone for their stay.", "question": "Prepare to host"},
{"answer": "If you list your space on Airbnb and other websites, you can prevent multiple guests from booking the same dates by syncing your Airbnb calendar with your other calendars. Calendar importing Calendar importing allows you to automatically keep your Airbnb calendar up to date with an external calendar that supports the iCalendar format, including Google calendar or the calendar on HomeAway or VRBO. To import a calendar:                              Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Sync Calendars, select Import calendar                 Paste your calendar\u2019s URL in the Calendar address (URL) field Name your calendar Click Import calendar                                  If you edit an external calendar that syncs with your calendar on Airbnb, it will take a few hours for those changes to be visible to guests viewing your listing. Calendar exporting                      Calendar exporting lets you view your Airbnb calendar on an external calendar that supports the iCal format. To export your calendar in iCal format and add it to your external calendar: To export your calendar                               Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Sync Calendars, select Export calendar                 Copy and paste the Airbnb calendar link into your iCal applications                        Related Content               How do I change my reservation settings?       How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?", "question": "How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?"},
{"answer": "If you don\u2019t want to receive any inquiries or requests, you can either snooze or deactivate your listing.  Turning your listing off doesn\u2019t affect your confirmed reservations.  Snooze your listing for a set period of time To pause your listing and hide it from search results for a set period of time:   Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to snooze Select Snoozed in the drop-down menu on the bottom-left Enter the Start date and End date Your listing will automatically reactivate when the timeframe you set is over. The day before your listing reactivates, you'll get a reminder email. Temporarily deactivate your listing To deactivate your listing:  Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to deactivate Use the drop-down menu on the bottom-left to select Unlisted You can reactivate your listing at any time from the Manage Listings page.  Permanently deactivate your listing To permanently deactivate your listing:  Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to deactivate Select Basics on the left-hand side of the screen Click deactivate this listing at the bottom of the page   You won't be able to permanently deactivate your listing if you have any upcoming reservations or reservation requests. Past reviews of your listing will remain on your public profile\u2014they cannot be removed. If you would like to cancel your Airbnb account entirely,  learn how to cancel your account.", "question": "How do I snooze or deactivate my listing?"},
{"answer": "To make your listing public in search results and on your profile page:  Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to activate Select Listed in the drop-down menu on the bottom-left  Keep in mind that once you change your status to listed, it can take up to an hour for this update to be reflected in search results. If you don\u2019t want to receive any inquiries or requests, you can either snooze or deactivate your listing.", "question": "How do I activate my listing?"},
{"answer": "For the best experience using the Airbnb site, we suggest using the most up-to-date version of Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox. Browser developers frequently make improvements to provide you with a faster, more secure online experience. Newer browsers also support a wider range of designs and features than older browsers. If you prefer to use Internet Explorer, please upgrade to IE9 or higher. Many features of the Airbnb website don't work with older versions of Internet Explorer\u2014and we often can't provide technical support if you're using an outdated browser.", "question": "Which Internet browsers work best on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "A listing is automatically assigned to a neighborhood based on its address and this neighborhood can\u2019t be edited. The best way to make sure your listing\u2019s neighborhood is correct is to make sure your address is as accurate as possible. How boundaries are determined Neighborhood boundaries are based on research with locals and city experts. A cartographer helps make sure these boundaries are accurate and up-to-date, and we\u2019re always looking for ways to improve how we use boundaries. Since neighborhoods evolve over time, we are continuously updating our maps to increase their accuracy. If your listing\u2019s neighborhood is a subset of a larger neighborhood, or if two neighborhoods overlap, your listing may show in search results for both neighborhoods. How \u201cneighborhood types\u201d are defined On the mobile app, guests have the ability to filter their search by neighborhood type (for example, \u201cquiet\u201d or \u201chip\u201d). These descriptions allow guests to see the most relevant neighborhoods that best fit their trip, and were chosen based on research on the most common words guests use to describe a neighborhood they want to stay in. At this time, guests are asked in the review flow after checkout to choose which neighborhood types that best fit their listing. These guest selections are combined for every listing in a neighborhood, and the most frequently selected descriptions by guests are used to represent an important aspect of that neighborhood. These neighborhood types may change over time as guests and hosts provide more feedback. Leave feedback about neighborhoods If you feel your listed neighborhood is wrong or information regarding a neighborhood is incorrect, you can provide us direct feedback. While we can\u2019t respond to everything, we encourage you to share your knowledge and opinions because the Neighborhoods team uses feedback to improve our platform. My address is wrong If the address of your listing is wrong, the neighborhood for your home may be incorrect as well. To change the address before your first booking, you can edit your listing. If you\u2019ve already booked a reservation, you\u2019ll need to contact us to change your address. No neighborhood showing for my listing While we\u2019ve recently updated neighborhood information for popular travel destinations worldwide, not all locations have neighborhoods on Airbnb. If no neighborhoods are available, the search results won\u2019t display a neighborhood filter for that location. Describe your neighborhood for guests Many travelers, instead of searching by neighborhood, use listing pages to learn about what location is right for their trip. Write a robust description of your listing so guests know your opinion of the surrounding neighborhood when looking at your listing page. Related articles   What are Neighborhoods? How do I search by neighborhood? How are search results determined?", "question": "How do I edit my neighborhood?"},
{"answer": "You can edit the listing address or map location if they are incorrect. Your exact address will only be seen by guests with confirmed reservations. Edit your listing address  To edit your listing address: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Location Click Edit Address and complete the fields Click Save Address   Edit your listing\u2019s location on the map To edit your listing's location on the map: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Location Click on the map and drag it until the location pin is in the right spot   If you want to edit your address because you've moved to a new location or you're listing a new space, you need to create a new listing rather than updating the address.    Related articles               How do I edit my listing?       How do I edit my neighborhood?       Where can I see how my listing is performing?", "question": "How do I set my map or address?"},
{"answer": "If you didn\u2019t receive an email notification from us, there are a few different steps you can try to figure out the issue. Make sure your email address is correct  We might be sending emails to an old or incorrect email address. To check the email being used: Go to Edit Profile. Look for the Email Address field. Make sure your address is correct. If it\u2019s incorrect, add the correct address, scroll to the bottom of the page, and click Save. Check your email notification settings  We'll only send the emails you tell us you want. Check your notification settings to make sure you haven't opted out of the email type you're looking for: Go to your Notification Settings. Look for the \"Email Settings\" field. Make sure you\u2019ve chosen the email types you want to receive. After adding or removing checkmarks from the right boxes, scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save. Search all messages in your email inbox Sometimes emails can get lost in your inbox. In your email account, search for terms like \"Airbnb\", \"reservation\", \"verification\", or other words related to the email you're looking for. Check your spam and other email filters It's possible your email provider mistakenly sent our messages to your spam or junk folder. To avoid this: Remove Airbnb messages from your spam list Add automated@airbnb.com, express@airbnb.com, and response@airbnb.com to your personal email address book If you have other filters or routing rules in your email account that may have sorted Airbnb emails elsewhere, be sure to check those, too. Check for issues with your email service provider Depending on your provider, emails can take up to a few hours to be delivered. If undelivered or delayed emails continue to be an issue, check with your provider to see if there are any configuration issues or problems with their network that might be affecting your account.", "question": "Why didn't I receive my email notification?"},
{"answer": "Login notifications are an extra security feature that can help alert you if someone accesses your Airbnb account without your permission.      When you turn on login notifications, we\u2019ll send you an email each time someone logs ins. In these emails, we\u2019ll give you information on the type of Internet browser used to access your account, the time your account was accessed, and where we believe it was accessed from.          To turn login notifications on:                   Go to Account         Select Security on the left         Look for Login Notifications and click the check box next to Enable login notifications         Click Save        If you use certain browsers often, you can mark them as trusted. We won\u2019t notify you when your account is accessed from a trusted browser.  Related Articles   What is a trusted browser? My account details changed, but I didn\u2019t update them. What should I do?", "question": "What are login notifications?"},
{"answer": "If you turn on login notifications, you can mark the browser you use to access your Airbnb account often as trusted\u2014when you use a trusted browser to access your account, we won\u2019t notify you.     To mark a browser as trusted:                 Enable login notifications.         Log in to your Airbnb account from the browser you want to trust.         You\u2019ll see a Add to trusted browsers? window appear. Select the option next to Trust this browser.         Click Save.        You should only mark a browser as trusted if you're on a private computer or phone.  Related Articles   What are login notifications? My account details changed, but I didn\u2019t update them. What should I do?", "question": "What is a trusted browser?"},
{"answer": "No. The currency you pay in is controlled by your payment method and, in some cases, by your country. It\u2019s not possible to manually choose what currency you'll use to pay. When you select your country and payment method on the checkout page, the currency in which you'd be charged will be clearly displayed before you confirm your reservation request. Exchange rates and currency conversion  When the currency you\u2019re paying with is different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we convert your payment automatically. The base exchange rate uses data from one or more third parties, such as OANDA. It\u2019s updated regularly, but may not be identical to the real-time market rate. If you\u2019re paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we also charge a 3% conversion fee on your total cost; the conversion fee accounts for Airbnb\u2019s holding costs and foreign currency risks. The exchange rate used will display on the checkout page before you confirm your booking. Third-party fees  If you pay in a currency that\u2019s different from the designated currency of your payment method, your provider or third-party payment processor may apply a currency conversion rate or fees to your payment. Contact your provider (for example, your credit or bank card issuer) for information on what fees may apply, since they\u2019re not controlled by Airbnb. Currency view You can view Airbnb listings in many currencies, but this won\u2019t affect what currency you\u2019ll be asked to pay in. To change your currency view, scroll to the bottom of any page on airbnb.com and click on the currency field to select what currency you want to view listing prices in.", "question": "Can I pay with any currency?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "Being a responsible host means being a considerate tenant, neighbor, and community member. Here are a few things you should consider when talking with others about hosting on Airbnb. Know the rules and regulations Before you start hosting, know what contracts and rules affect you, such as leases, condo board or co-op rules, HOA rules, or rules established by tenant organizations. Make sure you understand and comply with these rules before listing your space. Other laws in your city or state may also affect you, so be sure to review them as well. Talk with your landlord or HOA Talk to your homeowner\u2019s association or landlord about how often you plan to have guests, and how Airbnb builds trust in its community. You can share information about Airbnb\u2019s trust and safety resources, including community reviews and Verified ID. Remind them that you only host people you feel comfortable with. If applicable in your country, you can also explain that Airbnb offers a US$1M Host Guarantee. Talk with your neighbors Neighbors may want to know about many of the same things as your landlord or HOA, as well as more specifics about upcoming bookings, such as names, dates, and other information about your guests. Making sure your neighbors are comfortable might help address some of your landlord\u2019s concerns.  Be a responsible host Here are some things you can do to show your landlord, HOA, and neighbors that you care about the property and your neighbors as much as they do: Set an occupancy limit to only allow groups of a certain size  Share your home and building rules with each guest Provide your guests with phone numbers for emergency responders and a map of emergency exits and evacuation routes Make sure you have a working smoke and carbon monoxide detector Inform neighbors when a guest will be staying in your home With your guests\u2019 permission, share names or Airbnb profile pages", "question": "How should I talk to my neighbors, homeowners association, or landlord about Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We expect hosts to respect their guests\u2019 privacy. You must notify your guests about any security cameras or other surveillance devices at or around your listing, and get consent where required.  The use of surveillance equipment may also be against the law in some places, so make sure you understand your local regulations.", "question": "Can I install video or audio surveillance in my listing?"},
{"answer": "In most states and localities in the United States, guests who stay in a home or apartment for approximately 30 days\u2014the exact number depends on jurisdiction\u2014may establish rights as a tenant. Generally, this means that local tenancy laws could protect them, and you may not be able to remove them from your property without proceeding through required eviction processes in court. For example, in California, Illinois, and New York, a residential tenancy may be created after 30 consecutive days of occupancy. Someone who stays with you for fewer than 30 days generally does not have the rights of a tenant unless there is a written agreement to the contrary, but every state is different. Local laws may differ from state laws regarding residential tenancies. We encourage you to review your local rules and regulations before accepting a long-term reservation. Guests who refuse to leave\u2014and how Airbnb can help These situations are incredibly rare, but if they happen, we'll work with you to try and help resolve the problem with your guest. Should you face such a situation, let our 24/7 support team know\u00a0as soon as possible and we'll get in touch with you. Asking guests to sign a rental agreement If you rent your home or apartment for more than 30 days, consider whether you want guests to sign a rental agreement. If so, you should make these requirements clear in your House Rules before finalizing a booking. Laws governing these subjects vary widely depending on where you live, so be sure to contact a landlord-tenant attorney familiar with your local laws and regulations. Local rent control laws Rent control is a special set of laws that includes limits on rent increases and eviction restrictions. Some local rent control laws may override state law, and while many states or local jurisdictions do not have rent control, other laws may still protect tenants. For these reasons, we recommend you contact your local Rent board, Department of Consumer Affairs, Attorney General, or other agencies to learn more about rent control and rent stabilization and how these rules might impact a long-term reservation. Evicting guests that overstay a long-term reservation Statutes exist in nearly all jurisdictions that permit landlords to use summary proceedings to evict tenants. A summary proceeding is a judicial proceeding that lets a landlord regain possession of leased property in an expedited fashion. You should contact a landlord-tenant attorney or your local county courts to learn more about eviction laws where you live, as they may affect your ability to evict a guest who overstays a long-term reservation.", "question": "What are some things I should consider before hosting long-term guests?"},
{"answer": "When deciding whether to become an Airbnb host, it's important for you to understand how the laws work in your city.  Some cities have laws that restrict your ability to host paying guests for short periods. These laws are often part of a city's zoning or administrative codes. In many cities, you must register, get a permit, or obtain a license before you list your property or accept guests. Certain types of short-term bookings may be prohibited altogether. Local governments vary greatly in how they enforce these laws. Penalties may include fines or other enforcement.   These rules can be confusing. We're working with governments around the world to clarify these rules so that everyone has a clear understanding of what the laws are.\u00a0   In some tax jurisdictions, Airbnb will take care of calculating, collecting, and remitting local occupancy tax on your behalf. Occupancy tax is calculated differently in every jurisdiction, and we\u2019re moving as quickly as possible to extend this benefit to more hosts around the globe.   In the meantime, please review your local laws before listing your space on Airbnb. More information about your city's laws and regulations may be available on our  Responsible Hosting page in the Your City's Regulations section.  By accepting our Terms of Service and activating a listing, you certify that you will follow your local laws and regulations.", "question": "What legal and regulatory issues should I consider before hosting on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Host management services are third-party companies that assist with hosting responsibilities like key exchanges, cleanings, and listing management\u2014they're not affiliated with Airbnb.  If you choose to use a host management service, you'll be held to the same standards and policies as other Airbnb community members.", "question": "Can I use a host management service?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:                          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements                   Related articles   How do I change my reservation settings? What is Verified ID? Is verifying my ID secure?", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Hosts share their House Rules to set expectations with their guests, like limits on smoking, areas beyond the listing space that are off-limits, and permission to have visitors.  To add or edit House Rules after you\u2019ve listed your space: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Under Hosting, click on Booking Under House Rules, enter your expectations and rules for guests  If a guest breaks a house rule, either before or during their stay, you can cancel their reservation without penalty.  House rules appear on your listing page, and guests must review and agree to them before requesting a reservation. They\u2019re also sent directly to a guest once they\u2019ve a confirmed reservation.", "question": "What are house rules?"},
{"answer": "To edit your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Click on the section of your listing that you want to edit.    There are a couple of other things to know about editing your listing:               Some of your editing options (for example: calendar, reservation settings, and pricing) won't appear until you've finished listing your space.         Edits only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes; they don't apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.         While you edit, your changes will be automatically saved. Changes may take up to an hour to appear on your public listing.                                 Related Articles        Hosting            How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?       How much should I charge for my listing?       Instant Book settings          Listing            What should I choose for my room type?       How do I set my map or address?       How do I edit my neighborhood?       How do I add amenities to my listing?       How do I add and reorder my listing\u2019s photos?       What is Airbnb doing to help hosts make their homes safer for guests?          Guest Resources            What are house manuals and house rules?       What's a Guidebook?       How can I see or change the cancellation policy for my listing?", "question": "How do I edit my listing?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb welcomes many different kinds of listings on our site as long as they meet the following criteria: The space is only used for lodging The space, if a mobile home, sailboat, yacht, or other vessel, will be semi-permanently attached to a set location during the reservation The space is accurately represented, located where the host says it is, and is bookable by the host  Listings that don\u2019t meet these criteria include: Motor vehicles or watercraft intended for mobile use Any listing whose primary purpose isn\u2019t serving as a lodging  If we discover a listing that doesn\u2019t meet our guidelines, we may exercise our discretion to limit, suspend, deactivate, or cancel the host's account. Refer to our Terms of Service for more information and other requirements for listing your space on Airbnb.", "question": "Are there any restrictions about what can be listed?"},
{"answer": "If you don\u2019t want to receive any inquiries or requests, you can either snooze or deactivate your listing.  Turning your listing off doesn\u2019t affect your confirmed reservations.  Snooze your listing for a set period of time To pause your listing and hide it from search results for a set period of time:   Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to snooze Select Snoozed in the drop-down menu on the bottom-left Enter the Start date and End date Your listing will automatically reactivate when the timeframe you set is over. The day before your listing reactivates, you'll get a reminder email. Temporarily deactivate your listing To deactivate your listing:  Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to deactivate Use the drop-down menu on the bottom-left to select Unlisted You can reactivate your listing at any time from the Manage Listings page.  Permanently deactivate your listing To permanently deactivate your listing:  Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to deactivate Select Basics on the left-hand side of the screen Click deactivate this listing at the bottom of the page   You won't be able to permanently deactivate your listing if you have any upcoming reservations or reservation requests. Past reviews of your listing will remain on your public profile\u2014they cannot be removed. If you would like to cancel your Airbnb account entirely,  learn how to cancel your account.", "question": "How do I snooze or deactivate my listing?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types: Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type. Related articles   How do I list multiple rooms? How do I add the type of bed to my listing? How do I edit my listing?", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "If you want to list multiple rooms in your house, you can create a separate listing for each space you have available. Each room will have it\u2019s own calendar and listing page that should accurately reflect the number of beds and amenities, as well as what space will be shared with others. To create a new listing, log in to airbnb.com and go to List your space. You can also create a listing for your whole house and separate listings for individual rooms in the house, but be sure to sync your calendars. If you rent your entire house, block those dates on all the individual rooms so you won't double-book. You can offer guests a discounted rate for booking multiple rooms by sending a Special Offer and blocking the calendar of the other listings to avoid double-booking.", "question": "How do I list multiple rooms?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can share your listing through different social media platforms or embed a preview of your listing on your website to reach people beyond those searching on Airbnb.          Share your listing on social media     To share your listing on Facebook, Pinterest, Google+, or Twitter:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click the name of the listing you want to share On your listing's page, under Save to Wishlist click ... More. Select the social media platform you want to use and follow the steps to share                     Embed a preview of your listing     If you have your own website, you can embed a preview of your listing:           Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click the name of the listing you want to embed On your listing's page, under Save to Wishlist click ... More. Select Embed this listing       Click Copy HTML in the preview window to save the HTML to your clipboard       Paste the HTML code into your website where you\u2019d like your listing preview to appear.", "question": "How can I share or embed my listing on other websites?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "In addition to written reviews, guests can submit an overall star rating and a set of category star ratings. Hosts can view their star ratings on their Stats page, under Ratings from Guests. To see a breakdown of guest ratings by category, click Show Details.  Guests can give ratings on: Overall Experience. What was your guest\u2019s overall experience? Cleanliness.  Did your guests feel that your space was clean and tidy? Accuracy.  How accurately did your listing page represent your space? Value.  Did your guest feel your listing provided good value for the price? Communication.  How well did you communicate with your guest before and during their stay? Arrival. How smoothly did their check-in go? Location. How did guests feel about your neighborhood?    In each category, you\u2019ll be able to see how often you get 5 stars, how guests rated nearby hosts, and, in some cases, tips to help you improve your listing. The number of stars displayed at the top of a listing page is an aggregate of the primary scores guests have given for that listing. At the bottom of a listing page there's an aggregate for each category rating. A host needs to receive star ratings from at least 3 guests before their aggregate score appears.", "question": "How do star ratings work?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To help make sure guests aren\u2019t contacting you if you're unable to host, and to preserve your response rate, your listing may be deactivated: If you let 4 consecutive reservation requests or booking inquiries expire  If you decline consecutive reservation requests and booking inquiries over an extended period of time  If you consistently take more than 7 days to pre-approve an inquiry  Reactivate your listing If your listing is temporarily deactivated, you\u2019ll receive an email with instructions on how to reactivate it. You can also reactivate your listing at anytime from your dashboard. It may take up to an hour for your listing to appear in search results after it has been reactivated.", "question": "Why was my listing deactivated?"},
{"answer": "Host Assist apps and products are offered by different companies who have partnered with Airbnb. If you\u2019re having trouble, you should contact the customer service team for the company offering the app.    Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more", "question": "What should I do if I need help with one of my Host Assist apps?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "You can manage nightly pricing directly from your calendar:              Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Select the dates you want to edit In the window that appears on the right, you can set your nightly price [Optional] Click Add note to enter private notes to yourself Click Save Changes after you\u2019ve made your changes  Your nightly rate will show for each available night. If you set weekend pricing or custom pricing those prices will show on the appropriate dates. Long-term pricing options will not be displayed.                               Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I change my reservation settings?", "question": "How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?"},
{"answer": "We\u2019re only able to offer one complimentary photography shoot per listing.  If your space has changed, we suggest taking your own photos and adding them to your listing's page. Get tips for taking your own great photos.", "question": "Can I receive a complimentary reshoot of my listing?"},
{"answer": "Dates that are available to book on your calendar are white. Unavailable dates are greyed out. You can manage your availability in your calendar:              Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Select the dates you want to edit In the window that appears on the right, you can set your nightly price or make dates either Available or Blocked  [Optional] Click Add note to enter private notes to yourself Click Save Changes after you\u2019ve made your changes                            Request and reservations Dates for pending requests and confirmed reservations will be automatically blocked on your calendar. Because one reservation could start in the second half of a day after a previous reservation ends, start and end dates of requests and reservations are partially filled.    Related articles               How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I manage my availability on my calendar?"},
{"answer": "You need at least one photo in order to list a space, but we recommend you upload at least 10\u2014enough to show potential guests a thorough view of the space they'll get to use if they stay with you. Add photos To add photos to an existing listing:  Go to Your Listing on airbnb.com Under the listing you want to edit, click Manage Listing and Calendar Click Photos on the left Click Add Photo and choose the photos you want to upload  Keep in mind that resolution matters\u2014take photos that are at least 1024 x 683px. When in doubt, a bigger photo is better. Changes to your photos may take up to 30 minutes to appear on your public listing. For a faster upload, we encourage you to use Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox web browsers. Reorder photos To reorder your uploaded photos, select a photo and drag it where you'd like it to go.  The first three photos are the most important, since they\u2019ll be prominently displayed on your listing. Your first photo will appear in search results and will be the largest image displayed at the top of your listing. Add captions You can add captions to each photo by clicking on the blank white box underneath the image. Your text will save automatically when you click out of the box. Delete photos To delete a photo, click the trash can icon in the top-right corner of the photo. If a photo you upload is facing the wrong direction, you\u2019ll need to correct the orientation from your computer. After you\u2019ve rotated the image and saved the file, re-upload the new image to your listing.", "question": "How do I add and reorder my listing\u2019s photos?"},
{"answer": "What is Instant Book? Instant Book is a host setting which lets guests who meet your requirements automatically book your space. Instant Book will apply to all available dates on your calendar.  Benefits of Instant Book   Convenience: Book guests without having to respond to each request.   More guest interest: Guests can use filters to search for listings that can be booked instantly. Instant Book listings are more popular with guests since they\u2019re able to more easily plan their trip.    Search placement: Instant Book positively affects your response rate for your listing, which can improve your listing\u2019s placement in search results.   Superhost Status: Instant book can also help you reach Superhost status, which requires that you maintain a 90% response rate  Related Content   Instant Book settings Prepare to host What are house manuals and house rules?", "question": "Learn about Instant Book"},
{"answer": "To reschedule your professional photography shoot, you can send your photographer a message through the Airbnb messaging system\u2014you should already have a message thread with them if you've been communicating to organize the shoot. You can also cancel the request from your account:   Go to Your Listing on airbnb.com Under the listing you want to edit, click Manage Listing and Calendar Click Photos on the left Click Cancel request  If you cancel through your account, it's a nice idea to follow up with your photographer via message thread as well, just to let them know that your plans have changed or that you'd like to reschedule. Note: You must give at least 24 hours notice if you need to change or cancel your appointment time.", "question": "How do I reschedule or cancel my photography shoot?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb offers free professional photography to hosts in many cities. For more information, visit airbnb.com/photography. If a photographer is available in your area, they'll reach out within a few days. While you wait for professional photography, we recommend uploading your own images. Check out our Top 5 Photo Tips for a Stellar Listing. Once you have a photo shoot scheduled, here are some tips to help you prepare:        Open any blinds or curtains to allow natural light in     Organize or put away objects that clutter your space, and remove any valuables you don't want photographed     Think about how you might want to highlight amenities your guest will enjoy     Make your bed with nice, clean sheets     Tidy up surfaces and bedside tables     Open the shower curtain, clean the bathroom mirror, and close the toilet lid     Fold your guest towels  If you have questions at any point about your photography shoot or timing, please reach out to your photographer. If your photo shoot's scheduled time doesn't work, please remember that you must cancel at least 24 hours before your scheduled shoot. You can cancel your request in the Edit Photos section of your account. After your shoot, your images will go through an editing process and will go live in approximately 4 weeks. If you don\u2019t hear from a photographer within a week of submitting your professional photography request, we may not have someone available in your area at the time. If this happens, please try canceling and requesting again in the future.", "question": "How should I prepare for my professional photography session?"},
{"answer": "After you request a photo shoot, Airbnb reaches out to independent, third-party photographers to handle the request. We do our best to connect hosts with freelance photographers, but due to high demand, professional photographer availability can\u2019t be guaranteed at all times.We recommend uploading your own images while you wait for professional photography. Planning to make changes to the appearance of your listing soon? Please wait to request. If you already requested photography, learn how to cancel your request. If a photographer is available If a photographer is available, they should reach out to you via the Airbnb messaging system within 7 days of your request. All Airbnb photographers have a verified badge on their profile. You'll also receive their contact information when they accept the assignment. Once a photographer accepts the assignment, you'll work together to set up a time that suits you both. Be sure that your contact details are up to date and to schedule the shoot for a date when you don't have guests. Photo shoot timing A photography shoot of an apartment typically takes 30 minutes, while larger spaces can take up to an hour. Check with the photographer to see how much time they think they'll need for your home\u2014setting aside enough time for the shoot will help ensure you get the best photos possible. You'll also want to clean and tidy up your space in preparation for the shoot. After the shoot After your shoot, photos are typically uploaded, reviewed, and made public on the Airbnb site within 4 weeks. We review every photo taken by our photographers and only accept shoots that meet our standards. Occasionally, photos need to be sent back for additional post-processing and editing, which can take additional time, or we may need a second photo shoot to get quality images.  Note: We can't provide copies of these photos because they're copyrighted by Airbnb. Airbnb will hold all rights (including copyright rights), title and interest in the resulting images, and Airbnb may use the resulting images for advertising, marketing, commercial and other purposes in any media or platform, whether in relation to your listing or otherwise.", "question": "What happens after I request professional photography?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "High-quality photos are a great way to showcase your space and help set guests\u2019 expectations.    Here are a few tips for taking your own photos:    A few photos are better than none: Start by some of your own photos when you create a new listing\u2014cell phone photos are fine.   Resolution matters: Take photos that are at least 1024 x 683px. When in doubt, a bigger photo is better.   Take your photos in landscape format: Vertical photos won\u2019t showcase your space as well.   Set the scene: Clean up, remove clutter and pretend you\u2019re preparing for your first guest.   Take photos during the day: Open the blinds and turn on the lights to brighten your space.   Highlight unique amenities: Guests love to stay in spaces with character. Consider including photos of your space's exterior, too. Read more about uploading and arranging your listing photos. You can also visit the Airbnb blog to get detailed tips for taking your own photos. In some cities, we offer free professional photography for hosts. For more info visit airbnb.com/photography.", "question": "How can I make my listing photos look their best?"},
{"answer": "High-resolution photographs that showcase your space can help your listing stand out\u2014and help guests know what to expect. To make it easier for hosts to get access to beautiful, professional photographs, Airbnb offers professional photography in many cities.  Visit airbnb.com/photography to see if this service is available in your area.  If it is, you'll see your listings appear at the bottom of the page. Select the listings you'd like to have photographed and click Check Availability. If professional photography is available in your area, you:  Must have a verified telephone number and email address on your Airbnb profile.  Can apply for photography for up to 4 individual listings. To apply for photography for 5 or more listings, you need to have at least an equivalent number of accepted reservations. For example, if you have 10 accepted reservations, you can apply for photography of up to 10 individual listings.  Can only have a listing photographed once.  If professional photography isn\u2019t available in your area, or while you wait for professional photography, we recommend uploading your own images. Photos don\u2019t have to be professional-quality to help give your guests a good sense of what to expect from your space. Learn more about preparing your space, and what happens after you request a shoot.", "question": "Where can I learn more about Airbnb's professional photography service?"},
{"answer": "If you add Internet or Wi-fi as an amenity, your listing will appear when people search and filter for places with Internet. We encourage you to password protect your network. You should only share your password with guests only after they\u2019ve confirmed their reservation.  It may be useful to tell guests that if they use your network, they agree to use it only for legal purposes and they promise not to use it for illegal uploading, downloading, or other illegal activities.", "question": "What should I consider when offering Internet access to guests?"},
{"answer": "Guidebooks let hosts suggest local spots, like restaurants, grocery stores, parks, and attractions. If you add a Guidebook to your listing, your recommended places will appear on the map on your public listing page.  Some cities also have city guidebooks, which are combined lists of recommendations that hosts have added to their own guidebooks. Add a host guidebook to a listing To create your guidebook:   Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com. Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit. Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu. Click Guidebook. Under a category, enter a business name or address of a favorites place. Write a short recommendation and any tags that apply. Click Add. You'll need to create a separate host guidebook for each of your listings. You can only create a host guidebook once you've completed the steps to list your space. Since these guidebooks are public, you\u2019ll have to remove your recommendations if you don\u2019t want them to appear for all guests. Edit or delete a host guidebook You can edit or remove recommendations from your guidebook, or delete your guidebook altogether.   Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Guidebook Next to the business you want to edit, click Edit If you want to remove the business, click Delete. Otherwise, you can edit your recommendation. To delete your guidebook, you need to remove each recommendation individually. Host recommendations in city guidebooks With city guidebooks, recommendations from host guidebooks are used to provide a detailed picture of what guests can do in that city. Three recommendations will be featured and will include a link to the host\u2019s guidebook and listing. These featured recommendations will change over time. To determine which recommendations to use, our algorithms look at the most interesting content created around each location, based on informativeness, uniqueness, and representation of the place. We then show the most helpful recommendations which seem to provide the most compelling information for guests. The best way to be featured in city guidebooks is to continue expanding your own host guidebook with your favorite places in the area. Can\u2019t find a city guidebook  At this time, not all cities have a city guidebook but we\u2019re actively looking to add more. The best way to help your city get a guidebook is to expand your own host guidebook with your recommendations. Once enough hosts create robust guidebooks, this information can be gathered together in a city guidebook. Leave feedback about guidebooks If you have any thoughts or concerns about guidebooks, you can provide us direct feedback. While not all feedback will make it to the site or receive a response, we encourage you to share your knowledge and opinions.", "question": "What's a Guidebook?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Nightly pricing You can set custom prices for any individual night or set of nights.  Go to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Select any upcoming day or set of days Set your nightly rate Click Save changes You\u2019ll see your custom nightly prices on your calendar.  Pricing for specific weeks or months   You can account for seasonal demand or local events like a conference or festival by setting custom prices for specific weeks or months.     Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Long-term prices, click the link to set custom weekly or monthly rates Set your custom weekly or monthly rates Save by clicking Apply Custom weekly and monthly prices will override your normal nightly, weekly, and monthly prices, as well as custom nightly prices you\u2019ve saved on your calendar. If you have custom pricing set for specific weeks or months you'll see a notification on your Pricing page, in the Long-term pricing section.      Related Articles         How do I use my calendar to check pricing and availability?       How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "You can set your listing\u2019s price to automatically adapt to changes in demand with Smart Pricing. If you turn on Smart Pricing, you instruct the tool to automatically adjust your daily prices within the minimum and maximum price range you have chosen. Adjustments are based on supply and demand in your area for that date, your listing\u2019s features, location, amenities, booking history, and availability.  Turn on Smart Pricing Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Look for Try Smart Pricing Set your minimum price, which is the lowest nightly price you want to charge  Set your maximum price, which is the highest nightly price you want to charge Select how often you\u2019d like to host Under Smart Pricing, toggle to turn on Once you turn on Smart Pricing, your prices will be automatically updated within the parameters you set. Smart Pricing works for all open nights on your calendar, and you can still set custom prices for specific days.  Turn off Smart Pricing  You can always go back to your previous prices or edit your prices. To turn off Smart Pricing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Click Pricing Settings on the right hand corner of the page Under Smart Pricing, toggle to turn off", "question": "Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand"},
{"answer": "Your response rate and response time measure how quickly and consistently you respond to inquiries and requests. You can view your response rate in your Dashboard in the Pending section.  Calculating response rate and response time Your response rate is the percentage of new inquiries and reservation requests you responded to within 24 hours in the past 30 days. Your response time is the average amount of time it took you to respond to all the new messages in the past 30 days. If you\u2019ve received fewer than 10 new message threads in the past 30 days, your response rate and response time will be based on the 10 most recent message threads from the past 90 days. The response rate to determine Superhost status is calculated differently and is based on your responses over the past 365 days.  Improving response rate and response time Doing one of the following within 24 hours improves your response rate and response time:  Accepting or declining a reservation request Sending a message back to a guest who has sent a reservation request or a booking inquiry Pre-approving or declining a trip described in a booking inquiry  Responses after 24 hours count as a late response, which will decrease your response rate and increase your response time. Your response rate can impact your position in search results.  Your response rate and response time aren\u2019t affected by follow-up messages between hosts and guests. You don't have to send the final message in a conversation to maintain your response rate.", "question": "How are my response rate and response time calculated?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you\u2019re having trouble getting in touch with your guest before their arrival you may want to try contacting them using a different form of communication. For example, you can try reaching them through: Airbnb message: Find your guest in your Messages and send them a note Email or phone: Go to Your Reservations, click on the reservation, and use the email address or phone number listed Keep in mind that many guests don\u2019t have access to a phone or have an alternate phone number while traveling, or they may also be in-transit or encountering travel delays that will affect their arrival time. If your guest decides to cancel or not show up for an active reservation, we\u2019ll uphold your cancellation policy, and your payout will be released 24 hours after the originally scheduled check-in. A reservation is active if the reservation status is Accepted in Your Reservations. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a host Where do I find information about my payouts? When do I get paid?", "question": "What if I my guest doesn\u2019t show up for their reservation?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "We don't share your personal email address even after you have a confirmed reservation. Instead, we create a unique, temporary Airbnb address for you, and share that with your host or guest. Keeping your real personal email address hidden helps protect your privacy, and prevent unwanted communication from people who may abuse our system. Any emails sent to your temporary Airbnb address are forwarded to your personal email address. This lets you use your email provider to send or reply to messages, attach files (up to 15 MB), and include links. A host's anonymized email address might look like: Personal email address: john.lastname@exampleemail.com Temporary Airbnb address: john-abc123xyz@host.airbnb.com A guest's anonymized email address might look like: Personal email address: jane.lastname@exampleemail.com Temporary Airbnb address: jane-def456@guest.airbnb.com  We recommend communicating using the Airbnb messaging system, but we recognize that sometimes you'll need to attach photos, directions, or other information in an email. These addresses let you send emails like your normally would\u2014with an extra layer of security.", "question": "How will my email address look to other people?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows designated people at companies enrolled in Airbnb for Business to book business trips on behalf of other people\u2014these people are called bookers. When a booker books a trip for someone else, the booker handles the reservation request, introductions, and payment for the reservation\u2014then they transfer responsibility for the trip to your guest. Once a reservation is accepted, both the booker and your guest join the message thread with the host and receive all trip communication. If you're a host, you'll see booked by and booked for in your communications with the booker and your guest. Read more about bookers and Airbnb for Business. Personal travel We require Airbnb reservations booked for personal travel to be booked by the person who's going to stay at the listing.", "question": "Who can book trips on behalf of someone else?"},
{"answer": "Your safety and comfort are always a priority. If you find that a guest isn't a fit for your space or hosting style, you can decline their reservation request or cancel the reservation.          Before you've accepted a reservation          We encourage you to take advantage of the safety features we've built to help give you peace of mind and help you get to know potential guests.          Declining an individual reservation request won't negatively impact your listing's placement in search results\u2014however, if you decline many or most reservation requests, your search result placement may be negatively impacted.     After you've accepted a reservation          If you've already accepted the reservation, you can cancel it. You may be subject to cancellation penalties.          You won't be eligible for Superhost status if you cancel a confirmed reservation\u2014unless it\u2019s under extenuating circumstances.          Flagging inappropriate messages                  If a message from a guest makes you uncomfortable, let us know by flagging it. To flag a message, open the message thread and click the flag icon  next to the message you want to flag to Airbnb for review.                              Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "What should I do if I'm uncomfortable hosting someone?"},
{"answer": "Messaging on Airbnb starts when a guest makes an inquiry or reservation request. Afterward, all messages related to that inquiry or reservation request will appear in your inbox. View or send a message                      On airbnb.com, go to your Messages             In your inbox, you'll see a message thread for each inquiry or reservation.              Click on a message thread to view old messages or send a new one.                  You must be logged in to your Airbnb account to view or send messages, and you can only send 30 messages within any 24-hour period.                To remove a message from your inbox                                 Go to your Messages             In your inbox, you'll see a message thread for each inquiry or reservation.              Hover over the message thread you'd like to remove and select Archive.          If a message makes you feel uncomfortable or someone tries to get you to pay outside Airbnb, click the  next to it to let us know. Message Threads When you click on a message, you can view the conversation and also the following information:   Host or guest profiles including number of reviews, verifications, and description.   Reservation and payment details such as date of inquiry, number of guests, and price breakdown.   Events such as reservation confirmation, pre-approvals, and special offers are notated in the timeline of the conversations.   If any actions are needed from you, you\u2019ll see the prompt at the top of the page, above the conversation. Guests can make booking inquiries or reservation requests, and hosts will be able to accept or decline requests.     Hosts will see what the guest pays and what they will earn. They will also be able to see a snapshot of their calendar.", "question": "How do I view and send messages?"},
{"answer": "You can decline any booking inquiries or reservations that you can\u2019t accommodate, but you should do so within 24 hours. Whether you accept or decline, the amount of time it takes you to respond to requests is factored into your response rate. When you decline a reservation request, you can choose to keep the calendar dates blocked or make them available for someone else to book. Update your calendar regularly so you only receive reservation requests for when you're able to host. If you change your mind and would like to accommodate a reservation you declined, ask the guest to send a new request, or send them a Special Offer or pre-approval.", "question": "Can I decline booking inquires or reservation requests?"},
{"answer": "You can see if your listing is showing up in search results by checking the number of views your listing has: Go to your Stats on airbnb.com Under Views, you can check how many times your listing was viewed by Search Date   Search for your listing You can also see how your listing appears in search results by searching for it yourself. Keep in mind that each guest will see different results when searching based on the preferences they add, their past booking history, and other search criteria.  Go to airbnb.com and enter the location of your listing Select dates that you\u2019ve confirmed are available and that fit within your calendar settings and requirements Select the number of guests that your listing can accommodate and click Search On the results page, use search filters to narrow down to a set of listings you can easily look through to find your own   Keep in mind that the location pins on the map are approximate, so that people don\u2019t know exactly where a listing is until they have confirmed a reservation.", "question": "How do I confirm that guests can see my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can share your listing through different social media platforms or embed a preview of your listing on your website to reach people beyond those searching on Airbnb.          Share your listing on social media     To share your listing on Facebook, Pinterest, Google+, or Twitter:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click the name of the listing you want to share On your listing's page, under Save to Wishlist click ... More. Select the social media platform you want to use and follow the steps to share                     Embed a preview of your listing     If you have your own website, you can embed a preview of your listing:           Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click the name of the listing you want to embed On your listing's page, under Save to Wishlist click ... More. Select Embed this listing       Click Copy HTML in the preview window to save the HTML to your clipboard       Paste the HTML code into your website where you\u2019d like your listing preview to appear.", "question": "How can I share or embed my listing on other websites?"},
{"answer": "Host Assist apps and products are offered by different companies who have partnered with Airbnb. If you\u2019re having trouble, you should contact the customer service team for the company offering the app.    Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more", "question": "What should I do if I need help with one of my Host Assist apps?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Host Assist is a collection of apps that can help you share your space with ease. These apps are offered by companies who have partnered with Airbnb.  Currently, Host Assist apps are only offered in select locations. If there are any apps available to you, you\u2019ll be able to see a Host Assist section near the top of the page, after navigating to your Airbnb dashboard.   From there, you\u2019ll be able to see which apps are available for each of your listings and sign up for the ones you\u2019re interested in using.", "question": "Host Assist and how to sign up"},
{"answer": "If your guest cancels their reservation, we\u2019ll notify you and automatically unblock the dates on your calendar so that you can host other guests. Any payout for a canceled reservation will be released 24 hours after the originally scheduled check-in date.  If the reservation status hasn\u2019t changed to Canceled in Your Reservations, it's still considered active, and will appear on your calendar.  Guest refunds Guests who cancel are automatically refunded according to your cancellation policy\u2014unless the cancellation qualifies as an extenuating circumstance or a Guest Refund Policy case. If you\u2019d like to offer your guest more money back, learn how to issue an additional refund.  Cancellations after check-in If your guest cancels after they\u2019ve already checked in: They\u2019re required to to leave your space as soon as they cancel The terms of your cancellation policy will still apply You must make any security deposit claims within 48 hours of the original checkout date, which you can check in your Transaction History  Related articles   How do I refund my guest? Change a reservation as a host What if I can't get in touch with my guest?", "question": "What happens if my guest cancels?"},
{"answer": "At a high-level, the factors that affect search ranking can be broken down into the following categories: listing quality, trip experience, ease of booking, and guest preferences. As a host, you have control over many of these factors. Learn more about  making your listing more competitive. Keep in mind that each guest will see different results when searching based on the preferences they add, their past booking history, and other search criteria.   Listing quality   The way you list your space and how well you look after your guests impacts where you appear in search compared to other listings.        Booking appeal: If guests frequently click through to your listing page or try to book your space, this can also positively affect your placement in search. High-quality photos that accurately depict your space can attract interest from guests.  Reviews: Both the quantity and quality of reviews from past guests can impact your search performance.       Ease of booking How reliably and easily guests can book your space impacts search results.   Response rate and response time: The quicker and more consistently you respond to guests, the better your listing can do in search. Search also considers how many guests you accept. Rejecting a large number of requests, or failing to respond to inquiries will affect your placement and visibility in search.  Cancellations: If you do cancel on a guest, it can negatively impact where your listing appears in search. Guest preferences Search results may vary depending on the person, their preferences, and the specifics of their trip.   Location relevance: Guests can search broadly at the city level or narrow into specific neighborhoods, so we try to show search results that are most relevant to their location preferences. We may use past booking information to determine which locations are most relevant for a given search. On mobile, guests can specify travel preferences such as neighborhood types (for example, \u201cquiet\u201d or \u201cscenic\u201d). If they specify these preferences, they\u2019ll still see \u201cPopular\u201d listings as well based on our existing ranking factors. Personalized results: We try to understand a guest\u2019s preferences and trip characteristics, so search results may vary depending on the person or the specifics of their trip. We understand that new hosts may not have had a chance to get many inquiries and bookings yet, so we also take this into account.", "question": "How are search results determined?"},
{"answer": "If your guest changes a long-term reservation with less than 30 days notice, you have the option to either enforce or waive your cancellation policy.  If you enforce your cancellation policy:  Your guest is charged for the remaining nights of the original reservation up to 30 nights from the date of the alteration request  Your cancellation policy is immediately reinstated after the alteration is accepted Your calendar will be updated with the new dates  If you waive your cancellation policy:  Your guest is only charged for the actual nights stayed  Your cancellation policy is only waived temporarily to allow for the alteration, but it\u2019s not waived for the entire reservation  Your cancellation policy is immediately reinstated after the alteration is accepted Your calendar is updated according to the new dates  If your guest alters the dates of a long-term reservation with more than 30 days notice, you won't see the option to accept or decline the alteration request since the long-term cancellation policy already covers those 30 nights.   Related articles   Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation? Long-term Cancellation Policy", "question": "What does it mean to enforce or waive my cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Remove a pre-approval If a guest hasn\u2019t accepted a pre-approval and your situation has changed, you can remove a pre-approval. At the moment, you can only remove a pre-approval on a computer. Go to your Inbox  on airbnb.com Open the message thread with the guest Click Remove Pre-approval  You can't edit a pre-approval. If a guest wants to change their travel dates, they'll need to request a reservation for those dates. Why can\u2019t I send a pre-approval? If you don't see the option to pre-approve a guest, it means that your calendar is blocked for some or all of the guest\u2019s reservation dates.  To send a pre-approval, edit your calendar to reflect that your listing is available.  Related Articles     How do I pre-approve a guest? What is a pre-approval? How do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest? What does each reservation status mean?", "question": "How do I remove a pre-approval that I've sent to a guest?"},
{"answer": "Your safety and comfort are always a priority. If you find that a guest isn't a fit for your space or hosting style, you can decline their reservation request or cancel the reservation.          Before you've accepted a reservation          We encourage you to take advantage of the safety features we've built to help give you peace of mind and help you get to know potential guests.          Declining an individual reservation request won't negatively impact your listing's placement in search results\u2014however, if you decline many or most reservation requests, your search result placement may be negatively impacted.     After you've accepted a reservation          If you've already accepted the reservation, you can cancel it. You may be subject to cancellation penalties.          You won't be eligible for Superhost status if you cancel a confirmed reservation\u2014unless it\u2019s under extenuating circumstances.          Flagging inappropriate messages                  If a message from a guest makes you uncomfortable, let us know by flagging it. To flag a message, open the message thread and click the flag icon  next to the message you want to flag to Airbnb for review.                              Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "What should I do if I'm uncomfortable hosting someone?"},
{"answer": "You can still make changes or cancel a Special Offer as long as a guest hasn't accepted it. Cancel a Special Offer To cancel a Special Offer: Go to Your Messages on airbnb.com Open the message from the guest you sent a Special Offer to  Click Remove Special Offer within the message thread  Edit a Special Offer To edit a Special Offer: Go to Your Messages on airbnb.com Open the message from the guest you sent a Special Offer to  On the left side of the page under Payment click Send special offer In the Subtotal field, enter the new price you\u2019d like to offer your guest for their stay (be sure to include cleaning fee or your additional guest fee in this subtotal)  Click Send special offer  If the guest has already booked your place, use the alterations tool to make changes to accepted reservations.", "question": "How do I edit or remove a Special Offer?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb empowers hosts to set and manage their cancellation policies. If a host or guest needs to cancel a reservation, it\u2019s their responsibility to cancel as soon as possible. At times, certain circumstances outside of a host or guest\u2019s control can impact their ability to meet the terms of a reservation. In rare instances, if Airbnb determines that a Guest\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, Airbnb may override the Host's cancellation policy (ex: flexible, moderate, strict) and make refund decisions.  If Airbnb determines that a Host\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances policy, Airbnb may waive the host cancellation penalties outlined in Airbnb\u2019s Terms of Service and Airbnb\u2019s Payments Terms of Service. What might be covered? Valid extenuating circumstances include:  Unexpected death or serious illness of a host, guest or immediate family member  Serious injury that directly restricts a guest\u2019s ability to travel or a host\u2019s ability to host Significant natural disasters or severe weather incidents impacting the location of destination or location of departure Urgent travel restrictions or severe security advisories issued after the time of booking, by an appropriate national or international authority (such as a government office or department) Endemic disease declared by a credible national or international authority (such as the US Center for Disease Control or the World Health Organization) Severe property damage or unforeseen maintenance issues that directly impact the ability to host safely Government-mandated obligations issued after the time of booking  If you need to make a claim Claims can only be considered after a reservation has been canceled. Once you have informed your host or guest and canceled a reservation, if you feel that your reason for cancellation is covered by Airbnb\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, contact Airbnb for consideration. We generally require claims to be submitted no later than 14 days from the original check-in date and we may require valid supporting documentation.", "question": "Extenuating Circumstances Policy"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you need to make a claim on your security deposit, you can do so in the Resolution Center within 48 hours of your guest\u2019s checkout date.   Go to the Resolution Center on airbnb.com Choose the relevant reservation Under Select a reason, select Request compensation for damages Click Continue to submit details about the damages and associated costs on the next page  If your guest agrees to the amount you requested, we'll send you a payout between 5 to 7 business days.  If your guest declines or doesn't respond within 72 hours, click Involve Airbnb in your Resolution Center case. If we require additional documentation, you'll have 48 hours to provide this documentation.  Most security deposit claims will be resolved within one week. We'll make sure you and your guest are represented fairly, and if we determine you're owed money, we'll send it to you in a separate payout.", "question": "How do I make a claim on the security deposit?"},
{"answer": "To submit a Host Guarantee payment request, read through the terms and conditions of the Host Guarantee (www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee), then contact your guest to notify them of your complaint\u2014often hosts and guests resolve issues on their own via our Resolution Center.  If you and your guest aren't able to come to an agreement, update your case in the Resolution Center accordingly. Gather as much documentation as possible to submit to Airbnb, including photos, receipts, a police report, and any other documentation that proves ownership, damage, or estimates the fair market value of items damaged.  In the very rare occasion of malicious damages or damages involving any kind of illegal activity, please also file a police report with your local authorities. We'll ask you to provide Airbnb with an official copy of the report, so please be sure to ask for a paper copy for your records.  You must submit the request either 14 days from the guests check out or before the next guest checks in, whichever is earlier. For payment requests submitted on time, well send a confirmation email and follow-up emails to discuss next steps. Once we receive sufficient information from both the host and the guest, well review all documentation and evaluate the payment request. The length of the process will vary depending on the severity of the case, the quality of documentation, and the cooperation of the host and guest.                          Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.", "question": "How do I submit a Host Guarantee payment request?"},
{"answer": "Yes. Some hosts require guests to sign contracts or rental agreements prior to check-in. For hosts If you require guests to sign a contract, you must disclose the actual contract terms to them prior to booking. The easiest way to do this is to mention the contract in your listing's description, and include the terms in your message thread with the guest. Airbnb can't help enforce any special policies in your contract. For guests Hosts may ask you to sign a contract, but they must disclose this requirement and its terms prior to booking. If you\u2019re not comfortable with the contract, you may want to discuss your concerns with the host or look for another place to stay. If your host asks you to sign a contract that you weren\u2019t notified about before you made the reservation, you can decline to sign the contract and ask your host to cancel your reservation instead.", "question": "Can hosts ask guests to sign a contract?"},
{"answer": "The Airbnb Host Guarantee provides protection for up to $1,000,000 to a host for damages to covered property in the rare event of guest damages above the security deposit\u2014or if no security deposit is in place. The Host Guarantee Program doesn't cover cash and securities, collectibles, rare artwork, jewelry, pets or personal liability. We recommend that hosts secure or remove valuables when renting their place. The program also doesn't cover loss or damage to property due to wear and tear. For these types of incidents, hosts can add a security deposit in their pricing settings. The Host Guarantee Program isn't insurance and doesn't replace your homeowners or renters insurance. Make sure you review and understand the terms of your insurance policy and what it covers and doesn't cover. Not all insurance will cover damage or loss to property caused by a guest renting your space. Filing a host guarantee request doesn't preclude a guest from financial responsibility for the damages claimed if Airbnb determines a guest was at fault. Learn more about the Host Guarantee at: www.airbnb.com/guarantee.  View the Host Guarantee terms and conditions at: www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee. If you can't view this page, the country you're accessing Airbnb from doesn't have Host Guarantee coverage right now.", "question": "What is the Airbnb Host Guarantee?"},
{"answer": "You have 24 hours to accept or decline a reservation request before it expires. While a request is pending, the dates are automatically blocked on your calendar, so other guests can\u2019t request them. You can set up alerts on your mobile phone to get notified of reservation requests instantly. Accept or decline the reservation Accept or decline the reservation on your desktop or from your mobile app. You can also message the guest to review trip details before accepting or declining their request. A message doesn\u2019t count as a response to a request.  If you accept, we\u2019ll automatically update your calendar and schedule your payout for 24 hours after check-in.  If you decline, you may want to update your calendar to avoid receiving other requests for the same dates.  Expired reservation requests                 If you don\u2019t accept or decline a request within 24 hours it expires.      If you\u2019re still interested in hosting the guest, you can send a Special Offer .", "question": "What do I do after I receive a reservation request?"},
{"answer": "You can still make changes or cancel a Special Offer as long as a guest hasn't accepted it. Cancel a Special Offer To cancel a Special Offer: Go to Your Messages on airbnb.com Open the message from the guest you sent a Special Offer to  Click Remove Special Offer within the message thread  Edit a Special Offer To edit a Special Offer: Go to Your Messages on airbnb.com Open the message from the guest you sent a Special Offer to  On the left side of the page under Payment click Send special offer In the Subtotal field, enter the new price you\u2019d like to offer your guest for their stay (be sure to include cleaning fee or your additional guest fee in this subtotal)  Click Send special offer  If the guest has already booked your place, use the alterations tool to make changes to accepted reservations.", "question": "How do I edit or remove a Special Offer?"},
{"answer": "Special Offers allow you to set a custom price for a guest who has sent you a booking inquiry. Only send a Special Offer if you are ready to confirm a reservation.  Send a Special Offer To send a guest a Special Offer: Go to Your Messages on airbnb.com Open the message from the guest you want to send a Special Offer to  Click Send special offer On the left side of the page, in the Subtotal field, enter the price you\u2019d like to offer your guest for their stay (be sure to include cleaning fee or your additional guest fee in this subtotal)  Click Send special offer  Once you\u2019ve sent a guest a Special Offer, we'll notify them. If the guest accepts the Special Offer, the reservation will automatically be confirmed. There are a few things to know about Special Offers: A Special Offer doesn\u2019t block dates on your calendar until after it is accepted by your guest. If you don't see the option to send a Special Offer, check that the dates on your calendar aren't blocked or that you don't have any pending reservation requests for the same dates. If you have a pending request from another guest, you'll need to decline it before you can send a Special Offer. You can offer multiple guests a Special Offer for the same dates until someone books. We recommend being open and transparent with your potential guests that other guests may be interested in the same dates. If you have a security deposit on your listing, it will be handled as normal and you do not need to add it to your Special Offer total.  Confirmed reservations If the guest has already submitted a reservation request or confirmed a reservation, you won't have the option to send a Special Offer. You can still change the details on an existing reservation by changing the reservation.   Related articles   How do I cancel or remove a Special Offer? Change a reservation as a host", "question": "How do I send a guest a Special Offer?"},
{"answer": "Remove a pre-approval If a guest hasn\u2019t accepted a pre-approval and your situation has changed, you can remove a pre-approval. At the moment, you can only remove a pre-approval on a computer. Go to your Inbox  on airbnb.com Open the message thread with the guest Click Remove Pre-approval  You can't edit a pre-approval. If a guest wants to change their travel dates, they'll need to request a reservation for those dates. Why can\u2019t I send a pre-approval? If you don't see the option to pre-approve a guest, it means that your calendar is blocked for some or all of the guest\u2019s reservation dates.  To send a pre-approval, edit your calendar to reflect that your listing is available.  Related Articles     How do I pre-approve a guest? What is a pre-approval? How do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest? What does each reservation status mean?", "question": "How do I remove a pre-approval that I've sent to a guest?"},
{"answer": "When you send a pre-approval, you\u2019re giving the guest 24 hours to confirm a reservation without requiring any further action from you.  You should only send a pre-approval if you\u2019re ready to confirm a reservation. If the guest books your space within 24 hours, the reservation will be confirmed automatically.  Pre-approve a guest Go to your Inbox  on airbnb.com Open the message thread with the guest Click Pre-approve If you pre-approve multiple guests for the same dates, let each guest know that there are other people interested in booking  There are a couple of things to know about pre-approvals: Your listing\u2019s calendar is still marked as available when you pre-approve a guest.  You can offer multiple guests a pre-approval for the same dates. Once the space is filled, other guests will be automatically notified.  Guests have 24 hours to accept your pre-approval before it expires.  Once a pre-approval expires, the guest will need to send another inquiry or request in order to book. The new inquiry or request will still reflect the price from the original pre-approval. You have to retract your original pre-approval for new prices to be reflected.   Pre-approvals do not override your reservation requirements. Remove a pre-approval If a guest hasn\u2019t accepted a pre-approval and your situation has changed, you can remove a pre-approval. At the moment, you can only remove a pre-approval on a computer. Go to your Inbox  on airbnb.com Open the message thread with the guest Click Remove Pre-approval Why can\u2019t I send a pre-approval? If you don't see the option to pre-approve a guest, it means that your calendar is blocked for some or all of the guest\u2019s reservation dates.  To send a pre-approval, edit your calendar to reflect that your listing is available.  Related articles   What is a pre-approval? How do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest? What does each reservation status mean?", "question": "How do I pre-approve a guest?"},
{"answer": "A pre-approval is a way for host to let guests know that their listing is available when asked about a potential reservation. Once pre-approved, the guest can automatically confirm a booking for the specific dates provided. Hosts When you pre-approve a guest\u2019s inquiry, you give them permission to automatically confirm a booking for specific dates. The dates won\u2019t be blocked on your calendar, so you can pre-approve multiple guests at one time.   Guests have 24 hours to confirm a booking that has been pre-approved. After 24 hours, the guest can still request to book your listing with the price offered during the pre-approval, unless you remove the pre-approval. You can remove the pre-approval at any time in the message thread. Guests If a host has sent you a pre-approval, your booking isn\u2019t confirmed until you\u2019ve clicked Book It in the message thread with the host and added your payment information. Hosts can send pre-approvals to many potential guests, so if you\u2019ve found the perfect space, make sure to complete the booking process as soon as possible.  You have 24 hours to accept a pre-approval before it expires. If 24 hours have passed, you can still accept the pre-approval but your host will have to approve your request before your reservation is confirmed. Related articles   How do I pre-approve a guest\u2019s stay or remove a pre-approval? How do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest?", "question": "What is a pre-approval?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "The Resolution Center lets you request or send money for things related to your Airbnb trip. To open a refund or payment request, go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions.      You have up to 60 days after your reservation's checkout date to submit a Resolution Center request. Asking for help from Airbnb     If you\u2019re unable to reach an agreement, you can ask Airbnb to make the final decision 72 hours after the request was opened. To involve Airbnb:                 Wait 72 hours after you open the request       Go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions        Select the correct reservation       Click Involve Airbnb      When you involve Airbnb, our team will be notified and a dedicated team member will be assigned to your case. They\u2019ll review the information provided by you and your host or guest, before making a final decision. In some cases, we may need to contact you to gather additional information, before we can make a decision.", "question": "What is the Resolution Center?"},
{"answer": "Guests and hosts work out details for checking in, exchanging keys, and checking out directly with each other. There is no online check-in or checkout process. Read below for some guidelines to help you have a smooth check-in. Communication is essential Before the start of the reservation, message your host to figure out check-in and checkout times, make plans for the key exchange, and ask any other questions. Keeping communication in your message thread gives you and Airbnb a clear reference if any issues come up. Also, confirm your contact information and arrival details so you can reach each other in case plans change. Make sure to let each other know if you'll be without access to a phone or the Internet. Know your reservation details After a reservation is confirmed, refer to your itinerary for useful information about your reservation, such as the check-in and checkout time, the listing's address, your host's contact information, and your billing receipt. If there's no check-in or check-out time specified within a listing's description, check-in is 3:00 PM local time and checkout is 12:00 PM local time. Stay tuned to flight information and weather forecasts Look up travel advisories to make sure there is nothing impacting your reservation. With road closures and flight delays, guests and hosts might need a little extra time to safely meet up to exchange keys. Key exchange Many hosts greet guests in person to exchange keys. Others send keys and instructions in the mail, leave them in a lockbox, or have a neighbor meet a guest. The host can decide whether or not to give a guest a key. But, our Guest Refund Policy states that guests need to have reasonable access to the listing they booked. If you decide not to provide keys, you should mention in your listing\u2019s description and house rules that keys will not be available to the guests so people are aware of the situation before booking.", "question": "How does check-in work?"},
{"answer": "In most states and localities in the United States, guests who stay in a home or apartment for approximately 30 days\u2014the exact number depends on jurisdiction\u2014may establish rights as a tenant. Generally, this means that local tenancy laws could protect them, and you may not be able to remove them from your property without proceeding through required eviction processes in court. For example, in California, Illinois, and New York, a residential tenancy may be created after 30 consecutive days of occupancy. Someone who stays with you for fewer than 30 days generally does not have the rights of a tenant unless there is a written agreement to the contrary, but every state is different. Local laws may differ from state laws regarding residential tenancies. We encourage you to review your local rules and regulations before accepting a long-term reservation. Guests who refuse to leave\u2014and how Airbnb can help These situations are incredibly rare, but if they happen, we'll work with you to try and help resolve the problem with your guest. Should you face such a situation, let our 24/7 support team know\u00a0as soon as possible and we'll get in touch with you. Asking guests to sign a rental agreement If you rent your home or apartment for more than 30 days, consider whether you want guests to sign a rental agreement. If so, you should make these requirements clear in your House Rules before finalizing a booking. Laws governing these subjects vary widely depending on where you live, so be sure to contact a landlord-tenant attorney familiar with your local laws and regulations. Local rent control laws Rent control is a special set of laws that includes limits on rent increases and eviction restrictions. Some local rent control laws may override state law, and while many states or local jurisdictions do not have rent control, other laws may still protect tenants. For these reasons, we recommend you contact your local Rent board, Department of Consumer Affairs, Attorney General, or other agencies to learn more about rent control and rent stabilization and how these rules might impact a long-term reservation. Evicting guests that overstay a long-term reservation Statutes exist in nearly all jurisdictions that permit landlords to use summary proceedings to evict tenants. A summary proceeding is a judicial proceeding that lets a landlord regain possession of leased property in an expedited fashion. You should contact a landlord-tenant attorney or your local county courts to learn more about eviction laws where you live, as they may affect your ability to evict a guest who overstays a long-term reservation.", "question": "What are some things I should consider before hosting long-term guests?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.  Related articles   Where do I find information about my payouts? Long-term Cancellation Policy Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation? How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb releases your payout about 24 hours after your guest\u2019s scheduled check-in time. The time it takes for the funds to arrive in your account depends on your payout method.      If your guest is staying for longer than 29 nights, payouts for that reservation are released monthly. Payout status To check the status of your payout, visit your Transaction History. Once we\u2019ve sent your payout, a \u201cPayout\u201d line item appears for that reservation. If you have a minimum payout amount set, your payout won\u2019t be released until that amount is met. If you have multiple listings with check-ins on the same day, any funds going to the same payout method will be deposited as a single payout. Processing time After Airbnb releases the payout, it takes some additional time for the money to get to you.  The average processing time for each payout method is: ACH / Direct deposit: Up to 3 business days Bank transfer or international wire: 3\u20137 business days PayPal: Within 1 business day Western Union: 1 business day (US Pacific Time) Payoneer Prepaid Debit Card: Within 1 business day  Weekend or holiday delays   Many banking systems don't process transactions on weekends or holidays. If your payout from Airbnb is completed between Friday and Sunday, it might not be processed until the next week.   If you have any questions about processing time after your Airbnb transaction history shows a payout as completed, contact your payment processor directly.", "question": "When do I get paid?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb\u2019s payment system is designed to make transferring money between guests and hosts as simple and reliable as possible. Here\u2019s how it works:   Guests pay Airbnb when they book a place   Airbnb releases the money to hosts 24 hours after the guest checks in Using Airbnb\u2019s payment system is required to make a reservation, and it helps ensure that both parties are protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation policies, Guest Refund Policy, and other safeguards. Airbnb automatically includes service fees in each transaction, and some government-required taxes where applicable.  Related topics for guests: Prices &amp; Fees Payment Methods Related topics for hosts: How Payouts Work Payout Preferences", "question": "How does Airbnb process payments?"},
{"answer": "You can check the status of your payouts and view detailed information on your earnings at any time from your Transaction History.  You can filter transactions by payout method, listing, and date. View details of your payouts by clicking on the reservation code. Completed payouts  To see payouts that have been released by Airbnb, view Completed Transactions. We release payouts to hosts 24 hours after a guest checks in, but the time it takes to receive a payout after it\u2019s released depends on the payout method you\u2019ve selected.  When we release a payout to you, it appears as a line item with the type \"Reservation.\" Once the payout is processed, a \u201cPayout\u201d line appears. Hovering over the question mark next to the date of a payout will tell you when you can expect to see the funds in your account.  If you have multiple listings with reservations that begin on the same day, any payouts going to the same payout method will display as paid out together. Adjustments or any other fees are displayed separately. Upcoming payouts  To see your upcoming scheduled payouts, view Future Transactions. Before a payout is released, it will display as a \"Reservation\" with the date \"Pending\". If the payout is still pending, you can change your payout method for a particular reservation using the drop-down menu. Adjustments or any other fees are displayed separately. Gross earnings  For each reservation, the gross amount is the price agreed upon before Airbnb service fees and any taxes being collected on your behalf. Gross Earnings displays the total amount you've earned, which includes the 3% host fees. Earnings will appear in this tab after the payout for that reservation has been released. Exporting to a spreadsheet You can click Export to CSV to download a .csv file of your transactions from any tab. The CSV file can be opened by any standard spreadsheet program (like Microsoft Excel, Google Docs, or Apple Numbers) to give you a display of the data. This spreadsheet includes additional information, including host service fees paid and cleaning fees (if you charge one).    Related articles              When do I get paid?      What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?", "question": "Where do I find information about my payouts?"},
{"answer": "Inviting people to Airbnb can earn you\u2014and the people you invite\u2014travel credit to use toward a new reservation.     Invite friends to use Airbnb                     To begin earning credit, visit the invitation page and send the link to your friends. When a friend clicks the link, they will receive credit that will automatically apply towards their first reservation with Airbnb. The credit will show up automatically on the checkout page of any qualifying reservation.                                When your friend completes their first qualifying reservation, you'll earn travel credit to use for your own Airbnb reservations. You'll receive your travel credit after the departure date of your friend's trip. For each person you refer, there are two opportunities to earn travel credit. You earn credit when your friend completes a qualifying reservation as a guest and also when they complete a qualifying reservation as a host. You can earn up to $5,000 USD in travel credit overall.                       To see all of your current referral details, click Invite Friends on your Airbnb Dashboard. Terms apply.         Qualifying reservations         A qualifying reservation usually has a total value of $75 USD or more, excluding guest fees and any taxes. These amounts may vary during promotional periods.         Use your travel credit         Your available travel credits automatically appear as a coupon on the checkout page of your reservation request. If the travel credits aren't automatically added, it means the reservation doesn\u2019t qualify.         Travel credits can't apply to a trip that has already been paid for, but they will be available and applied to your next qualifying reservation. They expire one year from the date they're issued and can only be used once. They\u2019re also not reusable if you cancel a reservation where the credits were applied.", "question": "How do referrals and travel credits work?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "Hosts and guests can receive public references from friends, family members, and colleagues to help build their profile. References help people throughout the Airbnb community get to know you, and feel more comfortable booking a reservation with you.                      You need an Airbnb account to request and write references, and references will only display on the recipient\u2019s profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo.                      To request a reference:                                                                        Go to Profile on airbnb.com                                                                   Select References on the left                                                                   Use the Request References section to send emails to the people you want to get a reference from                                       In the References About You section, you'll see references that you\u2019ve received. You have to approve each reference before it will appear on your profile.                      In the References By You section, you\u2019ll see reference requests you\u2019ve received. The only way you can write a reference for someone else in the Airbnb community is in response to a reference request\u2014you can\u2019t proactively leave a reference for someone.                      References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip.", "question": "How do references work?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "The information you provide Airbnb during the Verified ID process is governed by our Privacy Policy and transmitted using SSL\u2014the same secure encryption that websites use to transmit credit card numbers. When we receive information from your driver\u2019s license or passport, we store the number in an encrypted form, so you should only have to verify your ID once. For countries with knowledge-based authentication, we don't store the questions or your answers. Only a small number of authorized Airbnb employees are allowed access to your original documentation for troubleshooting or internal purposes. Our third-party partners store information from the Verified ID process according to our written instructions and under our\u00a0Privacy Policy.", "question": "Is verifying my ID secure?"},
{"answer": "If you didn\u2019t receive an email notification from us, there are a few different steps you can try to figure out the issue. Make sure your email address is correct  We might be sending emails to an old or incorrect email address. To check the email being used: Go to Edit Profile. Look for the Email Address field. Make sure your address is correct. If it\u2019s incorrect, add the correct address, scroll to the bottom of the page, and click Save. Check your email notification settings  We'll only send the emails you tell us you want. Check your notification settings to make sure you haven't opted out of the email type you're looking for: Go to your Notification Settings. Look for the \"Email Settings\" field. Make sure you\u2019ve chosen the email types you want to receive. After adding or removing checkmarks from the right boxes, scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save. Search all messages in your email inbox Sometimes emails can get lost in your inbox. In your email account, search for terms like \"Airbnb\", \"reservation\", \"verification\", or other words related to the email you're looking for. Check your spam and other email filters It's possible your email provider mistakenly sent our messages to your spam or junk folder. To avoid this: Remove Airbnb messages from your spam list Add automated@airbnb.com, express@airbnb.com, and response@airbnb.com to your personal email address book If you have other filters or routing rules in your email account that may have sorted Airbnb emails elsewhere, be sure to check those, too. Check for issues with your email service provider Depending on your provider, emails can take up to a few hours to be delivered. If undelivered or delayed emails continue to be an issue, check with your provider to see if there are any configuration issues or problems with their network that might be affecting your account.", "question": "Why didn't I receive my email notification?"},
{"answer": "We created the Verified ID process to build trust in our community and help give you more information when you're deciding who to host or stay with.              How Verified ID works         Verified ID connects your Airbnb profile with other information about you. As part of Verified ID, you might be asked to:                                   Take a photo or upload an image of your government-issued ID, such as your driver's license or passport             Depending on where you live, you may have the option of answering a few questions about yourself instead             Connect another online profile to your Airbnb account, such as a Facebook, Google, or LinkedIn account             Upload an Airbnb profile photo and provide a phone number and email address                      Visit airbnb.com/verify to get started at any time.       When you'll need to complete it         Under certain circumstances, you might be required to complete Verified ID. For example, hosts can require that guests complete Verified ID before booking their place.                  If your host requires you to complete Verified ID, you'll be directed to complete the process right after you send your reservation request, and will have 12 hours to complete it. If you need to come back later, go to airbnb.com/verify and pick up where you left off.                           The Verified ID badge              When you complete Verified ID, you'll earn a badge on your profile. Many hosts and guests look for this badge when deciding whether to host or stay with someone\u2014but it's not an endorsement or guarantee of someone's identity.                    Privacy and encryption         We take privacy seriously. The information you provide during this process is encrypted and governed by our Privacy Policy.                      We won't share the government ID or personal details you provide during Verified ID with your host or guest\u2014they'll only know that you\u2019ve successfully completed the process. And we\u2019ll never post to your Facebook, Google, LinkedIn, or other connected accounts without your permission.                  Other ways your ID info is used     Where permitted by applicable law, we may also provide information from your government ID, such as your full name and date of birth, to our service providers to run checks against public records for criminal convictions and sex offender registrations. For now, these checks are limited to users in the United States about whom we have adequate identifying information, such as the user\u2019s full name and date of birth. While we believe these checks help us deter fraud and misuse of our services, they don\u2019t guarantee that interactions with people who book through Airbnb will be safe or problem-free. Please carefully review our notice about the limitations of background and registered sex offender checks.", "question": "What is Verified ID?"},
{"answer": "To verify your phone number:    Go to Profile on airbnb.com.   Next to Phone Number, click Add a phone number.   Use the drop-down menu to select your country, and we\u2019ll automatically insert the right country code.   Enter your area code and phone number.   Click Verify via SMS or Verify via Call. We'll send you a 4-digit code via text message (SMS) or an automated phone call.   Enter your code and click Verify  If you don\u2019t see a confirmation message, try refreshing the page. If the method you chose isn't working, try the other one.  After verifying your phone number, you can manage text message notifications by going to Account and choosing Notifications on the left. As always, standard message and data rates may apply for any calls or messages sent or received. For questions about these rates, get in touch with your phone provider.   Why verify? Having a verified phone number gives your hosts, guests, and Airbnb a way to contact you about your reservations or your account. Hosts are required to verify their phone numbers before listing their homes, and guests must have a verified phone number before booking a reservation. You also need a verified phone number to complete Verified ID.", "question": "How do I verify my phone number?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are experienced hosts who provide a shining example for other hosts, and extraordinary experiences for their guests. Once a host reaches Superhost status, a badge will automatically appear on their listing and profile to help you identify them.  We check Superhosts\u2019 activity four times a year, to ensure that the program highlights the people who are most dedicated to providing outstanding hospitality. The Superhost Terms &amp; Conditions apply. Airbnb doesn't endorse or sponsor any host, including Superhosts, or their listings.  Related Articles     How do I become a Superhost?   What benefits do Superhosts receive?", "question": "What is a Superhost?"},
{"answer": "You can edit information that appears on your Airbnb profile, such as your main profile photo or email address. If you\u2019re a host looking to make changes to your listing profile, learn how to edit your listing.  To edit your profile information:    Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com.  Use the menu on the left to choose different sections of your profile to edit.  The different sections of your profile include:  Edit Profile: Update the basics about who you are and where you live, including the phone number and email address you\u2019ll share when you have a confirmed reservation. Click Save at the bottom of the page to save your changes.  Photos, Symbol, and Video: Upload a photo from your computer, or take one with your webcam. A photo that clearly shows your face is needed before booking or hosting a reservation.  Trust and Verification: Add verifications to complete your Verified ID, which is required by some hosts.  Reviews: After you complete a reservation, write and read reviews that have been left for you. References: To build trust in the community, you can request friends, family members, and colleagues to post a reference on your profile explaining why you're a great host or guest.  To see what your profile looks like to others, you can also click View Profile.      Related articles   How do I complete my Airbnb account? How do I edit my listing as a host? What is Verified ID? How do I cancel my account?", "question": "How do I edit my profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.  Related Articles     What is a Superhost?   How do I become a Superhost?", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "The Superhost section of your dashboard helps you track your progress toward becoming a Superhost\u2014a host who receives a badge and other benefits for providing outstanding hospitality.   The Superhost section of your dashboard shows: The number of trips you\u2019ve hosted Your response rate over the last year The % of 5-star primary reviews you've received The number of confirmed reservations that you\u2019ve canceled  Your dashboard automatically reflects your activity from the past year, but in some instances it may take a day or two for your dashboard to reflect your most recent trips. It also tells you when the next Superhost assessment date will be.    If you meet the program requirements on the assessment date, you'll qualify for Superhost status. Keep in mind that you\u2019ll need to continue to meet the program qualifications to maintain your Superhost status on the next assessment date.", "question": "What\u2019s the Superhost section of my dashboard?"},
{"answer": "If you earn Superhost status, potential guests will see a Superhost badge on your host profile and each of your listings.  Other benefits     Superhosts are also rewarded with:      Priority support: You\u2019ll receive priority phone support whenever you call Airbnb or tweet @AirbnbHelp.     Search filter: A Superhost search filter lets guests search only for recognized hosts like you.     Travel coupon: If you maintain your Superhost status for a full year (4 evaluation periods) and have an active listing on the day that marks the 1 year anniversary of your Superhost status, you\u2019ll receive a $100 travel coupon to use towards your own Airbnb trip. Learn how to apply this coupon.     Product exclusives: You'll be invited to preview upcoming releases and attend exclusive events.  Related Articles     What is a Superhost?   How do I become a Superhost?", "question": "What benefits do Superhosts receive?"},
{"answer": "To become a Superhost, you need to have an account in good standing, and over the past year you must have:        Hosted at least 10 trips     Maintained a 90% response rate or higher     Received a 5-star review at least 80% of the time you\u2019ve been reviewed, as long as at least half of the guests who stayed with you left a review     Completed each of your confirmed reservations without canceling        You don\u2019t need to apply to become a Superhost. If you meet the program requirements on the assessment date, you'll qualify for Superhost status. We\u2019ll notify you of your Superhost status at the end of each assessment period\u2014usually 10 days after the assessment begins.     You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.    Measuring your activity   The Superhost requirements are measured every 3 months, and are based on your activity over the past year. The assessment dates are the first of the month in January, April, July, and October. If you meet the program requirements on the assessment date, you'll qualify for Superhost status, though it may take a couple days for your Superhost badge to appear on your listing. This process is automated, which means we can't update your status in between assessment dates.   Keep in mind that you\u2019ll need to continue to meet the program qualifications to maintain your Superhost status on the next assessment date. Superhost response rate In your progress toward receiving Superhost status, we look at your response rate for a longer period of time than the one we use to calculate the response rate that appears on your listing, where guests can see it.  On your listing, your response rate is based on the responses you send within 24 hours to the reservation requests and booking inquiries you\u2019ve received in the past 30 days. The response rate in the Superhost section of your dashboard is based on the responses you send within 24 hours to the reservation requests and booking inquiries you've received in the past 365 days. We use a longer period of time to determine your Superhost status, because having it should reflect a year-round commitment to providing outstanding hospitality.  Star reviews   The requirement that you receive a 5-star review at least 80% of the time is based on the primary reviews you\u2019ve received from guests, not the individual category reviews that you see directly above the written reviews on your listing page.    Keep in mind the number of stars you see at the top of your listing page is rounded to the nearest half of a star, and it\u2019s a cumulative average of the primary reviews you\u2019ve received since you started hosting. Those stars don\u2019t represent the percentage of 5-star reviews you\u2019ve received in the past year\u2014the only place to find the percentage is in the Superhost section of your dashboard.     If you\u2019ve received 5-star reviews 80% of the time or more, but fewer than half of your guests have left you a review, you won't receive Superhost status. Extenuating circumstances   Cancellations you make under extenuating circumstances won\u2019t count against your Superhost status, but all other cancellations will. We can't mark previous cancellations as \"made under extenuating circumstances,\" unless they're reported to us within two weeks of the cancellation.  Superhost Terms &amp; Conditions   Airbnb doesn't endorse or sponsor any host, including Superhosts, or their listings.", "question": "How do I become a Superhost?"},
{"answer": "To record a profile video using your webcam:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Select Photos, Symbol, and Video on the left  Click Record a new video and follow the instructions  You can use a profile video to express yourself to the Airbnb community and make a great first impression. We recommend you start with your first name and where you\u2019re from, and then let us know your interests, a fun fact about yourself, or why you love Airbnb. At this time, we don't support uploading saved videos from your computer, or uploading videos to your listing's page.", "question": "How do I make a profile video?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.  Related Articles   How do I edit my profile or profile photo? What is Verified ID? What are profile verifications and how do I get them?", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "The Superhost requirements are measured every 3 months, and are based on your activity over the past year. You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.    Measuring your activity      The assessment dates are the first of the month in January, April, July, and October. If you meet the Superhost program requirements on the assessment date, you'll qualify for Superhost status, though it may take a couple days for your Superhost badge to appear on your listing. This process is automated, which means we can't update your status in between assessment dates.   Keep in mind that you\u2019ll need to continue to meet the program qualifications to maintain your Superhost status on the next assessment date. Superhost response rate In your progress toward receiving Superhost status, we look at your response rate for a longer period of time than the one we use to calculate the response rate that appears on your listing, where guests can see it.  On your listing, your response rate is based on the responses you send within 24 hours to the reservation requests and booking inquiries you\u2019ve received in the past 30 days. The response rate in the Superhost section of your dashboard is based on the responses you send within 24 hours to the reservation requests and booking inquiries you've received in the past 365 days. We use a longer period of time to determine your Superhost status, because having it should reflect a year-round commitment to providing outstanding hospitality.  Star reviews   The requirement that you receive a 5-star review at least 80% of the time is based on the primary reviews you\u2019ve received from guests, not the individual category reviews that you see directly above the written reviews on your listing page.    Keep in mind the number of stars you see at the top of your listing page is rounded to the nearest half of a star, and it\u2019s a cumulative average of the primary reviews you\u2019ve received since you started hosting. Those stars don\u2019t represent the percentage of 5-star reviews you\u2019ve received in the past year\u2014the only place to find the percentage is in the Superhost section of your dashboard.     If you\u2019ve received 5-star reviews 80% of the time or more, but fewer than half of your guests have left you a review, you won't receive Superhost status. Extenuating circumstances   Cancellations you make under extenuating circumstances won\u2019t count against your Superhost status, but all other cancellations will. We can't mark previous cancellations as \"made under extenuating circumstances,\" unless they're reported to us within two weeks of the cancellation.  Superhost Terms &amp; Conditions   Airbnb doesn't endorse or sponsor any host, including Superhosts, or their listings.", "question": "Tracking your Superhost status"}][{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method   New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices  Select Guest Invoice For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history  To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices  Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation. .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about.", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment.", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:  New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable           Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable           Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable           Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types:  Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type.", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"}][{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method   New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices  Select Guest Invoice For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history  To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices  Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation. .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:  New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable           Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable           Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable           Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"}[{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method   New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices  Select Guest Invoice For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history  To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices  Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation. .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about.", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment.", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types:  Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type.", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "To edit your listing:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Click on the section of your listing that you want to edit.   There are a couple of other things to know about editing your listing:    Some of your editing options (for example: calendar, reservation settings, and pricing) won't appear until you've finished listing your space.         Edits only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes; they don't apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.         While you edit, your changes will be automatically saved. Changes may take up to an hour to appear on your public listing.", "question": "How do I edit my listing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation               Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay   In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays   Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:  New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable           Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable           Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable           Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"}][{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method   New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices  Select Guest Invoice For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history  To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices  Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation. .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment.", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:  New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable           Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable           Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable           Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about.", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types:  Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type.", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"}][{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices  Select Guest Invoice For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history  To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices  Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation. .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method   New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about.", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment.", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:  New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable           Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable           Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable           Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "To edit your listing:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Click on the section of your listing that you want to edit.   There are a couple of other things to know about editing your listing:    Some of your editing options (for example: calendar, reservation settings, and pricing) won't appear until you've finished listing your space.         Edits only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes; they don't apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.         While you edit, your changes will be automatically saved. Changes may take up to an hour to appear on your public listing.", "question": "How do I edit my listing?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types:  Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type.", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation               Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay   In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays   Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"}][{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.    Related Articles              Where can I find my VAT invoice?      What are the service fees?", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages  Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.  Related Articles   What are profile verifications? What is Verified ID?", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method  Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method    New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:    Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How long does it take a payout method to become ready?       How do I change my taxpayer information?", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices Select Guest Invoice  For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation.    Related Article              How do I provide my VAT ID number?         .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account. Related articles   How do I turn Instant Book on or off as a host? How does check-in work?", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.  Related Articles   How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar? How do I set reservation requirements? Why are reviews important?", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about. Related Content   How do I book a place on Airbnb? How do I search for listings? How do I view and send messages? What is Instant Book?", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment. Related articles   How do I check if my reservation is confirmed? Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.  Related articles   How do host cancellation penalties work?  Can I reply to a review? Extenuating Circumstances for Host Cancellations?", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:                          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements                   Related articles   How do I change my reservation settings? What is Verified ID? Is verifying my ID secure?", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types: Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type. Related articles   How do I list multiple rooms? How do I add the type of bed to my listing? How do I edit my listing?", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:      New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable          Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable          Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable          Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method  In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How do I split income between multiple people?", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.  Related articles   Where do I find information about my payouts? Long-term Cancellation Policy Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation? How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.  Related Articles   How do I edit my profile or profile photo? What is Verified ID? What are profile verifications and how do I get them?", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.  Related Articles     What is a Superhost?   How do I become a Superhost?", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"}][{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.    Related Articles              Where can I find my VAT invoice?      What are the service fees?", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices Select Guest Invoice  For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation.    Related Article              How do I provide my VAT ID number?         .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages  Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.  Related Articles   What are profile verifications? What is Verified ID?", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method  Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method    New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:    Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How long does it take a payout method to become ready?       How do I change my taxpayer information?", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.  Related articles   How do host cancellation penalties work?  Can I reply to a review? Extenuating Circumstances for Host Cancellations?", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about. Related Content   How do I book a place on Airbnb? How do I search for listings? How do I view and send messages? What is Instant Book?", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment. Related articles   How do I check if my reservation is confirmed? Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account. Related articles   How do I turn Instant Book on or off as a host? How does check-in work?", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.  Related articles   Where do I find information about my payouts? Long-term Cancellation Policy Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation? How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:      New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable          Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable          Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable          Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method  In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How do I split income between multiple people?", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.  Related Articles   How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar? How do I set reservation requirements? Why are reviews important?", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.  Related Articles     What is a Superhost?   How do I become a Superhost?", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.  Related Articles   How do I edit my profile or profile photo? What is Verified ID? What are profile verifications and how do I get them?", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:                          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements                   Related articles   How do I change my reservation settings? What is Verified ID? Is verifying my ID secure?", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types: Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type. Related articles   How do I list multiple rooms? How do I add the type of bed to my listing? How do I edit my listing?", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"}][{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices Select Guest Invoice  For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation.    Related Article              How do I provide my VAT ID number?         .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.    Related Articles              Where can I find my VAT invoice?      What are the service fees?", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages  Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.  Related Articles   What are profile verifications? What is Verified ID?", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method  Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method    New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:    Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How long does it take a payout method to become ready?       How do I change my taxpayer information?", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account. Related articles   How do I turn Instant Book on or off as a host? How does check-in work?", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment. Related articles   How do I check if my reservation is confirmed? Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.  Related articles   How do host cancellation penalties work?  Can I reply to a review? Extenuating Circumstances for Host Cancellations?", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.  Related articles   Where do I find information about my payouts? Long-term Cancellation Policy Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation? How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:      New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable          Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable          Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable          Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method  In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How do I split income between multiple people?", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.  Related Articles   How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar? How do I set reservation requirements? Why are reviews important?", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about. Related Content   How do I book a place on Airbnb? How do I search for listings? How do I view and send messages? What is Instant Book?", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.  Related Articles     What is a Superhost?   How do I become a Superhost?", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.  Related Articles   How do I edit my profile or profile photo? What is Verified ID? What are profile verifications and how do I get them?", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types: Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type. Related articles   How do I list multiple rooms? How do I add the type of bed to my listing? How do I edit my listing?", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:                          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements                   Related articles   How do I change my reservation settings? What is Verified ID? Is verifying my ID secure?", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"}][{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method   New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices  Select Guest Invoice For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history  To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices  Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation. .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about.", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment.", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation               Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay   In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays   Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:  New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable           Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable           Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable           Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To edit your listing:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Click on the section of your listing that you want to edit.   There are a couple of other things to know about editing your listing:    Some of your editing options (for example: calendar, reservation settings, and pricing) won't appear until you've finished listing your space.         Edits only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes; they don't apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.         While you edit, your changes will be automatically saved. Changes may take up to an hour to appear on your public listing.", "question": "How do I edit my listing?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types:  Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type.", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"}][{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method   New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices  Select Guest Invoice For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history  To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices  Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation. .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about.", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment.", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:  New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable           Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable           Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable           Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types:  Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type.", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"}][{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.    Related Articles              Where can I find my VAT invoice?      What are the service fees?", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages  Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.  Related Articles   What are profile verifications? What is Verified ID?", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method  Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method    New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:    Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How long does it take a payout method to become ready?       How do I change my taxpayer information?", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices Select Guest Invoice  For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation.    Related Article              How do I provide my VAT ID number?         .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.  Related Articles   How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar? How do I set reservation requirements? Why are reviews important?", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about. Related Content   How do I book a place on Airbnb? How do I search for listings? How do I view and send messages? What is Instant Book?", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:   Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site. Related Content   Why should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb? How do I view and send messages? What are profile verifications? How do reviews work?", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment. Related articles   How do I check if my reservation is confirmed? Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account. Related articles   How do I turn Instant Book on or off as a host? How does check-in work?", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.  Related articles     How do I submit a reservation request? How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.  Related articles   How do host cancellation penalties work?  Can I reply to a review? Extenuating Circumstances for Host Cancellations?", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save  When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.     Related Article              Where do I find my VAT invoice?", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.  Related Content   How does Airbnb handle security deposits? How do I include a security deposit on my listing? How do I make a claim on the security deposit?", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:                          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements                   Related articles   How do I change my reservation settings? What is Verified ID? Is verifying my ID secure?", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types: Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type. Related articles   How do I list multiple rooms? How do I add the type of bed to my listing? How do I edit my listing?", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.  Related articles   How do I set my base price? How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing? How do I set custom or seasonal pricing? How do I set up weekend pricing? Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.  Related articles   Where do I find information about my payouts? Long-term Cancellation Policy Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation? How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:      New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable          Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable          Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable          Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method  In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.     Related Articles              How do I add a payout method?      How do I split income between multiple people?", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.  Related Articles     What is a Superhost?   How do I become a Superhost?", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.  Related Articles   How do I edit my profile or profile photo? What is Verified ID? What are profile verifications and how do I get them?", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"}][{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Value Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.  VAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.   Guests  VAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee. Hosts VAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "A VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued. Guests To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Under the trip, click View Invoices  Select Guest Invoice For reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you. Hosts To access the VAT invoice for your reservation:    Go to Your Listings on airbnb.com Select Your Reservations on the left If the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history  To the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices  Select Host Invoice  If you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation. .", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "If you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.  Once we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.  The total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf. W-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)   Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.   You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase . Keep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "If you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.  US Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.  Non-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.  If you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.  Click here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.   Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.   At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.   You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on: Profiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile Listings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing Messages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages Read more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "There are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.  Some hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking. In some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax If you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection. In some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.  Learn more about Local Tax. Value Added Tax  If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.  Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.   Learn more about Value Added Tax. US Income Taxes  As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.     To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.  US persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year. Non-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.  You can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.   We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area. Learn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "You can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.  If the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.    Related Content              How do I change my taxpayer information?      How do I split income between multiple people?       How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "To divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.  Split payouts using routing rules Routing rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method Assign taxpayer information to each payout method Only one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:  Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account   Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer    Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method   New payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:   Go to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com  Under Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe. To that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations. Many countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). The Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs. In addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing. If you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account. When you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.  If you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us. If you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.   Your account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received. Your account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service. The following may occur with or without notifying you directly: Your account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience Any upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may: Communicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled. Refund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy. Contact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips.  Airbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "If you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up. You can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free. After you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "Instant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book. To be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback. Because reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide. Timeline for reviews You have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period. You and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to. Providing constructive feedback If you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.  Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:   Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.   Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.   Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.   Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor. Interested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack. You can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans. Calendar availability Keeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate. If you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates. Reservation requirements Setting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them. Learn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation. Look for Family/Kid Friendly listings If a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request. You can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you. You must be 18 or older to create an account In order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip. While we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about.", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters. Descriptions for filters For the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates. Other filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.     Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.         Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.     Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.     Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.     Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.     Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.     Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!     Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.         Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy. There are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including: Private messaging     Profile verifications   Reviews   Verified photography Hosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Hosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request. More than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours. If a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment.", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "Alipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long. When you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment. Once your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply. If your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary. If your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason. Common issues               Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.        Contact your bank or card issuer         If you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through. If your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "The Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations.  Changes to long-term reservations If a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host.  If the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes. Airbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price.  Canceling long-term reservations If a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests.  A host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation.  The Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation. Related articles   Cancel a reservation as a guest Cancel a reservation as a host What happens if my guest cancels a reservation? What to do if your host cancels", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home. To help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host. Before you book Share your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.  Airbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs. Spend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.  Get a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.  Feel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.  Before your trip Communicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.  Always let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.  On your trip Honor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.  Enjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.  Explore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!  Get your host's permission before having guests over.  When in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.  After your trip Always leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "If you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response. View Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "All the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.  Writing a review                      To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review.                   Review history          To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you.  Our community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "If you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.   To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:  Go to Edit Profile on airbnb.com  Under Optional, click Add VAT ID Number  Enter your VAT ID number verification information  Click Verify  Click Save When your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services.  Problems verifying VAT ID number  If your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.   If your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.   They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund. Find your itinerary   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. Find your receipt Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.   Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.    Information found in an itinerary Your itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:   Check-in time     Listing address   Detailed directions from your host   Telephone number for your host   Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details   House manual   House rules   Your billing information   Airbnb's contact information Information found in a receipt Your billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:   Name of the guest who made the booking     Any additional guest names you've included   Number of total guests for the reservation   Address of the listing   Name of the host   Dates of the reservation   Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.        Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.       Learn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account.     To add an additional host by (when available):     Go to Manage listings   Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit   Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu   Under Management, select Additional Hosts", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount. Service fees Service fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.  Guest service fee  We add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services. The exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt. If you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full. Host service fee  We deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments. You can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb. VAT  Depending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable. Conversion fee For guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "To help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes). We also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb. Find the service fee To see the amount of the service fee:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in   Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee   You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments VAT charges on service fees Depending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable. Note: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart.  Add a cleaning fee To add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee  Enter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation  The cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made. There are a few things to know about cleaning fees: In the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown. The cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation. Because the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply. Cleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.  If you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer. Set a weekly or monthly discount To set a weekly or monthly discount: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Click Pricing Under Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save)    Guests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown. There are a few things to know about long-term pricing: If you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount.  After the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts. If you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit                 Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation                Minimum night requirement for weekends To require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view Under Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay  In the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays  Enter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations       Click Save      Related articles               How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?       How do I edit my pricing settings?", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Go to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page Under Base price enter your nightly price Select your currency from the dropdown    Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.    Related articles              How do I manage my availability on my calendar?       How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?       How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?       How do I set prices for long-term stays?", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night. Set weekend pricing To change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays: Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu Select Pricing Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.  There are a few things to know about weekend pricing: You can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price. Pending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.  Custom pricing Any custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed.  If a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space. Reservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account.  Want more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "No. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:            Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Select the listing you want to edit Select Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner Under Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit Enter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD  The security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked. If a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary.    Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "An adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy.   To check the status of an adjustment:    Go to your Account Settings   Click Transaction History   Adjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "To print individual receipts for a reservation:    Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com   Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation   To see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file:    Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com   Click Export to CSV to download the file", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments.  We charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation.  You can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions.", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "PayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method. Connecting your PayPal account  You need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.  When you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly. Receiving payouts PayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "Setting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set.    To set a minimum payout amount:      Go to Account on airbnb.com  Select Payout Preferences on the left    Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method  Select Set Minimum Payout Amount  Enter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit  For most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "It usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.  There are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:  New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable           Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable           Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable           Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method In some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer.          To edit the amenities section of your listing:        Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com Click Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit     Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu     Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "After you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com   Select References on the left References will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo. Note: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "Your profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too. We require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation.     A great profile includes: At least one profile photo Multiple verifications and a Verified ID A description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know To view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:   Go to Profile on airbnb.com Next to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use Scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save Your email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications          We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.               To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings. In the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet: In the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon . Tap Settings &gt; Notifications. Manage your notifications. On the web:          Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.       Select Account.       Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.       Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.                When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.                   We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel. Push notifications        If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:            Go to Profile on airbnb.com       Select Trust and Verification on the left       Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect      To disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.         Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.      Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.  Enter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.  I want to update my password If you know your current password, but you want to change it:    Go to Account on airbnb.com   Select Security on the left.   Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen  I use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password If you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password. You can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.      Turn Social Connections on       To turn Social Connections on:                 Go to Profile on airbnb.com         Select Trust and Verification on the left         Next to Facebook, click Connect                  Turn Social Connections off         To turn Social Connections off:                Go to Privacy on airbnb.com         Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb         Click Save Social Connections                  If you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb. If you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year.  To keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period.  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.      Adding verifications        To add verifications to your account:          Go to Profile on airbnb.com     Tap Trust and Verification     Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add           Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.          Available verifications              Available verifications include:              Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages         Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted         Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews         Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations         Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities        Verified ID     You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types:  Shared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves.  Private rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping.  Entire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else.  As a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type.", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "Additional Fees  Cleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings. Other fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:        Go to your Manage Listings page       Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit    Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu    Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section  From there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room. Note: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing. Edit your check-in time To edit your check-in time:     On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings     Click the listing you want to edit     On the left side of the screen, click Check-in     Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time     (Optional) Set a checkout time  Note: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "We consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us. Airbnb takes trust seriously We're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives. Airbnb encourages responsibility We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting. Neighbor resources If your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.                      To set reservation requirements:          Go to your Manage Listings page Click Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen Check the box next to Require guests to go through verification Click Save Reservation Requirements", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "Almost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.  You can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Why can't I use Airbnb from my location? Airbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"}][{"answer": "\\n\\tAs a US company processing payments, we're required by US law to collect taxpayer information from hosts who appear to have US-sourced income. To add your taxpayer information, go to your Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form. It only takes a minute or two!\\n\\n\\n\\tEven if you're not a US person and have no US listings, we may be required to collect certain documentation from you to find out if your earnings through Airbnb are subject to US tax.\\n\\n\\n\\tDepending on your tax status, total earnings for the year, and number of reservations, we may provide you with a tax form showing your earnings.\\n\\n\\n\\tWhether or not you receive a form from us, it remains your responsibility to determine what amount to report as taxable income on your US income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax professional if you need advice on reporting your income. One resource for an overview of your US income tax responsibilities and information on how to complete your US income tax return is Ernst and Young\\u2019s \"General guidance on the taxation of rental income.\"\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Content\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     Where do I find my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?\\n     Should I expect to receive a tax form from Airbnb?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "Why is Airbnb requesting my taxpayer information?"},
{"answer": "\\nTo divide Airbnb income between multiple people, each person needs to be paid with a separate payout method. Once each payout method has a Ready status, you'll have the option to split your payouts by property, percentage, or both.\\n\\n\\nSplit payouts using routing rules\\n\\nRouting rules let you split your payouts between two payout methods per listing. To add a routing rule:\\n\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tGo to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com\\n\\t\\t\\n\\t\\tUnder Payout Routing Rules click Add Payout Routing Rule and direct your payouts to each payout method\\n\\t\\t\\n\\nAssign taxpayer information to each payout method\\nOnly one taxpayer can be assigned to each payout method. To assign taxpayer information to a payout method:\\n\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tGo to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com\\n\\t\\t\\n\\t\\tUnder Taxpayer Information click Add taxpayer and add taxpayer information for each individual or entity who receives earnings from your account\\n\\t\\n\\t Under Payout Methods click Options and select Assign taxpayer\\n\\t \\n\\t Under Assigned to taxpayer select a taxpayer for the payout method\\n\\n\\n \\nNew payout methods, and those that haven't been assigned to a specific taxpayer, are assigned to the default taxpayer. To change your default taxpayer:\\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tGo to Payout Preferences on airbnb.com\\n\\t\\n\\tUnder Taxpayer Information click Options and select Make default\\n\\t\\t\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     How do I add a payout method?\\n     How long does it take a payout method to become ready?\\n      How do I change my taxpayer information?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I split income between multiple people?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tIf you received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we're required to withhold 28% from your payouts and remit the withholdings to the Internal Revenue Service in Washington, DC. You can avoid this by submitting your taxpayer information.\\n\\t\\t\\n\\t\\tOnce we receive your information, we won't withhold from your future payouts. However, any amounts that have already been withheld and remitted to the IRS cannot be returned to you by Airbnb.\\n\\t\\t\\n\\t\\tThe total amount withheld will be included on any tax forms issued to you so that you may account for these withholdings on your income tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance accounting for any withholdings that have been remitted to the IRS on your behalf.\\n\\nW-8BEN Taxpayers (Non-US persons with US listings)\\n\\n  Unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed on your W-8BEN, Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons and remit the funds directly to the IRS. At the end of the year, Airbnb will report the total amount withheld and earnings to you on a Form 1042-S.\\n\\n  You may review or revise your Airbnb taxpayer information in your  Payout Preferences.\\n", "question": "Why are taxes being withheld from my payouts?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIt's possible that not all of your income is taxable. Deductible items may include rent, mortgage, cleaning fees, rental commissions, insurance, and other expenses. Other factors you might consider when assessing taxable income include renting vs. owning the space, number of nights hosted, tax status, and total net amount earned (any tax forms issued to you display your total gross earnings). \\n\\t\\n\\tWe encourage you to consult a tax advisor for more details, as there are many special rules in this area and we aren't able to provide tax advice.\\n\\tOne resource for an overview of your US income tax responsibilities and information on how to complete your US income tax return is Ernst and Young\\u2019s \"General guidance on the taxation of rental income.\"\\n\\t\\n\\t  Disclaimer: Airbnb's presentation of EY is not an endorsement. Tax advice is complicated, and you should do your own diligence when receiving advice. Airbnb is not responsible for any tax or other advice provided by any outside entity.\\n\\t", "question": "What expenses are deductible from my Airbnb income?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tYou can edit your taxpayer information or change the way your earnings are assigned between multiple taxpayers from your Payout Preferences, but changes made after December 31st, 2015 will be applied to the 2016 tax year.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tIf the earnings shown on an issued tax form show a higher amount than you were expecting, it's most likely the difference between your net and gross earnings. We're required to print gross earnings (inclusive of our 3% host fee) on all tax forms.\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Content\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     How do I change my taxpayer information?\\n     How do I split income between multiple people?\\n      How do I calculate my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "Can I correct an error on my tax form?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.\\n  \\n  Adding verifications\\n    \\n  To add verifications to your account:\\n    \\n    Go to Profile on airbnb.com\\n    Tap Trust and Verification\\n    Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add\\n    \\n  \\n  Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.\\n    \\n    Available verifications\\n    \\n        Available verifications include:\\n    \\n        Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages\\n        Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted\\n        Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews\\n        Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations\\n        Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities\\n    \\n  Verified ID\\n    You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "\\nWhether you\\u2019re looking for detailed information on a specific transaction or a static report, you can view your earnings at any time from your Airbnb account.\\n\\n\\nIt's your responsibility to determine what, from your total amount earned, to report as taxable income on your tax return. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor if you need assistance deducting any non-taxable income.\\n\\nTransaction history\\n\\n\\nYou can filter transactions by payout method, listing, and date from your Transaction History. Your transaction history includes completed and future transactions, along with an option to view gross earnings.\\n\\n\\nLearn more about how to use your transaction history.\\n\\n2015 earnings summary (US-only)\\n\\nAll transactions paid out in the 2015 calendar year are included in your Transaction History &gt; Earnings Summary. All transactions paid out in the 2015 calendar year are a part of the report, including both net and gross earnings. Gross earnings include any withholdings or adjustments that may have reduced payouts throughout the year. These amounts can be useful for income tax reporting purposes.\\n\\n\\nAt this time, your earnings summary is only available for display in USD. If you received payouts in other currencies, your earnings summary will display the exchange rate that was locked in on the date that the transaction took place.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     What expenses are deductible from my Airbnb income?\\n          Should I expect to receive a tax form from Airbnb?\\n     How do I split income between multiple people?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "Where do I find my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tTo update your taxpayer information:\\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tLog into airbnb.com from your desktop computer\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tGo to your Payout Preferences\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tTo the right of your Taxpayer Information, click Options\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tSelect Edit\\n\\n\\t\\n\\tDon't forget to click Submit after making any changes, and you're all set!\\n\\t\\n\\t  Some fields aren't editable, so if you're trying to change your tax ID number, tax classification, or enter a different taxpayer entirely, please add a new taxpayer.\\n\\n\\tIf you\\u2019ve added more than one taxpayer, you\\u2019ll be able to remove any record that is not your default by clicking Options &gt; Delete.\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Content\\n\\n  \\n    \\n      How do I split income between multiple people?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I change my taxpayer information?"},
{"answer": "Through awareness and a few simple tools, we'd like to help hosts make their homes safer and put guests more at ease.\\n\\t\\nEmergency safety cards\\nIf a guest encounters an urgent or emergency situation, it's important they know who to call, what, and where to go. To help make this information clear and easy to display, all hosts will see the option to fill out a safety card online in the Home Safety tab of each listing.\\n\\nThis card includes important information that hosts can provide guests, like emergency phone numbers, locations of fire extinguishers and fire alarms, and emergency exit routes. After you fill out the card online, guests will be able to see it after they book a reservation at your listing. You\\u2019ll also be able to easily print the card and display it in your space.\\n\\nSmoke and carbon monoxide detectors\\nWe\\u2019re encouraging all Airbnb hosts to install working smoke and carbon monoxide detectors in their homes. To help achieve this goal, the first 25,000 eligible hosts who request a detector through December 31, 2016 will get one for free. Terms, Conditions and Restrictions apply. Please check your local laws for any applicable requirements for where to put the detector(s) in your space.\\n\\nWhile we encourage hosts to install smoke and carbon monoxide detectors in their space, at this time, we don't require confirmation that they've been installed. If you don't indicate you have these devices by selecting the \\u201csmoke detector\\u201d and/or \\u201ccarbon monoxide detector\\u201d amenities in your listing description, guests will see those amenities crossed-out when they view your listing.\\n\\nFor more information, visit our Home Safety page: www.airbnb.com/home-safety", "question": "What is Airbnb doing to help hosts make their homes safer for guests?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb\\u2019s Host Protection Insurance will act as primary insurance and provides liability coverage to hosts and, where applicable, their landlords, subject to certain conditions, limitations, and exclusions. \\n\\nIf you have questions about how this policy interacts with any homeowner\\u2019s or renter\\u2019s insurance, you should discuss your coverage with your insurance provider. Some policies protect homeowners and renters from certain lawsuits that result from injury to a visitor, while others do not.  It\\u2019s always a good idea to let your insurance carrier know about rental activity in your space even though liability arising during an Airbnb stay should be covered by the Host Protection Insurance policy.  \\n\\nFor further guidance, refer to our Responsible Hosting page.", "question": "How does homeowner's insurance work with Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Being a host comes with certain responsibilities. Here are some resources to help support you along the way.\\n        Interact smartly\\n        Always pay and communicate on Airbnb. Use Airbnb\\u2019s messaging system to get to know your guests and share expectations about the trip or your space.\\n        \\n        Read profiles and reviews of your potential guests, and look for verified phone numbers, connected social networks, and references. If potential guests don\\u2019t have any profile verifications, you can ask them to complete some.\\n\\n        Trust your intuition: If you don\\u2019t feel right about a reservation, don\\u2019t accept it!\\n\\n        Fill out your House Rules, Home Safety Card, and House Manual\\n        Completing your house rules and house manual helps guests know what to expect. Include anything you\\u2019d like people to know before they book\\u2014for example, whether (or where) smoking is allowed, whether certain areas are off-limits, your Wi-Fi password, or if guests should take off their shoes before coming inside.\\n        \\n        If a guest encounters an urgent or emergency situation, it's important they know who to call, what, and where to go. To help make this information clear and easy to display, all hosts will see the option to fill out a safety card online in the Home Safety tab of their listings. This card includes important information that hosts can provide guests, like emergency phone numbers, locations of fire extinguishers and fire alarms, and emergency exit routes.\\n\\nIf a disaster affects your area and you\\u2019d like to help, you can list your space for free.\\n\\n        Make sure you're insured\\n        Airbnb's Host Protection Insurance program provides primary liability coverage for up to $1,000,000 per occurrence in the event of a third-party claim of bodily injury or property damage related to an Airbnb stay. Learn more.\\n        \\n        You may also want to talk to your insurance provider about adding an extra layer of protection with your own renter\\u2019s or homeowner\\u2019s insurance.\\n\\n        Set requirements for your listing\\n        You can require guests to complete certain verifications before they book, such as Verified ID.\\n        \\n        Adding a security deposit to your listing can also help protect you in the event of an accident, like spilled wine on a rug.\\n        \\n        Read Airbnb\\u2019s Responsible Hosting page\\n        We encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. Hosting offers rich experiences, but it requires commitment.\\n\\n        \\n      \\n        \\n        Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n        \\n      \\n", "question": "I'm a host. What are some safety tips I can follow?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tTo submit a Host Guarantee payment request, read through the terms and conditions of the Host Guarantee (www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee), then contact your guest to notify them of your complaint\\u2014often hosts and guests resolve issues on their own via our Resolution Center.\\n\\t\\n\\tIf you and your guest aren't able to come to an agreement, update your case in the Resolution Center accordingly. Gather as much documentation as possible to submit to Airbnb, including photos, receipts, a police report, and any other documentation that proves ownership, damage, or estimates the fair market value of items damaged.\\n\\t\\n\\tIn the very rare occasion of malicious damages or damages involving any kind of illegal activity, please also file a police report with your local authorities. We'll ask you to provide Airbnb with an official copy of the report, so please be sure to ask for a paper copy for your records.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tYou must submit the request either 14 days from the guests check out or before the next guest checks in, whichever is earlier. For payment requests submitted on time, well send a confirmation email and follow-up emails to discuss next steps.\\n\\n\\tOnce we receive sufficient information from both the host and the guest, well review all documentation and evaluate the payment request. The length of the process will vary depending on the severity of the case, the quality of documentation, and the cooperation of the host and guest.\\n\\n\\n      \\n        \\n        Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n        \\n      \\n", "question": "How do I submit a Host Guarantee payment request?"},
{"answer": "The Host Guarantee and Host Protection Insurance program are two separate programs that Airbnb offers to help cover hosts in the event of damage or injury. Learn more about the differences between the two below.\\nHost Guarantee\\n    Airbnb's Host Guarantee is designed to protect hosts in rare instance of property damage to their own possessions, unit, or home by a guest staying in the space. The Host Guarantee is not insurance and doesn\\u2019t replace your homeowner\\u2019s or renter\\u2019s insurance.\\n   \\n   Learn more about our Host Guarantee.\\n   \\n  Host Protection Insurance \\n    The Host Protection Insurance program is insurance, and is designed to cover hosts in the event of third-party claims of bodily injury or property damage. The Host Protection Insurance program is available to hosts regardless their other insurance arrangements, but will only act as primary insurance coverage for incidents related to an Airbnb stay.\\n    \\nLearn more about Host Protection Insurance.\\n\\nExamples of coverage\\nHere's an example to help show how the coverages offered by the Host Guarantee and Host Protection Insurance program differ:\\n\\n\\nDuring a stay in a covered country, a guest accidentally breaks the toilet and the host\\u2019s bathroom floods. The living room of the neighbor\\u2019s apartment also floods. The neighbor or landlord brings a claim against the host for damages to the living room.\\n\\nIn this example, damage to the host\\u2019s bathroom could be covered by the Host Guarantee, since the property belonged to the host. Damage to the neighbor\\u2019s living room could be covered by the Host Protection Insurance program, since a claim is being brought against the host by the neighbor or landlord for liability.\\n\\n  \\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nWhat is Host Protection Insurance?\\nWhat is the Airbnb Host Guarantee?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What\\u2019s the difference between Airbnb's Host Guarantee and Host Protection Insurance?"},
{"answer": "The Host Protection Insurance program provides primary liability coverage for up to $1,000,000 per occurrence in the event of a third-party claim of bodily injury or property damage related to an Airbnb stay.\\n    \\n    This coverage is subject to a $1,000,000 cap per listing location, and certain conditions, limitations, and exclusions may apply. Review the list of the covered countries.\\n\\nThe Host Protection Insurance program will only act as the primary insurance coverage for incidents related to an Airbnb stay, but it's available to hosts regardless of their other insurance arrangements.\\n\\nHere are some examples of what the Host Protection Insurance program should cover:\\n\\n\\nA guest breaks their wrist after slipping on the rug and brings a claim for the injury against the host.\\nA guest is working out on the treadmill in the gym of the apartment building. The treadmill breaks and the guest is injured when they fall off. They bring a claim for the injury against the host and the landlord.\\nA guest accidentally drops their suitcase on a third party's foot in the building lobby. The third party brings a claim for the injury against the host and the landlord of the host\\u2019s building.\\n\\nSome examples of what the Host Protection Insurance program doesn\\u2019t cover:\\n\\n\\nIntentional acts where liability isn\\u2019t the result of an accident.\\n\\nAccusations of slander or defamation of character.\\nProperty issues (ex: mold, bed bugs, asbestos, pollution).\\nAuto accidents (ex: vehicle collisions).\\n\\n\\nFor now, this policy only applies to hosts in covered countries. We\\u2019re working hard to expand this and other programs to hosts around the world. You can find the list of the covered countries at www.airbnb.com/host-protection-insurance.\\n\\nDownload a summary of the program.\\n    \\n    \\n    \\n  \\n    \\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nWhat\\u2019s the difference between Host Protection Insurance and the Host Guarantee?\\nHow does homeowner's insurance work with Airbnb?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is Host Protection Insurance?"},
{"answer": "Business Travel Ready listings must be an Entire Home/Apt and an eligible property type (house, apartment, bed &amp; breakfast, townhouse, loft, or condo). The listing must be no smoking, and can\\u2019t have pets on the property.\\n\\nThe space\\nMany business travelers are new to traveling on Airbnb, so we\\u2019ve limited Business Travel Ready listings to certain property types to help make sure guests know what to expect when they arrive.\\n\\nAs a part of this, and because of the potential for allergies and other sensitivities, we also ask that Business Travel Ready listings are smoke-free properties and don\\u2019t have pets living in the space while the guest is there.\\n\\nIf a pet lives in your space, but won\\u2019t be there during your guest\\u2019s stay we ask that you\\u2019re aware of traveler\\u2019s potential allergens and make sure your listing is cleaned before your guest\\u2019s arrival.\\n\\nAmenities\\nThe listing must also have the following Business Travel Ready amenities:\\n\\n  Wireless Internet\\nA laptop-friendly workspace\\n24-hour check-in (this could be a lockbox, doorman, keyless entry or similar 24-hour access)\\nA smoke detector\\nA carbon monoxide detector\\nEssentials (toilet paper, clean towels, and fresh linens)\\nAn iron\\nHangers\\nA hair dryer\\nShampoo\\n\\n\\nSmoke and carbon monoxide detectors are an important part of making Airbnb a trusted travel option for companies. As part of our commitment to guest safety, Airbnb offers free smoke and carbon monoxide detectors for hosts: www.airbnb.com/home-safety.\\n\\nReviews and response rate\\nListings must have at least 3 star rated reviews before they can be eligible for Business Travel Ready status. For listings with 3 or more star rated reviews, at least 60% of both the listing\\u2019s primary reviews, and the listing\\u2019s reviews for cleanliness and accuracy must be 5 star reviews.\\n\\nHosts of Business Travel Ready listings also must have responded to 90% of booking requests within 24 hours over the last year.\\n\\nCancellations\\nHosts of Business Travel Ready listings must provide a 7-day cancellation commitment to reservations. If a listing has a cancellation within 7 days of a confirmed check-in date, it can't be considered for Business Travel Ready for 1 year from the cancellation date.\\n\\nEligibility\\nListings and their hosts are evaluated for business travel readiness on a rolling basis. Keep in mind that you and your listing need to continue to qualify after the initial evaluation in order to maintain Business Travel Ready status.\\n\\nIf you\\u2019re a host, learn more or get started now.\\n\\nQuestions? Review the Business Travel Ready Terms &amp; Conditions.", "question": "What makes a listing Business Travel Ready?"},
{"answer": "Reviews are a way for Airbnb guests and hosts to share their experiences with the community. Any attempt to use reviews to force a user to do something they aren\\u2019t obligated to do is a misuse of reviews, and we don\\u2019t allow it.\\n\\nThis also means that:\\n\\nGuests are not allowed to threaten to use reviews or ratings in an attempt to force a host to provide refunds, additional compensation, or a reciprocal positive review.\\nHosts are not allowed to require a guest to leave a positive review or rating, or to revise a review in exchange for a partial or full refund, or reciprocal review. The host also cannot offer a free or discounted stay in exchange for a guest revising an existing review.\\nIf a guest contacts a host with a problem, the host should make every effort to resolve it. The host can't ask the guest to take specific actions related to a review in exchange for the resolution of the problem. After the issue is fixed, a host may ask the guest to leave a positive review or rating. A host may also ask a guest to revise a negative review provided certain time constraints are met.\\n\\n\\nWhether you're a guest or host, make sure you follow these guidelines. If you don't, your account may be restricted, suspended, or terminated. By posting a review, you agree to follow the Airbnb guidelines and policies that Airbnb may enforce at our sole discretion.\\nIf you think you've experienced extortion, please contact us.", "question": "Extortion Policy"},
{"answer": "By posting content on Airbnb, you agree to abide by these guidelines and other Airbnb policies. We reserve the right to remove content, in whole or part, that violates these guidelines or the Airbnb Terms of Service, or for any other reason at our sole discretion.\\n\\n  In the event of repeated or severe violations, we may suspend or permanently deactivate the account(s) in question. Airbnb's determination on whether any specific content is prohibited will be final and conclusive.\\n\\n  You can contact us or flag Group posts to report content that violates our Terms of Service or Content Guidelines.\\n\\n\\nListings and Profiles\\n  We expect Hosts to create listings that are honest, clear,\\nand helpful to potential guests. We prohibit:\\n  \\n    Advertising or other commercial content.\\n    Content that endorses or promotes illegal or harmful activity or violence,\\nor is profane, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, threatening, or discriminatory.\\n    Political, religious, or social commentary.\\n    Attempts to impersonate another person.\\n    Content that is fraudulent, false, misleading or deceptive.\\n    Content that refers to an Airbnb investigation.\\n    Content that violates another person or entity\\u2019s rights, including intellectual property\\nrights and privacy rights.\\n  \\n\\nReviews and Neighborhood Feedback\\n  Genuine reviews are the cornerstone of our community. We prohibit:\\n  \\n    Reviews that do not represent users\\u2019 personal experience.\\n    Reviews unrelated to the actual reservation (ex: political, religious, or social commentary).\\n    Content that endorses or promotes illegal or harmful activity or violence, or is profane, vulgar,\\nobscene, defamatory, threatening, or discriminatory.\\n    Content that violates another person or entity\\u2019s rights, including intellectual\\nproperty rights and privacy rights (ex: publishing another person\\u2019s full name,\\naddress or other identifying information without permission).\\n    Content that is proven to be used as extortion.\\n    Content that refers to an Airbnb investigation.\\n  \\nGroups\\n  Airbnb Groups are a way for people around the world to connect and build community.\\nWhen you create a Group, you are responsible for determining its membership.\\nYou may accept or remove members at your discretion. In addition, we prohibit:\\n  \\n    Advertising or other commercial content (ex: advertising for your business).\\nDiscussions or posts unrelated to Airbnb community building (ex: Groups devoted to investing or building a property management business).\\n    Content that endorses or promotes illegal or harmful activity or violence, or is profane, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, threatening, or discriminatory.\\n    Political, religious, or social commentary.\\n    Attempts to impersonate another person.\\n    Content that refers to an Airbnb investigation.\\n    Content that violates another person or entity\\u2019s rights, including intellectual property rights and privacy rights. For example, sometimes people use Groups to create local meetups. In these circumstances, please make sure to get permission before publishing another person\\u2019s real name or other identifying information.\\n", "question": "Content Policy"},
{"answer": "\\n\\n    \\n    \\n        It's important for U.S. hosts to understand their responsibilities under the Fair Housing Act (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA). We've included some useful information and resources below.\\n    \\n    \\n      The Fair Housing Act (FHA)\\n      The Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA)\\n      Improper Discriminatory Practices\\n      Service Animals\\n      State and Local Laws\\n      \\n    The Fair Housing Act (FHA)\\n    \\n        The FHA prohibits housing providers from discriminating against applicants or residents because of race, color, religion, sex, national origin, disability, and familial status\\u2014including children under the age of 18 staying with parents or legal custodians and pregnant women\\u2014in most housing related transactions, with a few limited exceptions.\\n    \\n    \\n        The FHA also makes it unlawful to advertise any preference, limitation, or discrimination based on these categories. One type of disability discrimination prohibited by the FHA is the refusal \"to make reasonable accommodations in rules, policies, practices, or services, when such accommodations may be necessary to afford person(s) [with disabilities] equal opportunity to use and enjoy a dwelling.\"\\n    \\n    \\n        Additionally, the FHA prohibits housing providers from treating persons less favorably than others because of their disability, refusing residency to persons with disabilities, or placing conditions on their residency, because those persons may require reasonable accommodations, and the FHA requires that new covered multifamily housing be designed and constructed to be accessible. The FHA also prohibits harassment of anyone exercising a fair housing right and retaliation against an individual because he or she has assisted\\u2014or participated in any manner\\u2014in a fair housing investigation.\\n    \\n    Does the FHA apply to me as a host?\\n    \\n        The FHA does not apply to all hosts. The FHA contains exemptions for owner-occupied buildings with no more than four units, single-family housing rented without the use of a broker if the private individual owner doesn\\u2019t own more than three such single-family units at one time, and housing operated by organizations and private clubs that limit occupancy to members and so long as all advertising is nondiscriminatory. There is also a bed-and-breakfast or rooming house exemption for properties \"containing living quarters occupied or intended to be occupied by no more than four families living independently of each other, if the owner actually maintains and occupies one of such living quarters as his or her residence\" which might apply to some hosts' listings.\\n    \\n    \\n        The FHA also specifically exempts some senior housing facilities and communities from liability for discrimination based on familial status. To qualify for this exemption, such housing must be intended and operated for occupancy by persons 55 years of age or older or intended for and solely occupied by persons 62 years of age or older. This \"housing for older persons\" exemption does protect against liability for housing discrimination based on race, color, religion, gender, disability or national origin.\\n    \\n    \\n        However, even if you\\u2019re exempt from complying with the FHA, it is still illegal to advertise or make any statement that indicates a limitation or preference based on race, color, national origin, religion, sex, familial status, or handicap. This prohibition against discriminatory advertising applies to single-family and owner-occupied housing that is otherwise exempt from the FHA. More information can be found at 24 C.F.R. pt. 100.\\n    \\n    \\n        Even if the FHA does not apply to you, we expect our hosts to conduct themselves in a respectful manner and work to bridge differences and make accommodations where possible. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe.\\n    \\n        Under the FHA, may I exclude people with children?\\n    \\n        If the FHA applies to you, in most instances, you may not exclude children. More information on this exemption can be found at 24 C.F.R. pt. 100, subpart E.\\n    \\n    \\n    Back to Top\\n    \\n    \\n    The Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA)\\n    \\n        The ADA prohibits discrimination on the basis of disability by places of public accommodation and places of public accommodation must comply with basic nondiscrimination requirements that prohibit exclusion, segregation, and unequal treatment. They also must comply with specific requirements related to architectural standards for new and altered buildings; reasonable modifications to policies, practices, and procedures; effective communication with people with hearing, vision, or speech disabilities; and other access requirements. Additionally, public accommodations must remove barriers in existing buildings where it is easy to do so without much difficulty or expense, given the public accommodation's resources. To be protected under the ADA, an individual must have a disability or have a relationship or association with an individual with a disability.\\n    \\n    Does the ADA apply to me as a host?\\n    \\n        The ADA does not apply to all hosts. In most cases, the ADA does not apply to residential housing. As a host, you\\u2019re subject to the provisions of the ADA if your listing fits its criteria for a \"place of public accommodation.\" Federal regulations (28 C.F.R. \\xa7 36.104) define a place of public accommodation to include a place of lodging, except for an establishment located within a facility that contains not more than five rooms for rent or hire and that actually is occupied by the proprietor of the establishment as the residence of the proprietor.\\n    \\n    \\n    This means that if you are a host renting out five or fewer rooms, the ADA does not likely apply to you. However, you should review the law and additional information regarding the definition of a \\u201cplace of lodging\\u201d at 28 C.F.R. \\xa7 36.104.\\n    \\n    \\n        Even if the ADA does not apply to you, we expect our hosts to conduct themselves in a respectful manner and work to bridge differences and make accommodations where possible. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe.\\n    \\n    Back to Top\\n    \\n    Improper Discriminatory Practices\\n    \\n        Any of the following actions are discriminatory if they are based on a person's race, color, religion, sex, handicap, familial status, or national origin:\\n    \\n    \\n        Refusing to rent, or applying more burdensome criteria to certain guests\\n        Misrepresenting the availability of a unit\\n        Discriminating in choosing guests\\n        Limiting the use of common facilities\\n        Failing to provide the same level of service, or adding extra fees or payments\\n        Denying a request for a reasonable accommodation\\n        Threatening, coercing, intimidating or interfering with anyone exercising a fair housing right or assisting others who exercise that right\\n    \\n    \\n        Bear in mind this list is not exhaustive.\\n    \\n    Back to Top\\n    \\n    Service Animals\\n    What is a service animal?\\n    \\n        You must accept service animals if the ADA or FHA applies to your listing. A service animal, in short, is a guide dog, signal dog, or other animal individually trained to provide assistance to an individual with a disability. If they meet this definition, animals are considered service animals under the ADA regardless of whether they have been licensed or certified by a state or local government. Some, but not all, service animals wear special collars and harnesses. Some, but not all, are licensed or certified and have identification papers.\\n    \\n    \\n        Remember that even if the ADA or FHA do not apply to you, there may be additional (broader) state laws that do.\\n    \\n    I have a clear \"no pets\" policy. Do I still have to allow service animals?\\n    \\n        If the ADA or FHA applies to you, yes. A service animal is not a pet. The ADA requires you to modify your no-pets policy to allow the use of a service animal by a person with a disability.\\n    \\n    May I charge a special maintenance or cleaning fee for guests who bring service animals?\\n    \\n        If the ADA or FHA applies to you, no. You may charge guests with disabilities if a service animal causes damage, so long as it is the regular practice to charge non-disabled customers for the same types of damages.\\n    \\n    Am I responsible for the service animal while the person with a disability is my guest? What if the animal is threatening?\\n    \\n        No. The care or supervision of a service animal is solely the responsibility of his or her owner. You\\u2019re not required to provide care or food or a special location for the animal. You may exclude any animal, including a service animal, when that animal's behavior poses a direct threat to the health or safety of others.\\n    \\n    Do I have to accept guests with service animals even if I am allergic, or animals are prohibited in my building, etc.?\\n    \\n        If you\\u2019re covered by the ADA or the FHA, you may be required to accept service animals or assistance animals, no matter your building\\u2019s policy or your allergies.\\n    \\n    Back to Top\\n    \\n        State and Local Laws\\n    \\n        While the FHA and ADA\\u2014which are federal laws\\u2014provide for minimum requirements, you may also be subject to additional and more stringent local laws that prohibit discrimination. Many states and local communities have passed anti-discrimination ordinances and statutes, and renters\\u2019 rights vary greatly from state to state. As a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing(s).\\n    \\n    Back to Top\\n", "question": "ADA and FHA Compliance Policy"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tThe Airbnb Host Guarantee provides protection for up to $1,000,000 to a host for damages to covered property in the rare event of guest damages above the security deposit\\u2014or if no security deposit is in place.\\n\\n\\tThe Host Guarantee Program doesn't cover cash and securities, collectibles, rare artwork, jewelry, pets or personal liability. We recommend that hosts secure or remove valuables when renting their place. The program also doesn't cover loss or damage to property due to wear and tear. For these types of incidents, hosts can add a security deposit in their pricing settings.\\n\\n\\tThe Host Guarantee Program isn't insurance and doesn't replace your homeowners or renters insurance. Make sure you review and understand the terms of your insurance policy and what it covers and doesn't cover. Not all insurance will cover damage or loss to property caused by a guest renting your space. Filing a host guarantee request doesn't preclude a guest from financial responsibility for the damages claimed if Airbnb determines a guest was at fault.\\n\\n\\tLearn more about the Host Guarantee at: www.airbnb.com/guarantee.\\n\\t\\n\\tView the Host Guarantee terms and conditions at: www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee. If you can't view this page, the country you're accessing Airbnb from doesn't have Host Guarantee coverage right now.", "question": "What is the Airbnb Host Guarantee?"},
{"answer": "\\n  \\n   If your host canceled your reservation, you can transfer your payment to a new Airbnb reservation or request a refund.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nIf you experience a travel issue that prevents you from being able to complete a trip with Airbnb, and you\\u2019re unable to resolve with your host, our Guest Refund Policy may be applied in certain circumstances.\\n  \\n  Eligible travel issues\\nSituations that may be eligible for a refund under this policy generally fall into one of three categories: \\n\\nThe host fails to provide reasonable access to the booked listing.\\nThe listing booked is misrepresented (ex: number of bedrooms, location, lacks promised amenities).\\nThe listing isn't generally clean, is unsafe, or there's an animal in the listing that wasn't disclosed prior to booking.\\n  \\n\\nAirbnb will either provide you with a refund or use reasonable efforts to find and book you at another comparable accommodation for any unused nights left in your reservation. The amount of any refund will depend on the nature of the travel Issue suffered.\\n\\nSubmit a valid claim for refund\\nTo submit a valid claim for your reservation, you are required to:\\n\\nContact us within 24 hours of check-in to document the issue and place a hold on the host's payment. Include photographs or other evidence of the issue as part of your claim.\\nBe responsive to our requests for additional information and cooperation.\\nNot have directly or indirectly caused the Travel Issue.\\nHave used reasonable efforts to remedy the circumstances of the Travel Issue with the host prior to making a claim, including messaging your host on Airbnb to notify them of the issue. We'll verify this in your account.\\n\\nReview the Guest Refund Policy Terms for more details, including more information about the minimum quality standards for accommodations, and what qualifies as a travel issue.", "question": "Guest Refund Policy"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tAirbnb is an open marketplace. Through their experiences on Airbnb, we hope that our guests and hosts build meaningful connections with people from all over the globe.\\n\\n\\tTo that end, we prohibit content that promotes discrimination, bigotry, racism, hatred, harassment or harm against any individual or group, and we require all users to comply with local laws and regulations.\\n\\n\\tMany countries, including the U.S., have laws preventing discrimination on the basis of race, religion, national origin, disability, sex, sexual orientation, or age. In the U.S., anti-discrimination laws apply to discrimination by any inn, hotel, motel, or other establishment that provides lodging to guests. The two main federal laws in this area are the Fair Housing Act (Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of 1968) (FHA) and the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA).\\n\\n\\tThe Americans with Disabilities Act prohibits discrimination in public accommodations on the basis of disability, which may include things such as access and service dogs.\\n\\n\\tIn addition, fair housing laws often prohibit discrimination in the selling or renting of such housing based on race, national origin, religion, sex, familial status or disability.\\n\\n\\tAs a host, you should be familiar with the laws that apply to you and your listing.\\n\\n\\tIf you believe a listing or person on the site is in violation of this position, let us know.", "question": "What is Airbnb's Anti-Discrimination Policy?"},
{"answer": "To help keep our community safe and trusted, we\\u2019ve published Standards and Expectations for all of our hosts and travelers. \\nWe developed these standards based on our extensive experience interacting with members of the Airbnb community.  These standards are intended to gather together our existing policies into a single framework that will help members of the Airbnb community better understand what to expect from us and what we expect of them.\\nHow will the standards be enforced?\\nEach enforcement decision is the result of careful and detailed work by a team of experts devoted to ensuring we make the right call. Our responses to violations of these policies have been and will continue to be based on the seriousness of the issue. We will strive to take the circumstances of each situation into account when reaching our enforcement decision, but we have limited discretion in our response to serious violations of the policies.\\nWhat can I do if I disagree with a decision?\\nOur enforcement teams are made up of dedicated professionals, but they\\u2019re still human.  So, in rare cases, enforcement decisions may be incorrect. If you disagree with a decision we\\u2019ve made, you can contact us and we\\u2019ll re-review the decision carefully. The definitions of the standards and expectations themselves aren\\u2019t subject to review.\\nWill the standards change over time?\\nWe\\u2019re always learning and growing and the standards and expectations will evolve over time. Make sure to review the standards if you have any questions about a particular situation.", "question": "Standards & Expectations"},
{"answer": "Airbnb empowers hosts to set and manage their cancellation policies. If a host or guest needs to cancel a reservation, it\\u2019s their responsibility to cancel as soon as possible. At times, certain circumstances outside of a host or guest\\u2019s control can impact their ability to meet the terms of a reservation.\\n\\nIn rare instances, if Airbnb determines that a Guest\\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, Airbnb may override the Host's cancellation policy (ex: flexible, moderate, strict) and make refund decisions.  If Airbnb determines that a Host\\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances policy, Airbnb may waive the host cancellation penalties outlined in Airbnb\\u2019s Terms of Service and Airbnb\\u2019s Payments Terms of Service.\\n\\nWhat might be covered?\\n\\nValid extenuating circumstances include:\\n\\n\\nUnexpected death or serious illness of a host, guest or immediate family member \\nSerious injury that directly restricts a guest\\u2019s ability to travel or a host\\u2019s ability to host\\nSignificant natural disasters or severe weather incidents impacting the location of destination or location of departure\\nUrgent travel restrictions or severe security advisories issued after the time of booking, by an appropriate national or international authority (such as a government office or department)\\nEndemic disease declared by a credible national or international authority (such as the US Center for Disease Control or the World Health Organization)\\nSevere property damage or unforeseen maintenance issues that directly impact the ability to host safely\\nGovernment-mandated obligations issued after the time of booking\\n\\n\\nIf you need to make a claim\\n\\nClaims can only be considered after a reservation has been canceled. Once you have informed your host or guest and canceled a reservation, if you feel that your reason for cancellation is covered by Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, contact Airbnb for consideration. We generally require claims to be submitted no later than 14 days from the original check-in date and we may require valid supporting documentation.", "question": "Extenuating Circumstances Policy"},
{"answer": "\\n  \\n\\n\\nBusiness travelers can use their regular Airbnb accounts to book business travel\\u2014all you need to do is link your work email address to your Airbnb account so we can confirm that you work for the company you say you work for. \\n\\n  If you need to switch the account your work email is linked to, or just no longer want your accounts to be linked, follow the steps below to unlink (or relink) your work email address and your personal Airbnb account:\\n  \\n  \\n        Go to Profile on airbnb.com\\n            \\n            Scroll down to Business Travel\\n            Click the X to unlink your accounts or the + Add work email to relink them\\n\\n\\nIf you unlink your accounts, you won't be able to use your company's payment information to pay for your business travel reservations.\\n\\nNote: If you're the only travel manager for a company's account, we recommend you add another travel manager before unlinking your accounts.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I join my company's business travel account?\\nWhat is Airbnb Business Travel?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I unlink or relink my work email address and Airbnb account?"},
{"answer": "If your company uses Concur\\u2019s TripLink service, you\\u2019ll need to link your Airbnb and Concur accounts to have your Airbnb reservation receipts automatically uploaded to your Concur account.\\n\\nLink your accounts\\n To link your Airbnb and Concur TripLink accounts:\\n\\nGo to Airbnb in the  Concur App Center, and click Connect\\nLog in to your existing Airbnb account or, if you don\\u2019t already have an account, create a new one\\n\\n\\nOnce your accounts are linked, you can have the receipt for any Airbnb reservation appear in your Concur account by marking the box next to Send this booking to Concur on the reservation request checkout page. \\n\\nUnlink your accounts\\n\\nTo unlink your Airbnb and Concur TripLink accounts:\\n\\nGo to Account on airbnb.com\\nSelect Settings on the left side\\nUnder Unlink From Concur, click Unlink\\n", "question": "How do I expense my business trip using Concur TripLink?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIf you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.\\n\\n\\t  To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:\\n\\n\\n\\t\\tGo to Edit Profile on airbnb.com\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tUnder Optional, click Add VAT ID Number\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tEnter your VAT ID number verification information\\n\\t\\t\\n\\t\\tClick Verify\\n\\t\\t\\n\\t\\tClick Save\\n\\n\\nWhen your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services. \\n\\nProblems verifying VAT ID number\\n\\n\\nIf your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.\\n\\n \\nIf your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Article\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     Where do I find my VAT invoice?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "\\n  Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.\\n  They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund.\\n\\nFind your itinerary\\n\\n  Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\nNext to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary.\\n\\nFind your receipt\\n\\nGo to Your Trips on airbnb.com.\\n  Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nInformation found in an itinerary\\nYour itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:\\n\\n  Check-in time\\n    Listing address\\n  Detailed directions from your host\\n  Telephone number for your host\\n  Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details\\n  House manual\\n  House rules\\n  Your billing information\\n  Airbnb's contact information\\n\\nInformation found in a receipt\\nYour billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:\\n\\n  Name of the guest who made the booking\\n    Any additional guest names you've included\\n  Number of total guests for the reservation\\n  Address of the listing\\n  Name of the host\\n  Dates of the reservation\\n  Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.\\n  \\n    Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.\\n  \\n  \\n\\nLearn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "After you\\u2019ve booked a reservation, you can add guest names and a business address to your billing receipt. Once the reservation ends, you won\\u2019t be able to make any changes to the receipt.\\n Information like passport numbers, birthdates, and tax identification numbers can\\u2019t be added to a receipt.\\n Add guest names\\n To add guest names to your receipt, you have to update the names on your itinerary.\\n \\n   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n      Next to the trip you want to edit, click View Itinerary\\n   Next to Guests, click Manage Guests\\n   Add or remove names of the other guests staying at the listing\\n   The names are automatically updated on the billing receipt\\n \\n \\n\\n Add a business address\\n  \\n \\n   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n      Next to the trip you want to edit, click View Itinerary\\n   Next to Billing, click Detailed Receipt\\n   On the receipt, click Add billing details\\n   Add the business address and other relevant information\\n   Click Save\\n \\n Note: Adding VAT details to your business information is documentation only and won't affect VAT charged on your reservation. VAT invoices can't be changed. Learn more about how VAT may apply to you.\\n \\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I find my trip itinerary or receipt?\\nWhat is Airbnb for Business?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How can I add a guest or business address to my receipt?"},
{"answer": "Business guests can identify a reservation as a business trip by selecting Business travel on the checkout page. Any notes you add in the What\\u2019s the purpose of this trip? box will be sent your company\\u2019s travel manager.\\n\\nChoosing Business travel won\\u2019t tell your host that you\\u2019re traveling for work, but sharing information about your trip in a message to your host is a great way to help them understand your business travel needs.\\n\\nAlready booked your trip? You can identify your reservation as a business trip at any time from your itinerary. Scroll down and select the checkbox next to This is a business trip in the Business Travel section.", "question": "How do I identify a reservation as a business trip?"},
{"answer": "Business Travel Ready listings must be an Entire Home/Apt and an eligible property type (house, apartment, bed &amp; breakfast, townhouse, loft, or condo). The listing must be no smoking, and can\\u2019t have pets on the property.\\n\\nThe space\\nMany business travelers are new to traveling on Airbnb, so we\\u2019ve limited Business Travel Ready listings to certain property types to help make sure guests know what to expect when they arrive.\\n\\nAs a part of this, and because of the potential for allergies and other sensitivities, we also ask that Business Travel Ready listings are smoke-free properties and don\\u2019t have pets living in the space while the guest is there.\\n\\nIf a pet lives in your space, but won\\u2019t be there during your guest\\u2019s stay we ask that you\\u2019re aware of traveler\\u2019s potential allergens and make sure your listing is cleaned before your guest\\u2019s arrival.\\n\\nAmenities\\nThe listing must also have the following Business Travel Ready amenities:\\n\\n  Wireless Internet\\nA laptop-friendly workspace\\n24-hour check-in (this could be a lockbox, doorman, keyless entry or similar 24-hour access)\\nA smoke detector\\nA carbon monoxide detector\\nEssentials (toilet paper, clean towels, and fresh linens)\\nAn iron\\nHangers\\nA hair dryer\\nShampoo\\n\\n\\nSmoke and carbon monoxide detectors are an important part of making Airbnb a trusted travel option for companies. As part of our commitment to guest safety, Airbnb offers free smoke and carbon monoxide detectors for hosts: www.airbnb.com/home-safety.\\n\\nReviews and response rate\\nListings must have at least 3 star rated reviews before they can be eligible for Business Travel Ready status. For listings with 3 or more star rated reviews, at least 60% of both the listing\\u2019s primary reviews, and the listing\\u2019s reviews for cleanliness and accuracy must be 5 star reviews.\\n\\nHosts of Business Travel Ready listings also must have responded to 90% of booking requests within 24 hours over the last year.\\n\\nCancellations\\nHosts of Business Travel Ready listings must provide a 7-day cancellation commitment to reservations. If a listing has a cancellation within 7 days of a confirmed check-in date, it can't be considered for Business Travel Ready for 1 year from the cancellation date.\\n\\nEligibility\\nListings and their hosts are evaluated for business travel readiness on a rolling basis. Keep in mind that you and your listing need to continue to qualify after the initial evaluation in order to maintain Business Travel Ready status.\\n\\nIf you\\u2019re a host, learn more or get started now.\\n\\nQuestions? Review the Business Travel Ready Terms &amp; Conditions.", "question": "What makes a listing Business Travel Ready?"},
{"answer": "Once your company is enrolled in Airbnb for Business, you\\u2019re ready to start planning your next work trip.\\n\\nOnce you've verified your work email address, start a search on the Airbnb for Business homepage. From there you can easily filter by location, type of space, and the amenities each host offers.\\n\\nBusiness Travel Ready listings also have a badge to help travelers find them. Just look for the briefcase .\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n \\nWhat makes a listing Business Travel Ready?\\nHow do I join my company's business travel account?\\nHow do I identify a reservation as a business trip?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I search for listings for my business trip?"},
{"answer": "To join your team's business travel account on Airbnb, you can link your work email address to your existing personal account, or, if you don't already have an Airbnb account, create a new account with your work details.\\n\\nLinking your work email address to your personal Airbnb account just lets us confirm that you work for your company\\u2014you\\u2019ll still use your personal email address and existing password to sign in to your account.\\n\\nLink your existing Airbnb account\\n\\n  If you already have an Airbnb account:\\n\\n    Go to airbnb.com/business\\n    Log in to your Airbnb account\\n    Enter your work email address and click Add Email\\n\\n\\nYou should see a verification email in your work inbox soon. Once you've received it, click Verify Business Email, then follow the steps on screen to complete your verification.\\n\\nCreate a new account\\n\\nIf you need to create an Airbnb account:\\n\\n    Go to airbnb.com/business\\n    Click Get Started\\n    Choose a way to sign up and follow the steps on screen\\n  \\n  \\n    Once you've created an account, you should see a verification email in your work inbox. Click Verify Business Email in that email and follow the steps on screen to complete your verification.\\n\\n\\n\"Please enter a valid company email\" error\\n\\nAt this time, you can't join a company's business travel account or register your company using public domains (ex: gmail.com, hotmail.com).\\n\\nEven if you already have a personal Airbnb account, make sure you're entering the email address associated your company's domain (ex: name@companyname.com) on airbnb.com/business. We'll help you link your personal account and work email address from there.", "question": "How do I join my company's Airbnb for Business account?"},
{"answer": "At this time, reviews can\\u2019t be written for canceled reservations. If you\\u2019d like to provide feedback for your host, you can send them a quick message using your Airbnb message thread. \\n\\nHosts: when you cancel a reservation, a review is automatically added to your listing\\u2019s page indicating that a reservation was canceled. These reviews are one of the penalties for canceling and can\\u2019t be removed. Learn more", "question": "Can I leave a review for a canceled reservation?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIf you cancel a reservation as a host, an automated review will be posted to your profile. These reviews are one of the host cancellation penalties and can't be removed.\\n\\t\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do host cancellation penalties work? \\nCan I reply to a review?\\nExtenuating Circumstances for Host Cancellations?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Why did I get a review that says I canceled?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb for Business makes it easy to travel for work without sacrificing the comforts of home. \\n\\nBusiness travelers\\n\\nIf your company is already enrolled in Airbnb for Business, join their account by visiting airbnb.com/business-travel.\\n\\nBusiness Travel Ready listings\\nSome homes have a badge to indicate that they\\u2019re Business Travel Ready. These listings meet certain requirements for home type, amenities, check-in, reviews, responsiveness, and host commitment\\u2014you\\u2019ll see them identified with a briefcase .\\n\\nTravel managers\\nFor travel managers, the Airbnb for Business program provides better transparency and more accurate reporting for their company. If you manage your company's travel arrangements, sign your company up for Airbnb for Business by visiting airbnb.com/business/signup.\\n\\nOnce you\\u2019re enrolled, learn more about using your travel manager account and dashboard.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nI'm a travel manager. How do I get started with Airbnb for Business?\\nHow do I join my company's business travel account?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is Airbnb for Business?"},
{"answer": "Yes, but only within 14 days of when you received the review\\u2014we\\u2019ll post it directly below the review you're responding to. \\n\\n\\nTo write a response:\\n\\nGo to Edit Profile on airbnb.com\\nClick Reviews\\nSelect Reviews About You\\nFind the review you\\u2019d like to respond to and click Leave a Response\\n\\n\\nIf you're a host and received a review related to a cancellation learn more.", "question": "Can I reply to a review?"},
{"answer": "When you complete your first business stay at an Airbnb listing, we\\u2019ll give you a $50 coupon to use towards your next Airbnb trip. \\n\\nHow do I get the coupon code?\\nYou\\u2019ll receive an email with your personalized $50 coupon code after you've checked in to your qualifying reservation.\\n\\nPromotion details\\n\\n  The coupon code will be sent to the email address you use to log in to your Airbnb account\\nThe $50 coupon is valid for one year\\nThe coupon can only be used towards one reservation\\nThere are no restrictions on destination or travel dates\\nOnce applied, the coupon can't be refunded, even if the reservation is canceled\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I apply a coupon code?\\nHow do I identify a reservation as a business trip?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Airbnb for Business: $50 promotion"},
{"answer": "No. Reviews can't be changed or deleted, but you can always write a public response.\\n\\nView Airbnb's complete review guidelines.", "question": "Can I delete a review?"},
{"answer": "We believe in free speech, transparency, and clear communication. When creating a review, we ask that you stick to the facts. The best reviews provide constructive information that helps the community make better decisions. \\n    \\n    Airbnb's default position is not to censor, edit, or delete reviews. However, we reserve the right to remove reviews that violate our content policy.\\n    \\n   We don't allow:\\n      \\n          Reviews that do not represent a user\\u2019s personal experience            .\\n        Reviews unrelated to the actual reservation (ex: political,             religious, or social commentary).\\n        Content that endorses or promotes illegal or harmful activity or         violence, or is profane, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, threatening,          or discriminatory.\\n        Content that violates another person\\u2019s or entity\\u2019s rights,              including intellectual property rights and privacy rights (ex:              publishing another person\\u2019s full name, address or other identifying         information without permission).\\n       Content that is proven to be used as extortion.\\n      Content that refers to an Airbnb investigation.\\n    \\n    \\n    \\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nHow do reviews work?\\nCan I delete a review?\\nCan I reply to a review?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What are Airbnb's review guidelines?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tAll the reviews on Airbnb are written by hosts and travelers from our community, so any review you see is based on a stay that a guest had in a host's listing.\\n\\n Writing a review\\n        \\n            To leave a review for a recent trip, go to your Reviews. Reviews are limited to 500 words and must follow Airbnb's review guidelines. You can edit your review for up to 48 hours, or until your host or guest completes their review. \\n        \\n        Review history\\n         To see reviews you've written or reviews about you, go to your Reviews. You'll also see any private feedback that people have left you. \\n\\n\\tOur community relies on honest, transparent reviews. We will remove or alter a review if we find that it violates our review guidelines.\\n   \\n   \\n   \\n   \\n    \\n", "question": "How do reviews work?"},
{"answer": "You can search for your listing using terms that match your listing description and calendar availability. Your Business Travel Ready listing will have a badge to help travelers find it, just look for the briefcase .\\n\\nKeep in mind that it can take up to 12 hours for new listings to appear in search results and up to one hour for changes to an existing listing's visibility to take effect.", "question": "Where can I see my Business Travel Ready listing?"},
{"answer": "Business guests can identify a reservation as a business trip by selecting Business travel on the checkout page. Any notes you add in the What\\u2019s the purpose of this trip? box will be sent your company\\u2019s travel manager.\\n\\nChoosing Business travel won\\u2019t tell your host that you\\u2019re traveling for work, but sharing information about your trip in a message to your host is a great way to help them understand your business travel needs.\\n\\nAlready booked your trip? You can identify your reservation as a business trip at any time from your itinerary. Scroll down and select the checkbox next to This is a business trip in the Business Travel section.", "question": "How do I identify a reservation as a business trip?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tThe Airbnb Host Guarantee provides protection for up to $1,000,000 to a host for damages to covered property in the rare event of guest damages above the security deposit\\u2014or if no security deposit is in place.\\n\\n\\tThe Host Guarantee Program doesn't cover cash and securities, collectibles, rare artwork, jewelry, pets or personal liability. We recommend that hosts secure or remove valuables when renting their place. The program also doesn't cover loss or damage to property due to wear and tear. For these types of incidents, hosts can add a security deposit in their pricing settings.\\n\\n\\tThe Host Guarantee Program isn't insurance and doesn't replace your homeowners or renters insurance. Make sure you review and understand the terms of your insurance policy and what it covers and doesn't cover. Not all insurance will cover damage or loss to property caused by a guest renting your space. Filing a host guarantee request doesn't preclude a guest from financial responsibility for the damages claimed if Airbnb determines a guest was at fault.\\n\\n\\tLearn more about the Host Guarantee at: www.airbnb.com/guarantee.\\n\\t\\n\\tView the Host Guarantee terms and conditions at: www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee. If you can't view this page, the country you're accessing Airbnb from doesn't have Host Guarantee coverage right now.", "question": "What is the Airbnb Host Guarantee?"},
{"answer": "No. We\\u2019ve made it easy to manage your company\\u2019s business travel by adding a specialized dashboard that you can access from your personal Airbnb account. From the dashboard, you can view active or upcoming trips, itinerary details, and financial reporting.\\n\\nTo access the dashboard:\\n\\n\\n  Hover over your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.\\n\\nSelect Business Travel\\n\\nYou\\u2019ll need to link your work email address to your account and be added as a travel manager before you can access this dashboard.\\n\\nIf your company isn\\u2019t enrolled in Airbnb for Business yet, learn how to enroll.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nI'm a travel manager. How do I get started with Airbnb for Business?\\nHow do I use my travel manager account?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Do I need to create a new Airbnb account to manage my company's travel?"},
{"answer": "Business Travel Ready hosts must provide 24-hour access to the listing for the duration of a guest\\u2019s stay\\u2014this starts with check-in.\\n\\n24-hour check-in means that your guest should be able to check in at any time after the check-in time you set for your listing on their arrival date. 24-hour check-in could be something like a lockbox, a doorman, a buzzer, or keyless entry.", "question": "What is 24-hour check-in?"},
{"answer": "Travel managers can create groups of travelers (ex: departments, office locations) and assign a name and payment method to each group from the travel manager dashboard. Travelers will then have the option to \"Charge to\" that group when they book a business trip through Airbnb.\\n\\nAdding or editing a group\\n  To create a new group:\\n    \\n      Go to your Business Travel dashboard\\n      Click People &gt; Groups\\n      Click Create Group\\n      Add a group name and select a payment method for the group\\n      Click Save\\n   \\n   \\n  Travelers will see the group name you choose when they bill business travel to the company (ex: Charge to Sales, Charge to North America Office).\\n  To add employees to a group:\\n    \\n      Go to Groups and click the group you want to edit\\n      Click Add Members and select or search for employees by name\\n      Click Save\\n   \\n\\n  To edit an existing group\\u2019s payment info:\\n    \\n      Go to Groups and click the group you want to edit\\n     Click Change Payment Method\\n     Under Payment Method select an existing credit card or choose Add Credit Card\\n     Add payments details and click Save\\n   \\n\\n  You won't be able to switch from payment by credit card to monthly invoicing or vice versa. If you want to switch a group's payment type from credit card to monthly invoicing, you'll need to delete and re-create the group.\\n\\nDeleting a group\\n  To delete a group:\\n    \\n      Go to Groups and click the group you want to edit\\n      Click Edit Group\\n      Click Delete This Group, then click Save\\n", "question": "How do I set up payment groups for my company?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb for Business makes it easy to travel for work without sacrificing the comforts of home. If you manage your company's travel read on to learn more about:\\n \\n \\n      How do I enroll my company?\\n       How do I set up my company's account?\\n       I already have a personal Airbnb account, do I need to set up a new one to manage my company's travel?\\n       How do I add or remove an employee from my company's account?\\n       How do I add another travel manager?\\n      \\n    \\n      \\n\\n How do I enroll my company?\\nTo enroll your company, go to airbnb.com/business/signup. After filling out the necessary information, you\\u2019ll be asked to verify your email address before setting up your company\\u2019s account. \\n\\n\\n\\nHow do I set up my company's account?\\n\\nWe\\u2019ll walk you through the steps to set up your company\\u2019s account after you confirm your email address. You'll start by:\\n\\n\\n    Inviting your employees to the program. You can add individual email addresses or upload them in bulk.\\n  Adding your company\\u2019s credit card. This gives your employees an easy way to pay for their Airbnb trip.\\n\\n\\nI already have a personal Airbnb account, do I need to set up a new one to manage my company's travel?\\n\\nNo. We\\u2019ve made it easy to manage your company\\u2019s travel by adding a specialized travel manager dashboard\\u2014which you'll be able to use from your existing Airbnb account. From this dashboard, you can invite employees, view active or upcoming trips, see itinerary details, and more.\\n\\nTo access your travel manager dashboard, go to airbnb.com/business/dashboard\\n\\nHow do I add or remove an employee from my company's account?\\n\\nTo add a traveler, go to People  and click Invite New Travelers.\\n\\nTo remove a traveler:\\n\\n  Go to the People section of your dashboard\\n  In the Travelers tab, click X next to the traveler you'd like to remove\\n\\n\\nHow do I add a travel manager or booker?\\n\\nTo add a travel manager or booker:\\n\\n Go to the People section of your dashboard\\n  Click Add People\\n  Choose a role under Select a role, then add the person's email address below\\n  Click Add People to save\\n", "question": "I'm a travel manager. How do I get started with Airbnb for Business?"},
{"answer": "Viewing your dashboard\\n  Once you\\u2019re logged in, visit your travel manager dashboard at airbnb.com/business/dashboard. This dashboard split up into 4 main sections: Activity, Reporting, People, and Settings.\\n\\n  \\n    Activity: Use the Activity section to see an overview of employee\\u2019s active and upcoming trips. For each trip you\\u2019ll see traveler name, destination, booking and trip dates, and number of guests.\\n    Reporting: Use the Reporting section to see details about number of nights booked, total amount spent, and average daily rate across your company. You can also export CSV reports from this page.\\n    People: Use the People section to view and manage the employee accounts that are linked to your company. You can also view, add, or remove travel managers from this page.\\n    Settings: Use the  Settings section of your dashboard to edit your company\\u2019s info, update your payment settings, change who can join your company\\u2019s account, and add or update your email alert settings.\\n", "question": "How do I use my travel manager account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb for Business makes it easy to travel for work without sacrificing the comforts of home. \\n\\nBusiness travelers\\n\\nIf your company is already enrolled in Airbnb for Business, join their account by visiting airbnb.com/business-travel.\\n\\nBusiness Travel Ready listings\\nSome homes have a badge to indicate that they\\u2019re Business Travel Ready. These listings meet certain requirements for home type, amenities, check-in, reviews, responsiveness, and host commitment\\u2014you\\u2019ll see them identified with a briefcase .\\n\\nTravel managers\\nFor travel managers, the Airbnb for Business program provides better transparency and more accurate reporting for their company. If you manage your company's travel arrangements, sign your company up for Airbnb for Business by visiting airbnb.com/business/signup.\\n\\nOnce you\\u2019re enrolled, learn more about using your travel manager account and dashboard.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nI'm a travel manager. How do I get started with Airbnb for Business?\\nHow do I join my company's business travel account?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is Airbnb for Business?"},
{"answer": "\\n            The following information is provided for law enforcement entities seeking information about users of the Airbnb platform.\\n        All other requests for information regarding the Airbnb platform, including user questions regarding reservations and user information, should be directed to our Customer Experience team.\\n        \\n        \\n        \\n            We reserve the right to make changes to the information on this page at any given time without notice. You should check this page each time you're making a request.\\n        \\n        \\n            Emergency Requests\\n            \\n            Cross-Border Information Requests\\n            \\n            Requests from US Law Enforcement\\n            \\n            Requests from Non-US Law Enforcment\\n            \\n            Form of Requests\\n            \\n        \\n        \\n        \\n        Emergency Requests\\n        In the event of an emergency involving the danger of death or serious physical injury to a person, law enforcement agents may make an emergency disclosure request by emailing leoinfo@airbnb.com with the subject: Emergency Disclosure Request.\\n\\n        Users or non-law-enforcement third parties aware of an emergency situation should not contact us at this email address, but instead should immediately and directly contact local law enforcement officials. Other urgent communications may be directed to Airbnb's Customer Experience team.\\n        Back to Top\\n        \\n        \\n        \\n        Cross-Border Information Requests\\n        If Airbnb Ireland\\u2019s initial research shows that the concerned data subject is likely a US resident, the guidelines that apply for requests from US law enforcement will be followed. Non-US law enforcement seeking information about US users needs to serve the request on the registered agent in the US, and Airbnb, Inc. may require the requesting law enforcement authority to follow the MLAT processes.\\n        Also, if Airbnb, Inc.\\u2019s initial research shows that the concerned data subject is likely a non-US resident, the guidelines that apply for requests from non-US law enforcement are to be followed. US law enforcement seeking information about non-US users needs to serve the request on Airbnb Ireland, and Airbnb Ireland may require the requesting law enforcement Authority to follow the MLAT processes.\\n        Back to Top\\n        \\n        \\n        \\n        Requests from US Law Enforcement\\n        All law enforcement requests for user information should be directed to Airbnb, Inc., located in San Francisco, California. Airbnb will respond to valid, properly served legal process to the extent permitted by our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, and US law, through service on its Registered Agent for Service of Process in Delaware and California: Corporation Service Company, 2711 Centerville Road, Suite 400, Wilmington, DE 19808, 866-403-5272, 302-636-5454 (fax), www.cscglobal.com, and/or at 888 Brannan Street, San Francisco, CA 94103 Attn: Legal. To expedite review of a request, in addition to serving Airbnb\\u2019s Registered Agent, please fax a copy of the legal process to 1-888-927-3493.\\n        The following materials are required for non-emergency information requests from US law enforcement:\\n        \\n            A valid trial, grand jury or administrative subpoena is required to compel the disclosure of basic subscriber records (defined in 18 USC \\xa7 2703(c)(2)).\\n            A court order issued pursuant to 18 USC \\xa7 2703(d) is required to compel the disclosure of certain other records pertaining to an account, not including contents of communications.\\n            For content of communications, a search warrant issued under the procedures described in the US Federal Rules of Criminal Procedure (or equivalent state warrant procedures) is required.\\n        \\n        Notification\\n        Please note that Airbnb, Inc. has a policy of using commercially reasonable efforts to notify users in the United States when we receive legal process from a third party requesting user data. Generally, except where a court order (and not just the request for information itself) requires delayed notification or no notification, or except where notification is otherwise prohibited by law or where we, in our sole discretion, believe that providing notice would be futile, ineffective or would create a risk of injury or bodily harm to an individual or group, or to our property, we will endeavor to provide reasonable prior notice to the relevant user of the request for user data in the event the user wishes to seek appropriate protective relief.\\n        Back to Top\\n        \\n        \\n        \\n        Requests from Non-US Law Enforcement\\n        All law enforcement requests for user information from non-US law enforcement should be directed to Airbnb Ireland, located in Dublin, Ireland. Generally, Airbnb Ireland will respond to a valid and properly notified legal request to the extent permitted by our Terms of Service, Privacy Policy and applicable law. Requests should be directed to:\\n        \\n        \\n            \\n                Airbnb Ireland\\n                Law Enforcement Liaison\\n                The Watermarque Building\\n                South Lotts Road\\n                Ringsend\\n                Dublin 4\\n                Ireland\\n            \\n        \\n        To expedite review of a request, in addition to notifying Airbnb Ireland by mail, please fax a copy of your request to 35316971830.\\n        Specifically the following is required for requests from non-US law enforcement:\\n        \\n            In case of alleged crimes against a person, a person\\u2019s property or alleged fraud, a valid police request on Police Department letterhead is required for the disclosure of basic subscriber records, transactional information or basic payments-related data (not including contents of communications) to be considered by Airbnb Ireland.\\n            For all other alleged crimes, a valid request on your law enforcement agency\\u2019s letterhead is required for the disclosure of basic subscriber records to be considered by Airbnb Ireland and a valid order (\\u201cordonnance judiciaire\\u201d, \\u201cDecreto del Giudice per le Indagini Preliminari\\u201d, subpoena, \\u201cAuskunftsersuchen\\u201d, \\u201crichterlicher Beschluss/formelles Auskunftsersuchen\\u201d) is required for the disclosure of transactional information pertaining to an account or payments-related data (not including contents of communications) to be considered by Airbnb Ireland.\\n            For content of communications, an appropriate and binding court order (or equivalent local warrant procedure) is required for the disclosure to be considered by Airbnb Ireland.\\n        \\n        The above notwithstanding, we explicitly reserve the right to require the use of diplomatic processes such as an applicable Mutual Legal Assistance Treaty.\\n        Notification\\n        Please note that Airbnb Ireland has a policy of using commercially reasonable efforts to notify users when we receive legal process from a third party requesting their user data. Generally, we will notify the relevant user of your request except where a court order (not a request) expressly requires us to delay or withhold notification, or where notification is otherwise prohibited by applicable law, or where based upon the information supplied by law enforcement we, in our sole discretion, believe that providing notice would be futile or ineffective or would create a risk of injury or great bodily harm to our rights or property or to an individual or group of individuals, including minors.\\n        Back to Top\\n        \\n        \\n        \\n        Form of Requests\\n        Airbnb is unable to process overly broad or vague requests. We will only consider law enforcement requests that are:\\n        \\n            Typed\\n            Duly signed and stamped by the appropriate law enforcement officer who is empowered by local law to represent the law enforcement unit that is making the request\\n            In compliance with local, international, and United States law\\n            Addressed to Airbnb, Inc. or Airbnb Ireland (as appropriate) and sent to Airbnb, Inc. or Airbnb Ireland (as appropriate) directly\\n            Translated into English\\n        \\n        Requests should explicitly mention the following elements:\\n        \\n            All known email addresses, names, and aliases of data subject or all known physical addresses and telephone numbers of the data subject.\\n            Your name, department, street address, telephone number, fax number, and email address. If your specific fax number is not supplied, our answer may be sent to your general department fax. Please note that for law enforcement communications by email, Airbnb will only respond to emails from law enforcement email domains.\\n            Exactly what information you're requesting, why you're requesting it, and how it pertains to your investigation.\\n            The applicable act or law under which the law enforcement agency is requesting the data.\\n        \\n        Back to Top\\n", "question": "How does Airbnb respond to data requests from law enforcement?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\t    We strongly encourage all hosts to install smoke and CO detectors in their listings, but we don't require hosts to show proof that they have these devices in their space right now. If you don't have a smoke or CO detector installed, you should mention this in your listing\\u2019s description.\\n\\t  \\n\\t  \\n\\t    If you're a host and already have these devices installed, update your listing description to let your guests know you have this important amenity installed.\\n\\t  \\n    \\n\\t    Having working smoke and carbon monoxide (CO) detectors in your home can make a big difference. To help you get started, we're giving away one free combination smoke and carbon monoxide detector to the first 25,000 eligible hosts who request one through December 31, 2016. Read more about this offer.\\n\\t \\n    \\n\\tBe sure to check you local regulations, which may require that you have more than one working smoke and carbon monoxide detector installed in your listing\\u2014for example, some cities require one in every room.\\n\\t", "question": "I'm a host. Am I required to have a smoke and CO detector installed?"},
{"answer": "Your safety and comfort are always a priority. If you find that a guest isn't a fit for your space or hosting style, you can decline their reservation request or cancel the reservation.\\n    \\n    Before you've accepted a reservation\\n    \\n    We encourage you to take advantage of the safety features we've built to help give you peace of mind and help you get to know potential guests.\\n    \\n    Declining an individual reservation request won't negatively impact your listing's placement in search results\\u2014however, if you decline many or most reservation requests, your search result placement may be negatively impacted.\\n\\n    After you've accepted a reservation\\n    \\n    If you've already accepted the reservation, you can cancel it. You may be subject to cancellation penalties.\\n    \\n    You won't be eligible for Superhost status if you cancel a confirmed reservation\\u2014unless it\\u2019s under extenuating circumstances.\\n    \\n    Flagging inappropriate messages\\n        \\n        If a message from a guest makes you uncomfortable, let us know by flagging it. To flag a message, open the message thread and click the flag icon  next to the message you want to flag to Airbnb for review.\\n        \\n        \\n\\n        \\n \\n\\nRemember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What should I do if I'm uncomfortable hosting someone?"},
{"answer": "We ask everyone who uses Airbnb for a few pieces of information before they travel on Airbnb. Guests need to have this info completely filled out before they can make a reservation request. This info helps make sure hosts know who to expect, and how to contact the guest.\\n\\nAirbnb\\u2019s requirements for guests include:\\n\\n  Full name\\n  Confirmed email address\\n  Confirmed phone number\\n  Profile photo that shows their face\\n  Introductory message\\n  Agreement to house rules\\n  Payment information\\n\\n\\nHosts won\\u2019t see guest\\u2019s real email addresses, even after they book. Instead, hosts will see a temporary Airbnb email address that forwards their messages to the guest.\\n\\nSome hosts may also ask guests to complete Verified ID before booking their space.", "question": "What are the requirements to book on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\nTo verify your phone number:\\n\\n\\n  Go to Profile on airbnb.com.\\n  Next to Phone Number, click Add a phone number.\\n  Use the drop-down menu to select your country, and we\\u2019ll automatically insert the right country code.\\n  Enter your area code and phone number.\\n  Click Verify via SMS or Verify via Call. We'll send you a 4-digit code via text message (SMS) or an automated phone call.\\n  Enter your code and click Verify\\n\\n\\nIf you don\\u2019t see a confirmation message, try refreshing the page. If the method you chose isn't working, try the other one.\\n\\n\\n\\nAfter verifying your phone number, you can manage text message notifications by going to Account and choosing Notifications on the left. As always, standard message and data rates may apply for any calls or messages sent or received. For questions about these rates, get in touch with your phone provider.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nWhy verify?\\nHaving a verified phone number gives your hosts, guests, and Airbnb a way to contact you about your reservations or your account. Hosts are required to verify their phone numbers before listing their homes, and guests must have a verified phone number before booking a reservation. You also need a verified phone number to complete Verified ID.", "question": "How do I verify my phone number?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\n    We created the Verified ID process to build trust in our community and help give you more information when you're deciding who to host or stay with.\\n      \\n      How Verified ID works\\n        Verified ID connects your Airbnb profile with other information about you. As part of Verified ID, you might be asked to:\\n          \\n          \\n            Take a photo or upload an image of your government-issued ID, such as your driver's license or passport\\n            Depending on where you live, you may have the option of answering a few questions about yourself instead\\n            Connect another online profile to your Airbnb account, such as a Facebook, Google, or LinkedIn account\\n            Upload an Airbnb profile photo and provide a phone number and email address\\n            \\n        Visit airbnb.com/verify to get started at any time.\\n      When you'll need to complete it\\n        Under certain circumstances, you might be required to complete Verified ID. For example, hosts can require that guests complete Verified ID before booking their place.\\n        \\n        If your host requires you to complete Verified ID, you'll be directed to complete the process right after you send your reservation request, and will have 12 hours to complete it. If you need to come back later, go to airbnb.com/verify and pick up where you left off.\\n        \\n        \\n        The Verified ID badge\\n      \\n      When you complete Verified ID, you'll earn a badge on your profile. Many hosts and guests look for this badge when deciding whether to host or stay with someone\\u2014but it's not an endorsement or guarantee of someone's identity.\\n      \\n            Privacy and encryption\\n        We take privacy seriously. The information you provide during this process is encrypted and governed by our Privacy Policy.\\n            \\n        We won't share the government ID or personal details you provide during Verified ID with your host or guest\\u2014they'll only know that you\\u2019ve successfully completed the process. And we\\u2019ll never post to your Facebook, Google, LinkedIn, or other connected accounts without your permission.\\n        \\n        Other ways your ID info is used\\n\\n    Where permitted by applicable law, we may also provide information from your government ID, such as your full name and date of birth, to our service providers to run checks against public records for criminal convictions and sex offender registrations. For now, these checks are limited to users in the United States about whom we have adequate identifying information, such as the user\\u2019s full name and date of birth. While we believe these checks help us deter fraud and misuse of our services, they don\\u2019t guarantee that interactions with people who book through Airbnb will be safe or problem-free. Please carefully review our notice about the limitations of background and registered sex offender checks.\\n            \\n    \\n    \\n", "question": "What is Verified ID?"},
{"answer": "Since we\\u2019re just getting started in Cuba, we want to offer some extra tips and guidelines to make sure your trip goes as smoothly as possible.\\n\\n        Call us if you need us\\n        If you need anything related to your Cuba trip, call us at one of these numbers:\\n          \\n            888-404-6895 (US toll-free)\\n            305-203-0879 (Miami)\\n            437-888-3133 (Toronto)\\n          \\n        Don\\u2019t rely on Internet access \\n        Internet access in Cuba can be sporadic. Consider printing your itinerary, contact numbers and addresses, and any maps you\\u2019ll need before leaving.\\n\\n        Enroll in the STEP program\\n        If you\\u2019re a US citizen, consider enrolling in the Smart Traveler Enrollment Program (STEP). This will help local embassies and US citizen services provide assistance faster in the unlikely event of a problem.\\n\\n        Know the local emergency numbers\\n        If you have an emergency while in Cuba, dial 106 to get in touch with the local police, fire department, or medical services.\\n\\n        Keep track of currency options and exchange rates\\n        Cuba has two currencies: the CUC, or \"convertible peso\", which is valued similar to the US dollar, and the \"national peso,\\u201d or CUP, which is the local currency and is valued much lower. Change money only at banks or at the airport, and make sure you know which currency you\\u2019re exchanging to avoid any misunderstandings.\\n\\n        Help your host register your visit\\n        Bed and breakfasts in Cuba are legally required to record every tourist's passport details at check in. Your host won\\u2019t need to hold your passport, they\\u2019ll only need to copy down a few details. Then they'll need to bring those details to their local immigration office.\\n\\n        Stay in touch with your host\\n        We're new to Cuba, but your host isn't\\u2014don't be afraid to ask questions, get directions, or share expectations. Also, be sure to check with your host before bringing visitors to your listing. Many hosts don't accept visitors and, if they do, will need to take down your visitors' passport details as well.", "question": "What are some helpful tips for traveling to Cuba?"},
{"answer": "To ensure a listing has what you\\u2019ll need for kids, you can always message the host directly with questions before you book.\\n        Safe Kids Worldwide, a global organization dedicated to preventing child injuries, provides an array of resources on child safety on its website. \\n        This includes a series of simple tips on how to make a home safer for children. Below is a full list of the various home risks Safe Kids Worldwide identifies:\\n        \\n            Batteries\\n            Burns and Scalds\\n            Carbon Monoxide\\n            Choking and Strangulation\\n            Falls\\n            Fire\\n            Guns\\n            Liquid Laundry Packets\\n            Medication\\n            Poison\\n            Sleep Safety and Suffocation\\n            Toy Safety\\n            TV and Furniture Tip-Overs\\n            Water and Drowning\\n        \\n        The safety of our hosts, guests, and any accompanying children is our highest priority. Whether you\\u2019re a seasoned traveler or a first time guest, our safety tips will help you along the way.", "question": "I\\u2019m traveling with children. What are some safety tips I should consider?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb will never ask you to pay off-site or through email. If someone messages you on Airbnb and asks you to contact them off-site to arrange payment details, don't respond, report it to us instead.\\n  \\n  Report requests for off-site payment\\n  If a host on the Airbnb site asks you to pay off-site, report it to us by flagging the message\\u2014just look for the flag icon  in your message thread.\\n\\n  If you receive a personal email from anyone (including an automated@airbnb.com or any other username@airbnb.com email address) asking you to pay or accept payment off-site, let us know immediately.\\n  \\n  You won't receive a paper or PDF invoice from a host or from Airbnb asking you for payment. Any of the following key words and similar terms should be immediately flagged or avoided: Western Union, MoneyGram, cashier's check, money order, Liberty Reserve.\\n  \\n  Types of scams\\n\\n\\tNever share your email address before a booking is accepted or transfer funds outside the Airbnb system, and always carefully examine emails claiming to be from Airbnb. Examples of common scams include:\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tAdvance Fee Scam: A type of scam in which an individual offers money or another reward in exchange for you transferring money through various payment services outside of Airbnb.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tPhishing Scam: A type of scam in which someone will send an email or link that is made to look like it's from Airbnb or another trusted site. These messages are designed to trick you into providing confidential information\\u2014such as passwords or other email addresses\\u2014and may contain malware, which is malicious software that gains access to your computer to gather your personal information, including passwords.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tTravel Scam: A type of scam in which someone will encourage you to secure your \"too good to be true\" listing by sending payment via wire transfer or with an advanced deposit in order to collect the money without providing the advertised accommodation.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tOverpayment Scam: A type of scam in which someone will offer more than what your listing may be worth, and ask you to repay them in cash.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nWhy should I pay and communicate through Airbnb directly?\\nHow can I keep my account secure?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What should I do if someone asks me to pay outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "We don't share your personal email address even after you have a confirmed reservation. Instead, we create a unique, temporary Airbnb address for you, and share that with your host or guest. Keeping your real personal email address hidden helps protect your privacy, and prevent unwanted communication from people who may abuse our system.\\n\\nAny emails sent to your temporary Airbnb address are forwarded to your personal email address. This lets you use your email provider to send or reply to messages, attach files (up to 15 MB), and include links.\\n\\nA host's anonymized email address might look like:\\n\\n\\tPersonal email address: john.lastname@exampleemail.com\\n\\tTemporary Airbnb address: john-abc123xyz@host.airbnb.com\\n\\nA guest's anonymized email address might look like:\\n\\n\\tPersonal email address: jane.lastname@exampleemail.com\\n\\tTemporary Airbnb address: jane-def456@guest.airbnb.com\\n\\n\\nWe recommend communicating using the Airbnb messaging system, but we recognize that sometimes you'll need to attach photos, directions, or other information in an email. These addresses let you send emails like your normally would\\u2014with an extra layer of security.", "question": "How will my email address look to other people?"},
{"answer": "Occasionally, people create fake emails or websites designed to look like Airbnb. These sites can be used to try steal personal information, like your password or bank account info. This is often called phishing or spoofing.\\n\\n        If you receive an email or are directed to a website that looks like Airbnb but asks for confidential information, be cautious. When in doubt, always start at the Airbnb home page. Type https://www.airbnb.com in your browser and go from there.\\n        Check the email address\\n        You can tell if an email is really from Airbnb by looking at what comes after the @ symbol. All official Airbnb emails will come from an address that ends in:\\n        \\n            @airbnb.com\\n            \\n            @airbnbmail.com\\n            \\n            @e.airbnb.com\\n            \\n            @host.airbnb.com\\n            \\n            @guest.airbnb.com\\n            \\n            @airbnb.zendesk.com\\n            \\n            @airbnbaction.com\\n            \\n            @express.medallia.com (learn more about Medallia)\\n            \\n        \\n        It's possible for fraudsters to \"spoof\" an email address, so these tips aren't failsafe. If you receive an email that looks like it's from Airbnb, but wasn't sent from one of these addresses, it's very likely fake. Don't click any of its links and delete the email.\\n        Learn to identify fraudulent emails\\n        Fraudulent emails often include the Airbnb logo and a fake Airbnb address in the \"From\" line.\\n        Fraudulent emails might also contain text from real Airbnb emails, such as a reservation confirmation message, payout confirmation, reservation reminder, or a request to update your profile. By making an email seem real, fraudsters hope to trick you into providing personal information that we would never ask for. Here are some signs to help you tell the difference:\\n        \\n            \\n                \\n                    Fake Email\\n                    Real Airbnb Email\\n                \\n            \\n            \\n                \\n                    \\n                        \\n                            They\\u2019re sent from fraudulent email addresses. Examples include john@bnb.com or automated@reservation-airbnb.com.\\n                        \\n                    \\n                    \\n                        \\n                            They're sent from an address that ends in @airbnb.com, @airbnbmail.com, @e.airbnb.com, @host.airbnb.com, @guest.airbnb.com, @airbnb.zendesk.com, @airbnbaction.com, or @express.medallia.com. If it's not sent from one of these addresses, it\\u2019s not from Airbnb.\\n                        \\n                    \\n                \\n                \\n                    \\n                        \\n                            They often contain links to fake Airbnb web pages that try to steal your information. Don\\u2019t click links in any email you\\u2019re not sure about.\\n                        \\n                    \\n                    \\n                        \\n                            They begin with https://www.airbnb.com (or a country-specific URL like https://es.airbnb.com or https://it.airbnb.com). If you click a link that takes you to a page that looks like Airbnb but doesn\\u2019t start with this address, it\\u2019s a fraudulent page and you should close it.\\n                        \\n                    \\n                \\n                \\n                    \\n                        \\n                            They often have an urgent tone and threaten account suspension, loss of a reservation or booking, or a delayed payout if you don't click a link or reply with certain information immediately.\\n                        \\n                    \\n                    \\n                        \\n                            If it\\u2019s truly important, you\\u2019ll usually find more information in your Airbnb dashboard. If you have any doubt about an email\\u2019s authenticity, log in to your account at www.airbnb.com and go from there. \\n                        \\n                    \\n                \\n            \\n        \\n      Report fake emails to Airbnb\\n      If you think you've received a fake email, forward it to report.phishing@airbnb.com. If possible, forward or send the email as an attachment\\u2014this gives us important information that will help us investigate.\\n      This inbox is strictly for reporting suspicious emails or websites, and isn't monitored for urgent issues. If you made a payment outside of Airbnb or are concerned about the security of your account, contact us instead.", "question": "How do I know if an email is really from Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Here are some tips to help you travel with confidence.\\n        Read carefully\\n            Look at the profiles and reviews of potential hosts before you book, and check for verified phone numbers, connected social networks, and references. If you'd like to see more, you can always ask them to complete profile verifications before booking with them, or look for hosts who already have a strong reputation on Airbnb.\\n\\n            It's also a good idea to read everything the host has posted about their listing in the description, the amenities, and the house rules so there won\\u2019t be any surprises. Make sure you understand the host's cancellation policy before submitting a reservation request, too.\\n        Pay and communicate on Airbnb\\n            \\n            Paying or communicating outside Airbnb makes it harder for us to protect your information and puts you at greater risk of fraud and other security issues. That's why we prohibit paying for a reservation outside our website in our Terms of Service and strongly encourage you to communicate using our messaging system.\\n        Use our messaging system before a booking to confirm details about specific amenities, ask whether other people share the same space, discuss house rules, and talk about the neighborhood. After booking, use it to discuss check-in details.\\n        Set clear expectations\\n            After learning more about your host\\u2019s Airbnb history, start a conversation with them about your plans and what you can expect. Your host will likely know all the great (and not so great) spots. Trust your intuition: if you don\\u2019t feel right about a reservation, don\\u2019t book it! If a message makes you feel uncomfortable or you need help during your reservation, let us know.\\n        Prepare for the unexpected\\n        Research the neighborhood where you\\u2019ll be staying, familiarize yourself with major roads and landmarks, and have a plan for where you\\u2019d go in an emergency. If you\\u2019re covering long distances in your travels, make sure to tell your friends and family where you\\u2019ll be.\\n            For any trip, think about signing up for traveler's insurance. Airbnb doesn't offer traveler\\u2019s insurance for guests, but traveler's insurance is a relatively affordable option that can protect you in case of an injury or emergency on a trip. Some policies even cover lost baggage and travel delays. Check with your local insurance provider for details on your options.\\n            \\n           Before booking international travel or traveling internationally, also be sure toconsult the relevant agencies in your government (for example the State Department for US citizens) for any travel warnings or travel advisories that may apply to countries or regions included in your travel plans.\\n\\n\\n        Be a considerate guest\\n            Whether you're still looking for the perfect listing or are already on your way, being a considerate guest matters.\\n          \\n            \\n      \\n        \\n        Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n        \\n      \\n", "question": "I\\u2019m a guest. What are some safety tips I can follow?"},
{"answer": "We remove text from messages when our system detects words or numbers that might include contact information. Communicating or paying outside Airbnb can put you at risk, so we do this to help protect you from potential online fraud.\\n  \\n    We ask that you communicate only through the Airbnb message thread until you have a confirmed Airbnb reservation. After a reservation is accepted, the phone number, listing address, and an anonymized version of your email address are automatically shared.\\n    \\n  By communicating and booking directly through Airbnb, you\\u2019ll have access to our secure payments platform, 24/7 customer support, the Host Guarantee, and the Host Protection Insurance program.", "question": "Why was text removed from my Airbnb message thread?"},
{"answer": "\\n  Related article: How does Occupancy Tax Collection and Remittance by Airbnb work?\\n\\n\\n\\tCurrently, Airbnb is collecting and remitting taxes on behalf of the host in the following locations:\\n\\nFrance\\n\\nChamonix- Mont-Blanc\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Chamonix-Mont-Blanc will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nTourist Tax: 0.75\\u20ac per person per night for the category \"meubl\\xe9s touristiques non class\\xe9s\".  Exemptions may apply to some guests. For detailed information, visit your local city hall's website. If a guest believes they are subject to an exemption, they may reach out to the Municipality.\\n\\n\\nParis\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Paris will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nTourist Tax: 0.83 \\u20ac per person per night for the category \"meubl\\xe9s touristiques non class\\xe9s\". This amount includes the city-imposed tourist tax and the administrative district tax.\\n\\nExemptions may apply to some guests. If guests believe they are subject to an exemption, they may reach out to the Municipality. You can find more information here, here and here.\\n\\n\\nOther cities\\n\\nAs of August 1, 2016, guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Ajaccio, Annecy, Antibes, Avignon, Biarritz, Bordeaux, Cannes, La Rochelle, Lille, Lyon, Marseille, Montpellier, Nantes, Nice, Saint-Malo, Strasbourg, or Toulouse will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nTourist Tax: 0.83 \\u20ac per person per night for the category \"meubl\\xe9s touristiques non class\\xe9s\". This amount includes the city-imposed tourist tax and the administrative district tax.\\n\\nExemptions may apply to some guests. If guests believe they are subject to an exemption, they may reach out to the Municipality. You can find more information here, here and here.\\n\\n\\n\\nIndia\\n\\nCountry of India\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the Country of India will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nIndia Service Tax: 14.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee, less a 40% abatement. Airbnb is required, as an aggregator, to collect and remit service tax on behalf of Airbnb hosts.For detailed information, visit India\\u2019s government website.\\n\\n\\nNetherlands\\n\\n\\tAmsterdam\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the City of Amsterdam, NL will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tAmsterdam Tourist Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee. For detailed information, visit Amsterdam\\u2019s government website.\\n\\n\\nPortugal\\n\\nLisbon\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Lisbon will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n  Tourist Tax: 1.00 \\u20ac per person per night, up to a maximum of 7.00 \\u20ac per person. For detailed information, visit the City of Lisbon website.\\n  \\n  \\nUnited States\\n\\nAlabama\\nState of Alabama\\n Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Alabama will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nAlabama State Lodging Tax: 4-5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 179 nights and shorter.\\nFor detailed information, visit Sales and Use Tax at the Alabama Department of Revenue website.\\n\\nCounty Lodging and Rental Tax collected by the State: 1-6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 179 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Local Sales, Use, Lodgings &amp; Rental Tax Rates at the Alabama Department of Revenue website.\\n\\nMunicipality Local Lodging Tax collected by the State: 2-12% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 179 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Local Sales, Use, Lodgings &amp; Rental Tax Rates at the Alabama Department of Revenue website.\\n\\n\\nHosts are responsible for collecting any city and county taxes that are not collected by the state.\\n\\nArizona\\nPhoenix\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Phoenix, AZ will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nPhoenix Hotel/Motel Tax: 3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter.\\n\\nPhoenix Transaction Privilege (Sales) Tax: 2.3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for all reservations. For detailed information, visit Phoenix.gov.\\n\\n\\nCalifornia\\n\\n   Humboldt County\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in unincorporated Humboldt County, CA (does not include the incorporated cities of Arcata, Blue Lake, Eureka, Ferndale, Fortuna, Rio Dell and Trinidad) will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation\\n\\n\\nHumboldt County Transient Occupancy Tax: 10% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Humboldt County Tax Collector  website.\\n\\n\\n   Santa Cruz County\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in unincorporated Santa Cruz County, CA (does not include the incorporated cities of Capitola, Santa Cruz, Scotts Valley or Watsonville) will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nTransient Occupancy Tax: 11% of the listing price including any cleaning fees for 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, please visit the Santa Cruz County Treasurer website.\\n\\n\\nTuolumne County\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Tuolumne County, CA (does not include the incorporated city of Sonora) will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n  \\nTransient Occupancy Tax: 10% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Tuolumne County Transient Occupancy Tax site.\\n\\n\\tMalibu\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Malibu, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nMalibu Transient Occupancy Tax: 12% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit MalibuCity.org.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\nOakland\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Oakland, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n  \\nOakland Transient Occupancy Tax: 14% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Oakland's FAQ page.\\n\\n\\nPalo Alto\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Palo Alto, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nPalo Alto Transient Occupancy Tax: 14% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter.  For detailed information, visit CityofPaloAlto.org.\\n\\n\\nSan Diego\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in San Diego, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nSan Diego Transient Occupancy Tax: 10.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter.\\n\\t\\nSan Diego Tourism Marketing District Assessment: 0.55% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit SanDiego.gov.\\n\\n\\n\\tSan Francisco\\n\\n\\tGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in San Francisco, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tSan Francisco Transient Occupancy Tax: 14% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. 14% is the tax rate imposed by the City and County of San Francisco (the tax jurisdictions are one and the same). For detailed information, visit SFtreasurer.org.\\n\\n\\t  \\n\\tSan Jose\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in San Jose, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nSan Jose Transient Occupancy Tax: 10% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit SanJoseCa.gov.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\tSanta Clara\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Santa Clara, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t  Santa Clara Transient Occupancy Tax: 9.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit SantaClara.gov.\\n\\t\\n\\n  Santa Monica\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Santa Monica, CA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nSanta Monica Transient Occupancy Tax: 14% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Santa Monica's website.\\n\\n\\nConnecticut\\n\\tState of Connecticut\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Connecticut will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nConnecticut State Room Occupancy Tax: 15% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for the first 30 nights of any reservation. For detailed information, visit the Connecticut Department of Revenue website.\\n\\t\\n\\nDistrict of Columbia\\n\\tDistrict of Columbia\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the District of Columbia will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nDC Sales Tax on Hotels (transient accommodations): 14.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 90 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit DC.gov.\\n\\t\\n\\nFlorida\\nState of Florida\\n\\n  Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Florida will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n  \\nFlorida Transient Rental Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Florida Dept. of Revenue website.\\n\\nFlorida Discretionary Sales Surtax: 0.5%-1.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. The State imposes both a statewide 6% tax and a local 0.5-1.5% tax, which varies by county. For detailed information, visit the Florida Dept. of Revenue website.\\n\\nCounty Tourist Development Taxes collected by the State: 2-5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter.  The state administers 22 county taxes, including: Bradford, Citrus, Columbia, Desoto, Dixie, Flagler, Franklin, Gadsden, Gilchrist, Glades, Hamilton, Hendry, Holmes, Jackson, Jefferson, Levy, Madison, Okeechobee, Pasco, Sumter, Wakulla, and Washington.\\n\\nBrevard County Tourist Development Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Brevard Tax Collector website. \\n\\nHernando County Tourist Development Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Hernando County Comptroller site.\\n\\nLee County Tourist Development Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Lee Clerk website. \\n\\nOrange County Tourist Development Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Orange County Comptroller website.\\n\\nPinellas County Tourist Development Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Pinellas County Tax Collector website.\\n\\nPutnam County Tourist Development Tax: 4% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Putnam County Tax Collector website.\\n\\nTaylor County Tourism Development Tax: 3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 182 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Taylor County Tax Collector website.\\n\\n\\nIllinois\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Illinois, Cook County, and Chicago will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nIllinois Hotel Operators Occupation Tax: 5.98-6.17% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit tax.Illinois.gov.\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Cook County, IL will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n \\nCook County Hotel Accommodations Tax: 1% of the listing price including any cleaning fee. For detailed information, visit the  Cook County Department of Revenue website.\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Chicago, IL will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nChicago Hotel Accommodation Tax: 4.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit CityofChicago.org.\\n\\n  Other Taxes administered by the State of Illinois: 5.73% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit tax.Illinois.gov.\\n\\n\\n\\nLouisiana\\n\\tState of Louisiana\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Louisiana will pay the following taxes administered by the State as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nLouisiana Sales and Use Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for all reservations. For detailed information, visit the Louisiana Department of Revenue website.\\n\\n\\nMaryland\\n\\tMontgomery County\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Montgomery County, MD will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nMontgomery County Room Rental and Transient Tax: 7% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Room Rental-Transient Tax Information page.\\n\\n\\nNevada\\n\\tWashoe County, Sparks and Reno\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Washoe County, the City of Sparks or the City of Reno, NV will pay the following tax as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nCity or County Transient Lodging Tax: of either 13.5% or 13% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for 27 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the \\n RSCVA Finance and Accounting Department website.\\n\\n\\nNew Jersey\\n\\tJersey City\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Jersey City, NJ will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\n Hotel and Motel Use and Occupancy Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 89 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Article V of Jersey City's Code of Ordinances at municode.com.\\n\\t\\n\\nNew York\\n\\tTompkins County\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Tompkins County, NY will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\tTompkins County Hotel Room Occupancy Tax: 3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit Tompkins County's website.\\n\\t\\n\\nNorth Carolina\\n\\tState of North Carolina\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of North Carolina will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nNorth Carolina Sales Tax: 6.75-7.5% of the listing price including any cleaning and guest fees for reservations less than 90 nights. The State imposes both a statewide 4.75% tax and a local 2-2.75% tax, which varies by county. For detailed information, visit North Carolina's website.\\n\\nCity and/or County Occupancy Tax: All locally imposed occupancy taxes will be collected on reservations in North Carolina. The tax varies by city and county. It is typically 1-8% of the listing price including any cleaning and guest fees for reservations less than 90 nights.\\n\\n\\nOhio\\nCleveland, OH USA\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Cleveland, OH will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nCleveland Transient Occupancy Tax: 3% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the City of Cleveland website.\\n\\nCuyahoga County, OH USA\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Cuyahoga County, OH will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nCounty Bed Tax: 5.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fees for 29 nights and shorter. For detailed information, please visit Cuyahoga County's FAQ page.\\n\\n\\nOregon\\nState of Oregon\\n\\n\\tGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Oregon, Multnomah County and/or the City of Portland will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tOregon Transient Lodging Tax: 1.8% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. 1.8% is the State imposed tax rate only. For detailed information, visit Oregon.gov.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tMultnomah County Transient Lodging Tax: 11.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. 11.5% is the maximum Transient Lodging Tax for listings in Multnomah County (excluding the State level tax). For example, for Portland listings that are also located in Multnomah County, the Portland Transient Lodging Tax is 6% and the Multnomah County Transient Lodging Tax is 5.5%. For detailed information, visit  PortlandOregon.gov.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tPortland Transient Lodging Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tWashington County Transient Room Tax: Guests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Washington County, OR will pay 9% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the Washington County Finance Department website.\\n\\n\\n\\nPennsylvania\\nState of Pennsylvania\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Pennsylvania will pay the following taxes administered by the State as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nPennsylvania Hotel Occupancy Tax: 6% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter that are in the State of Pennsylvania. For detailed information, visit the Pennsylvania Department of Revenue website.\\n\\t\\nLocal Sales Tax Collected by the State: 1% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter. The State administers 2 Local Sales Taxes: Allegheny County and Philadelphia County. For detailed information, visit the Pennsylvania Department of Revenue website.\\n\\nAllegheny County\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Allegheny County will pay the following tax as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\n\\t\\nAllegheny County Hotel Room Rental Tax: 7% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 29 nights and shorter.  For detailed information visit the Allegheny County Treasurer website.\\n\\nPhiladelphia\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Philadelphia, PA will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\t\\nPhiladelphia Hotel Room Rental Tax: 8.5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. 8.5% is the tax rate imposed by the City and County of Philadelphia (the tax jurisdictions are one and the same). For detailed information, visit Phila.gov.\\n\\n\\nRhode Island\\nState of Rhode Island\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in Rhode Island will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\n  Rhode Island Sales Tax: 7% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit  RI.gov.\\n\\n  Rhode Island Local Hotel Tax: 1% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter.\\n\\n  Rhode Island Statewide Hotel Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee for reservations 30 nights and shorter on rentals of private rooms or shared rooms only.  Rentals of an entire home or apartment are excluded from this tax.\\n\\n\\nSouth Carolina\\n  State of South Carolina\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of South Carolina will pay the following taxes administered by the State as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nSouth Carolina State Sales and Use Tax: 5% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 89 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the South Carolina Department of Revenue website.\\n\\nSouth Carolina State Accommodations Tax: 2% of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 89 nights and shorter. For detailed information, visit the South Carolina Department of Revenue website.\\n\\nLocal Taxes collected by the State: 0.5-8%, per Local Tax type, of the listing price including any cleaning fee and guest fee for reservations 89 nights and shorter.  One or more of the following Local Taxes may apply:  Capital Project Tax, Catawba Tribal Tax, School District Tax, Education Capital Improvement Tax, Transportation Tax, Local Option Tax, Tourism Development Tax.  Note that Airbnb is only collecting the Local Taxes that are administered or collected by the State at this time.  For detailed information, visit the South Carolina Department of Revenue website and the Sales and Use Tax Manual.\\n\\n\\nWashington\\n\\tState of Washington\\n\\nGuests who book Airbnb listings that are located in the State of Washington will pay the following taxes as part of their reservation:\\n\\n\\nWashington Combined Sales Tax: 7.0-9.6% of the listing price including any cleaning fees for reservations 29 nights and shorter.  Washington's combined sales tax is a combination of the state retail sales tax of 6.5% and the local retail sales tax, which varies by county and city. For detailed information, visit WA.gov.\\n\\nSpecial Hotel/Motel Tax, Convention and Trade Center Tax, Regional Transit Authority Tax, and Tourism Promotion Area Charges: All locally imposed taxes on transient lodging will be collected on reservations in Washington. The Special Hotel/Motel Tax is typically 1-5% of the listing price including any cleaning fees for reservations 29 nights and shorter. Other local taxes vary and are only applicable in certain cities and counties.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nHosts located in these areas are responsible for assessing all other tax obligations, including state and city jurisdictions. Hosts with listings in these areas should also review their agreement with Airbnb under the Terms of Service and familiarize themselves with the Occupancy Tax provisions which allow us to collect and remit taxes on their behalf and explains how the process works. Under those provisions, hosts instruct and authorize Airbnb to collect and remit Occupancy Taxes on their behalf in jurisdictions where Airbnb decides to facilitate such collection. If a hosts believes applicable laws exempt the host from collecting a tax that Airbnb collects and remits on the host's behalf, the host has agreed that, by accepting the reservation, the host is waiving that exemption. If a host does not want to waive an exemption the host believes exists, the host should not accept the reservation.", "question": "In what areas is Occupancy Tax Collection and Remittance by Airbnb available?"},
{"answer": "\\nIn areas that Airbnb has made agreements with governments to collect and remit local taxes on behalf of hosts, Airbnb calculates applicable local taxes and collects those taxes from guests at the time of booking. Airbnb then takes care of remitting collected taxes to the applicable tax authority on the hosts' behalf. \\n\\n\\nThis doesn\\u2019t change which taxes are due, but automating the process makes tax collection easier for all parties involved.\\n\\n\\nIf occupancy tax is being collected for your area, it appears as a line item on your listing\\u2019s public page. You can also confirm what taxes are being collected and remitted by looking for occupancy tax details in Manage Listing &gt; Location, underneath the Address section.\\n\\n\\nTaxes collected on reservations do not affect the amount of host payouts. Hosts continue to get their payout of accommodation fees minus Airbnb service fees.\\n\\n\\nCollected Occupancy Taxes are listed in the Gross Earnings section of hosts\\u2019 transaction history, and appear as a line item on all guest receipts.\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Content\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     In what areas is Occupancy Tax Collection and Remittance by Airbnb available?\\n     Where do I find information about my payouts?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How does Occupancy Tax Collection and Remittance by Airbnb work?"},
{"answer": "We strive to provide our hosts and guests with the right tools to make informed decisions regarding who they interact with on the site and in the real world.\\n\\n  Airbnb offers a number of features that help build trust and cultivate a transparent community marketplace, including our secure messaging system, reviews, the Host Guarantee, and Verified ID or other identity checks.\\n\\n  At Airbnb, we want to build the world's most trusted  community. To help ensure our member's safety, we dedicate a knowledgeable and experienced team to monitor any suspicious activity in our marketplace.\\n\\n  You can help our efforts by reporting suspicious or inappropriate activity. Look for the flag icon  on:\\n\\n\\tProfiles: You'll see a flag at the top of each profile\\n\\tListings: You'll see a flag in the right sidebar of any listing\\n\\tMessages: You'll see a flag in the top right corner of messages\\n\\t\\n\\nRead more about tools used to help verify user information, and review our safety tips for hosts and guests.\\t\\n\\t\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nWhat are profile verifications?\\nWhat is Verified ID?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How does Airbnb help build trust between hosts and guests?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tWe consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us.\\n\\n\\tAirbnb takes trust seriously\\n\\n\\tWe're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives.\\n\\n\\tAirbnb encourages responsibility\\n\\n\\tWe encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting.\\n\\n\\tNeighbor resources\\n\\n\\tIf your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "\\nWhat is Occupancy Tax?\\n\\nOccupancy tax is a tax on the rental of rooms that your state or locality may require. In many places this is known as an occupancy tax, but may also be known as a lodging tax, a room tax, a sales tax, a tourist tax, or a hotel tax.\\n\\nOccupancy tax rates and rules vary by city, county, state, and country. They\\u2019re generally owed on the accommodations price plus any fees for other items, like cleanings or extra guests. In some places, occupancy tax is required on a per person, per night basis. There are typically long-term stay exceptions that exempt reservations over a certain number of nights. Occupancy tax is generally paid by the guest, but the obligation to remit the taxes to the government usually falls on the host. We expect all hosts to familiarize themselves with and follow their local laws and regulations.\\n\\nWhat are my options to collect and pay occupancy tax?\\n\\nAs an Airbnb host, if you determine that you need to collect occupancy tax, you can collect Occupancy Taxes by either incorporating it into your nightly price, adding it within a Special Offer, or asking your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect Occupancy Taxes in person, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we\\u2019re unable to assist with collection.\\n\\nIn some locations, like Amsterdam, Portland and San Francisco, Airbnb automatically collects occupancy tax from guests and sends it to the tax authority on hosts\\u2019 behalf. For these areas, Occupancy Tax amounts will appear as a line item on your listing\\u2019s public page, and you should not collect taxes separately for those jurisdictions. Learn more. To confirm if you listing is included in a collection area:\\n\\n\\nGo to Your Listings\\n\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you'd like to view\\n\\nSelect Location on the left\\n\\nIf occupancy taxes are being collected and remitted on your behalf, they'll be listed at the bottom of the page.\\n\\nWhen will Airbnb start collecting occupancy tax in my area?\\n\\nWe\\u2019ll let you know if an occupancy tax related feature becomes available for your listing.\\n\\nWe want to help hosts follow the laws relevant to them, and we understand that many of these rules are complex and difficult to follow. We're continuing to work with governments across the world to explore ways to help facilitate occupancy tax collection in as many locations as possible.", "question": "What is occupancy tax? Do I need to collect or pay it?"},
{"answer": "Paying and communicating through Airbnb helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program and other safeguards. It also makes it easy to find and reference important reservation details like a listing's address, your itinerary, check-in details, and other useful information. We can\\u2019t provide these benefits if your reservation isn\\u2019t booked and paid for directly through Airbnb.\\n\\n      Paying or communicating outside of Airbnb also makes it harder for us to protect your information and puts you at greater risk of fraud and other security issues, such as phishing.\\n\\n    Flag suspicious messages\\n\\n      Never pay for your reservation outside of Airbnb. If someone asks you to pay for a reservation outside our on-site payment system\\u2014or you think someone might be sending you links to a fake Airbnb site\\u2014let us know and click the flag icon  in your message thread with that person.", "question": "Why should I pay and communicate through Airbnb directly?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tWe'll send you an email or text (SMS) alert whenever certain changes are made to your account (ex: updates to your password, email address, payout method). When you receive one of these alerts, make sure it was you who made the change.\\n\\n\\tIf you didn't make the change, reset your password and let our team know here.", "question": "My account details changed, but I didn\\u2019t update them. What should I do?"},
{"answer": "To see a list of recent logins to your Airbnb account:\\n    \\n      Go to Account on airbnb.com\\n      Select Security on the left\\n      Scroll down and look for Login History section\\n    \\n    Under Login History, you\\u2019ll find a list of logins to your Airbnb account, including information on the type of browser used to access your account, when your account was accessed, and where we believe it was accessed from. You can hover over the  icon in the Recent Activity column to get more information, such as the precise time or IP address of the device used to access your account.\\n    Trusted browsers are included in your login history.", "question": "Can I see a list of recent logins to my Airbnb account?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIf you are a photographer, translator, or other service provider paid through your Airbnb account, please be sure to complete your taxpayer information so that we can process your payouts.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tUS Persons may fill out a Form W-9. In January, if you've submitted a Form W-9 and earned $600 or more during the previous year, we'll provide you with a Form 1099-MISC showing your earnings under \"Box 7 - Nonemployee compensation.\" Corporate service providers will not receive a tax form.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tNon-US persons may submit a Form W-8 to certify that their earnings are not subject to US tax.\\n\\n\\n\\tIf you're unsure of what form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status.\\n\\n\\n\\tClick here for more information specific to US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for photographers and other service providers?"},
{"answer": "Using a strong password for your Airbnb account makes it harder for people to gain access your account without your permission. The password you choose should be easy for you to remember, but hard for someone else to figure out. \\n\\n        Create a unique password\\n        Make sure your Airbnb password is different than the passwords you use for other websites, like your email or bank account. That way, if someone figures out your Airbnb password, they won\\u2019t be able to use it to access your other accounts (or vice versa).\\n        Change your password often \\n        If someone knows your password, they might be accessing your Airbnb account without you knowing. Changing your password often helps prevent this kind of unauthorized access.\\n        Use at least 8 characters and avoid common phrases\\n        Make sure your password is at least 8 characters long, and try to use a mix of special characters (#, $, &amp;, !, etc.). You should also avoid using common words or phrases in your password, and never include personal information.\\n        \\n        \\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I reset my password?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How can I make my password strong?"},
{"answer": "Review the tips below to learn more about how you can help keep your account and information secure.\\n    \\nIf you make a change to sensitive account information, we may send you an account alert or ask you to confirm the change by entering a security code sent to your verified phone number.\\n\\nPassword strength\\n\\nCreate a password that's at least 8 characters, and contains a unique combination of letters, numbers, and symbols. Don't use the password you create for your Airbnb account for other accounts (ex: your email account). Learn how to update your password.\\n\\nOnline security\\nA few general guidelines to help you stay safe online:\\n\\n\\tAlways log in at https://www.airbnb.com: Check any page's URL before you enter your login info\\u2014when in doubt, you can always type https://www.airbnb.com directly into your browser.\\n\\tTurn browser security alerts on: Many newer browsers have built-in security protection that might be able to warn you if you're about to visit an unsecure website.\\n\\tInstall a pop-up blocker and antivirus software: Install a pop-up blocker or antivirus software from a trustworthy source. Remember to run scans for viruses and malware frequently, and keep your antivirus software up-to-date.\\n\\tCheck the sender: Don't click any links or download any attachments unless you know and trust the source.\\n\\n\\n\\nOff-site payments and messages\\nAirbnb will never ask you to pay elsewhere\\u2014and we ask that you keep all payment and communication on the Airbnb platform. Don't share your email address before a booking is accepted or transfer funds outside the Airbnb system, and always carefully examine emails claiming to be from Airbnb.\\n\\nIf you encounter a suspicious profile, listing, or message thread, flag it for review. If someone emails you asking you to pay or accept payment off-site, let us know right away.\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\n  What should I do if someone asks me to pay outside of the Airbnb website?\\nWhy should I pay and communicate through Airbnb directly?\\n\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How can I keep my account secure?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tThere are a few instances where an Airbnb guest may need to pay tax.\\n\\n\\n\\tSome hosts are required by their local regulations to charge a tax. We recommend they include the tax in the price of the reservation, but some may require the tax to be paid directly upon check-in. We ask that hosts explain any taxes they may be required to collect in their listing description and their communication with guests prior to booking.\\n\\n\\tIn some locations, Airbnb has made agreements with government officials to collect and remit certain local taxes on behalf of hosts. The taxes vary and, depending on the local law, may include calculations based on a flat rate or percentage rate, the number of guests, number of nights, or property type booked. When you book a listing in one of these locations, the local taxes collected will be displayed automatically when you pay and appear on your receipt once your reservation is confirmed.\\n\\n\\n\\tAdditionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or a VAT equivalent (i.e. Japanese Consumption Tax) on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan. Learn more about Value Added Tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for guests?"},
{"answer": "Local Tax\\n\\nIf you determine that you need to collect tax, you can usually either incorporate it into your nightly price, add it within a Special Offer, or ask your guests to pay it in person. In each case, it's important that guests are informed of the exact tax amount prior to booking. If you choose to collect tax outside of your listing's rates, please note that it should be collected only upon arrival and that we are unable to assist with collection.\\n\\nIn some locations, Airbnb hosts may have a  collect and remit feature available to handle occupancy tax. Hosts should not collect occupancy taxes separately for those jurisdictions.\\n\\n Learn more about Local Tax.\\n\\n\\tValue Added Tax\\n\\n If your country of residence is part of the European Union, you may need to assess Value Added Tax (VAT) on the services you provide. We encourage you to consult a tax advisor in your area for more insight or if you need assistance assessing VAT on the services you provide.\\n\\n Additionally, Airbnb is required to collect VAT or JCT on its service fees in countries that tax Electronically Supplied Services. Currently, that includes all countries in the EU, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan.\\n\\n  Learn more about Value Added Tax.\\n\\nUS Income Taxes\\n\\n As a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. To assist with US tax compliance, we may collect your taxpayer information. Even if you're not a US taxpayer, we may still require certain information from you.\\n \\n  To add new taxpayer information, go to your  Payout Preferences and complete the appropriate form.\\n\\n\\nUS persons (including domestic corporations) may fill out a Form W-9. At the end of January, we will provide hosts who've earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations with a Form 1099-K showing their reportable earnings from the previous year.\\n\\nNon-US persons who have a US Taxpayer Identification Number (either a Social Security Number or Employer Identification Number) may fill out a Form W-8ECI. We'll provide hosts who submit a W-8ECI with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.\\n\\nNon-US persons who do not have a US Taxpayer Identification Number may fill out a Form W-8BEN to certify their foreign status. Airbnb is required to withhold 30% on all payouts from US listings hosted by non-US persons unless valid tax treaty benefits have been claimed. We'll provide hosts who have submitted a W-8BEN with a Form 1042-S showing any US sourced earnings from the previous year.\\n\\n\\nYou can learn more about how the IRS classifies taxpayers for US tax purposes at irs.gov. If you're unsure of which form to submit, we encourage you to consult a tax professional who can clarify your tax status. If you've received a request to submit your taxpayer information and haven't provided it yet, we may be required to withhold a percentage of your earnings.\\n\\n  We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area.\\n\\n\\tLearn more about US Federal tax.", "question": "How do taxes work for hosts?"},
{"answer": "Being a responsible host means being a considerate tenant, neighbor, and community member. Here are a few things you should consider when talking with others about hosting on Airbnb.\\nKnow the rules and regulations\\nBefore you start hosting, know what contracts and rules affect you, such as leases, condo board or co-op rules, HOA rules, or rules established by tenant organizations. Make sure you understand and comply with these rules before listing your space. Other laws in your city or state may also affect you, so be sure to review them as well.\\nTalk with your landlord or HOA\\nTalk to your homeowner\\u2019s association or landlord about how often you plan to have guests, and how Airbnb builds trust in its community. You can share information about Airbnb\\u2019s trust and safety resources, including community reviews and Verified ID. Remind them that you only host people you feel comfortable with. If applicable in your country, you can also explain that Airbnb offers a US$1M Host Guarantee.\\nTalk with your neighbors\\nNeighbors may want to know about many of the same things as your landlord or HOA, as well as more specifics about upcoming bookings, such as names, dates, and other information about your guests. Making sure your neighbors are comfortable might help address some of your landlord\\u2019s concerns. \\nBe a responsible host\\nHere are some things you can do to show your landlord, HOA, and neighbors that you care about the property and your neighbors as much as they do:\\n\\nSet an occupancy limit to only allow groups of a certain size \\nShare your home and building rules with each guest\\nProvide your guests with phone numbers for emergency responders and a map of emergency exits and evacuation routes\\nMake sure you have a working smoke and carbon monoxide detector\\nInform neighbors when a guest will be staying in your home\\nWith your guests\\u2019 permission, share names or Airbnb profile pages\\n", "question": "How should I talk to my neighbors, homeowners association, or landlord about Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Whether you want to get to know hosts and guests in your home city, or you\\u2019re looking to meet other people who use Airbnb while you travel, meetups are a great way to connect with our global community, swap tips, and share experiences. Events include things like volunteering at a local garden, taking a neighborhood architectural tour, exchanging hosting tips, or just throwing a party to celebrate the Airbnb community in your city.\\n\\n  Check out our Meetup page to see what's going in your city, or other cities around the world.\\n\\tTo sign up for an Airbnb meetup, you must:\\n\\t  \\n\\t    Have your own Airbnb account\\n\\t   RSVP on the event's invitation page\\n    \\n    \\n  RSVPs are only good for one person per Airbnb account. When you RSVP, you'll receive a confirmation email, and your name and Airbnb profile photo will appear on the confirmed list of attendees.\\n\\nIf a meetup's guest list is full, you'll see the option to add yourself to the waitlist. If a spot opens up, you'll receive a notification.\\n\\n\\nYou can also connect with other hosts and guests at any time through our online community platform, the Airbnb Community Center. Interested in a specific city? Check out our Cities boards.", "question": "What are Airbnb meetups?"},
{"answer": "\\nDepending on your account status, forms submitted to Airbnb, and other factors, you may receive a tax form from Airbnb.\\n\\n\\t\\nAs always, we encourage you to consult a tax professional for assistance reporting your income. If you think you've submitted the wrong information, you can make changes to taxpayer information you've already submitted.\\n\\n\\nAirbnb expects to issue tax forms to the following categories of persons:\\n\\n\\nUS persons who have earned over $20,000 and had 200+ reservations\\n\\n\\nThe Internal Revenue Service (IRS) requires that all US companies processing payments, including Airbnb, report the gross earnings of US customers that earn over $20,000 and have 200+ transactions in the calendar year. If you cross both IRS thresholds in a calendar year, Airbnb will provide you with a Form 1099-K.\\n\\nDelivery of Form 1099-K\\n\\n  Any Form 1099-K issued to you will be available in your Payout Preferences. You'll receive an email notification when your form is ready, typically in late January of each year. We also mail a copy to the address you provided along with your taxpayer information, unless you opted for electronic delivery only. You may receive more than one Form 1099-K if your taxpayer information is listed on multiple Airbnb accounts.\\n\\n\\nNon-US persons who have submitted a Form W-8\\n\\n\\nHosts with US sourced earnings who have filled out a Form W-8 will be provided a Form 1042-S.\\n\\nDelivery of Form 1042-S\\n\\nYou'll receive a Form 1042-S in the mail at the address you entered when you submitted your tax information, typically in late February of each year. The IRS requires that we mail Form 1042-S by the end of March. \\n\\n\\nHosts that had funds withheld from their payouts for taxes\\n\\n\\nIf taxes were withheld from your payouts during the calendar year, you\\u2019ll be provided with the appropriate tax form so that you may account for the withholdings on your income tax return. Read more about withheld taxes.\\n\\n\\nAirbnb service providers (photographers, translators, others)\\n\\t\\n\\nAirbnb service providers, including photographers, translators, and additional service providers, will receive a Form 1099-MISC. \\n\\nDelivery of Form 1099-MISC\\n\\nAny Form 1099-MISC issued to you will be available in your Payout Preferences. You'll receive an email notification when your form is ready, typically in late January of each year. We also mail a copy to the address you provided along with your taxpayer information, unless you opted for electronic delivery only.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Content\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     Where do I find my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?\\n     \\n  \\n", "question": "Should I expect to receive a tax form from Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "\\nAs a host, your earnings may be subject to US income taxes. We expect all hosts to comply with the tax regulations in their area, and encourage you to consult a tax professional if you need advice on reporting your income.\\n\\nH&amp;R Block will provide a $20 discount on in-person tax preparation services and a 35% discount on online tax preparation services for Airbnb hosts who use the service between January 1, 2016 and April 18, 2016. Visit  hrblock.com/Partner/airbnb to learn more. \\n\\nErnst and Young (\\u201cEY\\u201d) has prepared an overview of tax considerations for Airbnb hosts relating to the US taxation of rental income. This information provides an overview of how to complete your US income tax return as well as some of your tax responsibilities as an Airbnb host. Access EY\\u2019s \\u201cGeneral guidance on the taxation of rental income\\u201d here.\\n\\n  Disclaimer: Airbnb's presentation of EY and H&amp;R Block is not an endorsement. Tax advice is complicated, and you should do your own diligence when receiving advice. Airbnb is not responsible for any tax or other advice provided by any outside entity.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     Where do I find my Airbnb earnings for tax purposes?\\n     Should I expect to receive a tax form from Airbnb?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "Resources for the 2015 US Tax Season"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tWe consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us.\\n\\n\\tAirbnb takes trust seriously\\n\\n\\tWe're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives.\\n\\n\\tAirbnb encourages responsibility\\n\\n\\tWe encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting.\\n\\n\\tNeighbor resources\\n\\n\\tIf your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIf you have a VAT ID number registered with the European Commission, you may want to associate that number with your Airbnb account. You can do this whether you're a host operating as a business, or a guest paying with an employer's payment method. This option is not available in Ireland.\\n\\n\\t  To provide a valid VAT Information Exchange System (VIES) VAT ID number for your account:\\n\\n\\n\\t\\tGo to Edit Profile on airbnb.com\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tUnder Optional, click Add VAT ID Number\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tEnter your VAT ID number verification information\\n\\t\\t\\n\\t\\tClick Verify\\n\\t\\t\\n\\t\\tClick Save\\n\\n\\nWhen your VAT ID number is successfully verified by the European Commission, you won't be charged VAT on our service fees. It will be your responsibility to self-assess whether you need to pay VAT for the use of our services. \\n\\nProblems verifying VAT ID number\\n\\n\\nIf your VAT ID number isn't successfully verified by the European Commission, you may want to try re-entering your information. Airbnb isn't able to associate a VAT ID number with your account without this verification, and can't troubleshoot problems. For a list of correct formats for VAT ID numbers by member state and additional information, please see the European Commission's VIES FAQ.\\n\\n \\nIf your VAT ID number can't be verified and you determine you need to self-assess VAT on our service fees, we encourage you to consult a tax advisor for assistance.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Article\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     Where do I find my VAT invoice?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I provide my VAT ID number?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tA VAT invoice is provided whenever VAT is assessed on Airbnb service fees. An invoice is finalized and issued when a reservation is accepted, and includes your information (name, address, etc) as you entered it in your Airbnb account. Airbnb is not able to modify a VAT invoice after it's been issued.\\n\\nGuests\\n\\n\\tTo access the VAT invoice for your reservation:\\n\\n  \\nGo to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n\\nUnder the trip, click View Invoices\\n\\nSelect Guest Invoice\\n\\n\\nFor reservation details, reference your billing receipt. If you believe you need additional documentation for travel, we encourage you to communicate with your host before booking to see if they're able to assist you.\\n\\nHosts\\n\\n\\tTo access the VAT invoice for your reservation:\\n\\n  \\nGo to Your Listings on airbnb.com\\n\\nSelect Your Reservations on the left\\n\\nIf the reservation you're looking for isn't displayed, click View all reservation history\\n\\nTo the right of the reservation, click View VAT Invoices\\n\\nSelect Host Invoice\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tIf you add a verified VAT ID number to your account, it will be included on VAT invoices created after the addition. For reservation details, reference your host confirmation.\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Article\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     How do I provide my VAT ID number?\\n    \\n  \\n.", "question": "Where do I find my VAT invoice?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb Open is our annual host convention that includes workshops, keynote presentations, and festive celebrations. Hosts learn hospitality tips from industry leaders, improve their knowledge of Airbnb's platform, connect with others, and share feedback and tips. \\n\\nAirbnb Open 2016 will be in Los Angeles. Stay tuned to airbnbopen.com for dates and more information.", "question": "What is Airbnb Open?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tValue Added Tax, or VAT, is a tax assessed on the supply of goods and services. In Japan, Japanese Consumption Tax, or JCT, is applicable instead of VAT. JCT is a tax assessed on the supply of digital services.\\n\\t\\n\\n\\tVAT and JCT rates are calculated according to the local rate of the customer's country of residence. Airbnb charges VAT on its service fees for customers from the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and South Africa. Airbnb charges JCT on its service fees for customers from Japan.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tGuests\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tVAT or JCT is charged at the time of payment and is based on the total guest service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.\\n\\n\\tHosts\\n\\n\\tVAT or JCT is deducted from your payout and is based on the total host service fee for a reservation. If you change your reservation, VAT adjusts to reflect any change in the service fee.\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     Where can I find my VAT invoice?\\n     What are the service fees?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "What is VAT and how does it apply to me?"},
{"answer": "The Community Center is a place to connect with other hosts, share stories, ask for advice, and get updates from the Airbnb team. You can also plan or join meetups.\\n\\nGetting started\\n\\nHere are a few of the features the Community Center offers:\\n\\n\\n  Conversations: Ask a question, share a story, or connect with other hosts by starting a conversation\\u2014or joining in on an existing one.\\nTags: Add topic tags to your conversations to help people find and follow them. We\\u2019ll show trending topics on the Community Center homepage. You can also follow a topic to get updates whenever new content is posted.\\nTop contributors: We\\u2019re so lucky to have a vibrant and active community of hosts, and we want to make sure your amazing contributions to the community get recognized\\u2014that\\u2019s why you\\u2019ll see a Top Contributors section on the homepage. New to hosting? Use this section to find a community expert.\\nDirect messaging: Want to ask another host a private question? You can now direct message other community members right from the Community Center.\\nMeetups: Meetups are a great way to meet other hosts, share best practices, and get advice from people like you. Over 12,000 meetups have been organized by hosts in 85 cities around the world.\\n  \\n\\nAvailable languages\\nThe Community Center is available in English, French, Italian, German, Spanish, Brazilian Portuguese, Korean, Dutch, and Japanese. We plan to offer support more languages soon.  \\n\\nCities\\nCities boards are location-specific boards you can use to connect with other hosts in your area. You can view any Cities board to connect with hosts in that area.\\n\\nDon\\u2019t see your city yet? Use the Where in the world? board to start a location-specific conversation. You can use tags to help other community members find your post.\\n\\nManaging the Community Center\\nThis is your community. You own the discussions, and the Community Center will ultimately rely heavily on your level of engagement. \\nThe Community Center will be largely self-moderated, but you may also see a faces from the Airbnb team around from time to time to to share updates, answer tricky questions, and help keep things clean and safe.\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nVisit the Community Center\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is the Airbnb Community Center?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tAirbnb may limit, suspend, or deactivate your account, as outlined in our Terms of Service.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\nYour account may be temporarily deactivated due to your response rate or acceptance rate. To reactivate your account in this case, please follow the steps in the email you received.\\n\\nYour account may be deactivated during a review of Airbnb accounts. Reviews are part of an effort to foster a trustworthy community and uphold the Terms of Service.\\n\\nThe following may occur with or without notifying you directly:\\nYour account can be deactivated or suspendedYou may not be able to access the platform, your account or content, or receive assistance from Airbnb Customer Experience\\n\\n\\tAny upcoming pending or accepted reservations you have as either a host or guest can be canceled; you may not be entitled to any compensation for the reservations that were canceled as a result of your suspension. We also may:\\n\\tCommunicate to the appropriate guests or hosts that their reservation was canceled.\\n\\tRefund guests in full, regardless of the cancellation policy.\\n\\tContact guests about alternative accommodations that may be available.", "question": "Can Airbnb deactivate my account?"},
{"answer": "To cancel your Airbnb account, go to Account &gt; Settings &gt; Cancel my account.\\n\\tWhen you cancel your account, any reservations you've made as a host or a guest will automatically be canceled.\\n\\t\\n\\tIf you want to reopen a canceled account, contact us.\\n\\nIf you want to deactivate a listing instead of canceling your account, learn how.", "question": "How do I cancel my account?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIf you don't have an Airbnb account yet, go to airbnb.com and click Sign Up.\\n\\n\\tYou can sign up using your email address, Facebook account, Google account, or Amex. Signing up and creating an Airbnb account is free.\\n\\n\\tAfter you sign up, be sure to complete your account before booking a reservation.", "question": "How do I create an account?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb empowers hosts to set and manage their cancellation policies. If a host or guest needs to cancel a reservation, it\\u2019s their responsibility to cancel as soon as possible. At times, certain circumstances outside of a host or guest\\u2019s control can impact their ability to meet the terms of a reservation.\\n\\nIn rare instances, if Airbnb determines that a Guest\\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, Airbnb may override the Host's cancellation policy (ex: flexible, moderate, strict) and make refund decisions.  If Airbnb determines that a Host\\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances policy, Airbnb may waive the host cancellation penalties outlined in Airbnb\\u2019s Terms of Service and Airbnb\\u2019s Payments Terms of Service.\\n\\nWhat might be covered?\\n\\nValid extenuating circumstances include:\\n\\n\\nUnexpected death or serious illness of a host, guest or immediate family member \\nSerious injury that directly restricts a guest\\u2019s ability to travel or a host\\u2019s ability to host\\nSignificant natural disasters or severe weather incidents impacting the location of destination or location of departure\\nUrgent travel restrictions or severe security advisories issued after the time of booking, by an appropriate national or international authority (such as a government office or department)\\nEndemic disease declared by a credible national or international authority (such as the US Center for Disease Control or the World Health Organization)\\nSevere property damage or unforeseen maintenance issues that directly impact the ability to host safely\\nGovernment-mandated obligations issued after the time of booking\\n\\n\\nIf you need to make a claim\\n\\nClaims can only be considered after a reservation has been canceled. Once you have informed your host or guest and canceled a reservation, if you feel that your reason for cancellation is covered by Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, contact Airbnb for consideration. We generally require claims to be submitted no later than 14 days from the original check-in date and we may require valid supporting documentation.", "question": "Extenuating Circumstances Policy"},
{"answer": "Guests and hosts work out details for checking in, exchanging keys, and checking out directly with each other. There is no online check-in or checkout process.\\nRead below for some guidelines to help you have a smooth check-in.\\nCommunication is essential\\nBefore the start of the reservation, message your host to figure out check-in and checkout times, make plans for the key exchange, and ask any other questions. Keeping communication in your message thread gives you and Airbnb a clear reference if any issues come up.\\nAlso, confirm your contact information and arrival details so you can reach each other in case plans change. Make sure to let each other know if you'll be without access to a phone or the Internet.\\nKnow your reservation details\\nAfter a reservation is confirmed, refer to your itinerary for useful information about your reservation, such as the check-in and checkout time, the listing's address, your host's contact information, and your billing receipt. If there's no check-in or check-out time specified within a listing's description, check-in is 3:00 PM local time and checkout is 12:00 PM local time.\\nStay tuned to flight information and weather forecasts\\nLook up travel advisories to make sure there is nothing impacting your reservation. With road closures and flight delays, guests and hosts might need a little extra time to safely meet up to exchange keys.\\nKey exchange\\nMany hosts greet guests in person to exchange keys. Others send keys and instructions in the mail, leave them in a lockbox, or have a neighbor meet a guest. The host can decide whether or not to give a guest a key. But, our Guest Refund Policy states that guests need to have reasonable access to the listing they booked. If you decide not to provide keys, you should mention in your listing\\u2019s description and house rules that keys will not be available to the guests so people are aware of the situation before booking.", "question": "How does check-in work?"},
{"answer": "Traveling with Airbnb provides an opportunity to stay in unique spaces and connect with other members of our community. Like millions of travelers before you, we hope you find that experiencing a destination like a local creates memories, stories, and a feeling of belonging no matter how far you journey from home.\\n\\nTo help you prepare, here are a few tips to help enhance your experience with your listing and your host.\\n\\nBefore you book\\n\\n\\tShare your story in the bio section of your profile, and get a Verified ID. Hosts prefer to know who's asking to stay with them, and as a result you may have a better chance of your requests being accepted.\\n\\t\\n\\tAirbnb has a diversity of listings, from shared rooms to entire homes. Make sure the space, house rules, and hosting style match your needs.\\n\\n\\tSpend some time reviewing your host's listing to make sure the place is a good match for you.\\n\\t\\n\\tGet a sense of the strengths and weaknesses of the listing by reading reviews from other travelers.\\n\\t\\n\\tFeel free to contact a host with any questions you have about a listing.\\n\\n\\nBefore your trip\\n\\n\\tCommunicate clearly with your host about any expectations or special needs you may have.\\n\\t\\n\\tAlways let your host know if you're likely to arrive late for check-in.\\n\\n\\nOn your trip\\n\\n\\tHonor your commitments (including arrival time) and any house rules.\\n\\t\\n\\tEnjoy your host's home as if you were staying with friends. Be respectful of your neighbors.\\n\\t\\n\\tExplore the neighborhood and support local businesses. It's a great way to feel more like a local. Try asking your host about their favorite neighborhood spots!\\n\\t\\n\\tGet your host's permission before having guests over.\\n\\t\\n\\tWhen in doubt, reach out to your host with any questions or problems that arise.\\n\\n\\nAfter your trip\\n\\n\\tAlways leave an honest review for your host to help guide future guests. Airbnb is built on community, and your host will also be invited to leave a review for you.\\n", "question": "How can I be a considerate guest?"},
{"answer": "Hosts share their House Rules to set expectations with their guests, like limits on smoking, areas beyond the listing space that are off-limits, and permission to have visitors. \\nTo add or edit House Rules after you\\u2019ve listed your space:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick on the listing you want to edit\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\nUnder Hosting, click on Booking\\n\\nUnder House Rules, enter your expectations and rules for guests\\n\\n\\nIf a guest breaks a house rule, either before or during their stay, you can cancel their reservation without penalty. \\nHouse rules appear on your listing page, and guests must review and agree to them before requesting a reservation. They\\u2019re also sent directly to a guest once they\\u2019ve a confirmed reservation.", "question": "What are house rules?"},
{"answer": "If you notice that something is missing, not working, or otherwise not what you expected when you check in, contact your host right away. Your host is often in the best position to help you\\u2014giving them the chance to fix an issue can be the fastest way to make sure you get what you need, and can continue on with your reservation as planned.\\n\\nIn the event that you experience a travel issue, and you and your host aren't able to resolve the issue on your own, please take the following required steps within 24 hours of your check-in to make sure you're covered by our Guest Refund Policy:\\n  \\n\\t  Contact us to document the issue and place a hold on the host's payment.\\n\\t  Message your host on Airbnb to notify them of the issue. We'll need to verify this in your account.\\n    Take photographs to document the situation. It's important that your photos show what's happening and where (in relation to the rest of the room or space) so we can verify what's going on.\\n  \\n\\nIf your host is unreachable or unresponsive, we'll work on issuing you an adequate partial refund if you decide to stay, or a full refund if you decide to leave, as we deem appropriate. You can see a complete explanation of coverage in our Guest Refund Policy.\\n\\n\\nThe Guest Refund Policy doesn't apply beyond 24 hours after check-in, but we can always help you mediate with your host if you've tried reaching out with no response.\\n\\n\\n      \\n        \\n        Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n        \\n      \\n", "question": "What should I do if something's missing or not as expected when I check in?"},
{"answer": "\\nNo. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nHow does Airbnb handle security deposits?\\nHow do I include a security deposit on my listing?\\nHow do I make a claim on the security deposit?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "The Resolution Center lets you request or send money for things related to your Airbnb trip. To open a refund or payment request, go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions. \\n    You have up to 60 days after your reservation's checkout date to submit a Resolution Center request.\\n\\nAsking for help from Airbnb\\n\\n    If you\\u2019re unable to reach an agreement, you can ask Airbnb to make the final decision 72 hours after the request was opened. To involve Airbnb:\\n    \\n    \\n      Wait 72 hours after you open the request\\n      Go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions \\n      Select the correct reservation\\n      Click Involve Airbnb\\n    \\n\\nWhen you involve Airbnb, our team will be notified and a dedicated team member will be assigned to your case. They\\u2019ll review the information provided by you and your host or guest, before making a final decision. In some cases, we may need to contact you to gather additional information, before we can make a decision.\\n\\n", "question": "What is the Resolution Center?"},
{"answer": "When you book a listing with a security deposit, your payment details are stored but not charged or authorized for the deposit unless the host makes a claim. The host has 48 hours from your checkout date to make a claim on the deposit for damages to their property.\\nWhat to expect if a host reports damages\\nIf your host makes a claim on your security deposit, here\\u2019s the process that will be followed:\\n\\n  We'll ask for documentation from the host, and as soon as we receive it, we'll ask them to contact you through Airbnb\\u2019s Resolution Center to discuss the claim. If your host sends you a request, you'll be notified by email and through an alert on your Dashboard.\\n    Reply to your host's request in the Resolution Center within 48 hours. Your response will depend on whether or not you agree to the amount requested by the host:\\n    \\n      Agree to the amount: Click Accept in the Resolution Center. We'll process your payment and send it to your host, which usually takes 5 to 7 business days.\\n            Don't agree to the amount: Click Involve Airbnb in the Resolution Center and let us know why you think your host's claim is invalid. We'll contact you and give you 48 hours to respond to us so we can mediate.\\n    \\n    \\n\\nIn any case, we'll make sure you and your host are represented fairly and gather any details and documentation needed to reach a resolution. Most security deposit claims will be resolved within one week.\\n\\tDocumentation from hosts\\nCommunication through email is required in order to collect needed documentation from the host, which will include photos and/or video along with receipts, invoices, written estimates, or links to comparable items denoting actual cash value for repair or replacement. If we determine money is owed based on documentation and communication from both parties, we will move forward with collecting from the deposit.\\xa0We reserve the right to collect payment from you using the payment details we have on file.", "question": "What happens if a host makes a claim on my security deposit?"},
{"answer": "When you book a place on Airbnb, you\\u2019re making arrangements to stay in someone\\u2019s home. Each host has their own style of hospitality, starting with how they like to get to know their guests. Some hosts want to approve reservations, while others are comfortable letting you book their place instantly without waiting for approval.\\n\\n1. Complete Your Profile\\nIn either case, it\\u2019s important to know that Airbnb is a community that relies on trust. Complete your profile before you request a reservation with a host, so they can know a little bit about you when they confirm. Your profile should include photos and verifications, especially because some hosts require guests to have a profile photo or Verified ID in order to book.\\n2. Find the Right Place\\nWith over 800,000 unique listings around the world, you\\u2019ll want to make sure the place you choose has everything you need for a comfortable and memorable trip.\\nWhen searching for a place, make sure to include your dates and number of guests to get the most accurate pricing. Read reviews, descriptions, house rules, and amenities for each place to see if it\\u2019s the right fit for your trip. You can always contact the host if you have any questions about their home.\\n3. Book It!\\nYou\\u2019ve found the perfect place, and now it\\u2019s time to make it official. This is where the host\\u2019s preferred way of booking will determine how you\\u2019ll confirm your reservation.\\nInstant Book\\nFor hosts who don\\u2019t want to approve each reservation, you\\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Instant Book. Like the name suggests, you can confirm a reservation at these places right away. Learn more about Instant Book.\\nRequest to Book\\nMany hosts prefer to approve reservations before they\\u2019re final. In this case, you\\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Request to Book. To submit a reservation request, you\\u2019ll need to enter your payment details. Hosts have 24 hours to accept your request, and your reservation is automatically confirmed once they do. Learn more about submitting a reservation request.\\nPre-approvals and Special Offers\\nIf you decide to contact the host to ask questions before attempting to book, the host may respond to your message by inviting you to make a reservation with either a pre-approval or Special Offer. A pre-approval is an invitation to finish booking for the dates and number of guests you noted in your message. A Special Offer gives the host the opportunity to provide special pricing, dates, and other reservation details before you book. Learn more about booking a pre-approval or Special Offer.", "question": "How do I book a place on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tInstant Book listings don't require approval from the host before you can book them. Instead, you can just choose your travel dates and discuss check-in plans with the host. There is no additional fee for confirming a reservation with Instant Book. You can filter your search to only view listings that are available through Instant Book.\\n\\n\\tTo be eligible for Instant Book, you must complete your Airbnb account.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I turn Instant Book on or off as a host?\\nHow does check-in work?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "Transparency and trust are vital to the Airbnb experience. People rely on information in Airbnb profiles, reviews, and other verifications when deciding whether to host or stay with someone. \\n\\nWe require Airbnb reservations booked for personal travel to be booked by the person who's going to stay at the listing.\\n\\nInstead of making a reservation for someone else, consider referring them to Airbnb. You can refer them to Airbnb directly from your dashboard by clicking the Invite Friends button. When a referred friend or family member successfully completes a qualifying reservation, you\\u2019ll earn travel credit.\\n  \\n  For business trips, Airbnb allows designated bookers at companies enrolled in Airbnb for Business to book trips on behalf of others. If you book travel for a company, read more.", "question": "Can I book on behalf of a friend or family member?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason.\\n\\nCommon issues   \\n           Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.\\n   \\n   Contact your bank or card issuer        \\nIf you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through.\\n\\nIf your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "The Community Center is a place to connect with other hosts, share stories, ask for advice, and get updates from the Airbnb team. You can also plan or join meetups.\\n\\nGetting started\\n\\nHere are a few of the features the Community Center offers:\\n\\n\\n  Conversations: Ask a question, share a story, or connect with other hosts by starting a conversation\\u2014or joining in on an existing one.\\nTags: Add topic tags to your conversations to help people find and follow them. We\\u2019ll show trending topics on the Community Center homepage. You can also follow a topic to get updates whenever new content is posted.\\nTop contributors: We\\u2019re so lucky to have a vibrant and active community of hosts, and we want to make sure your amazing contributions to the community get recognized\\u2014that\\u2019s why you\\u2019ll see a Top Contributors section on the homepage. New to hosting? Use this section to find a community expert.\\nDirect messaging: Want to ask another host a private question? You can now direct message other community members right from the Community Center.\\nMeetups: Meetups are a great way to meet other hosts, share best practices, and get advice from people like you. Over 12,000 meetups have been organized by hosts in 85 cities around the world.\\n  \\n\\nAvailable languages\\nThe Community Center is available in English, French, Italian, German, Spanish, Brazilian Portuguese, Korean, Dutch, and Japanese. We plan to offer support more languages soon.  \\n\\nCities\\nCities boards are location-specific boards you can use to connect with other hosts in your area. You can view any Cities board to connect with hosts in that area.\\n\\nDon\\u2019t see your city yet? Use the Where in the world? board to start a location-specific conversation. You can use tags to help other community members find your post.\\n\\nManaging the Community Center\\nThis is your community. You own the discussions, and the Community Center will ultimately rely heavily on your level of engagement. \\nThe Community Center will be largely self-moderated, but you may also see a faces from the Airbnb team around from time to time to to share updates, answer tricky questions, and help keep things clean and safe.\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nVisit the Community Center\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is the Airbnb Community Center?"},
{"answer": "Guidebooks let hosts suggest local spots, like restaurants, grocery stores, parks, and attractions. If you add a Guidebook to your listing, your recommended places will appear on the map on your public listing page. \\nSome cities also have city guidebooks, which are combined lists of recommendations that hosts have added to their own guidebooks.\\nAdd a host guidebook to a listing\\nTo create your guidebook:\\n\\n  Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com.\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit.\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu.\\nClick Guidebook.\\nUnder a category, enter a business name or address of a favorites place.\\nWrite a short recommendation and any tags that apply.\\nClick Add.\\n\\nYou'll need to create a separate host guidebook for each of your listings. You can only create a host guidebook once you've completed the steps to list your space.\\nSince these guidebooks are public, you\\u2019ll have to remove your recommendations if you don\\u2019t want them to appear for all guests.\\n\\nEdit or delete a host guidebook\\nYou can edit or remove recommendations from your guidebook, or delete your guidebook altogether.\\n\\n  Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\nClick Guidebook\\nNext to the business you want to edit, click Edit\\nIf you want to remove the business, click Delete. Otherwise, you can edit your recommendation.\\n\\nTo delete your guidebook, you need to remove each recommendation individually.\\nHost recommendations in city guidebooks\\nWith city guidebooks, recommendations from host guidebooks are used to provide a detailed picture of what guests can do in that city. Three recommendations will be featured and will include a link to the host\\u2019s guidebook and listing. These featured recommendations will change over time.\\nTo determine which recommendations to use, our algorithms look at the most interesting content created around each location, based on informativeness, uniqueness, and representation of the place. We then show the most helpful recommendations which seem to provide the most compelling information for guests.\\nThe best way to be featured in city guidebooks is to continue expanding your own host guidebook with your favorite places in the area.\\nCan\\u2019t find a city guidebook \\nAt this time, not all cities have a city guidebook but we\\u2019re actively looking to add more. The best way to help your city get a guidebook is to expand your own host guidebook with your recommendations. Once enough hosts create robust guidebooks, this information can be gathered together in a city guidebook.\\nLeave feedback about guidebooks\\nIf you have any thoughts or concerns about guidebooks, you can provide us direct feedback. While not all feedback will make it to the site or receive a response, we encourage you to share your knowledge and opinions.", "question": "What's a Guidebook?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tNo, Airbnb can't split your reservation cost across multiple payment methods. To make a reservation, you'll need to make your payment with a single payment method.\\n\\n\\n\\tIf you need to update your payment method for a long-term reservation or an unsuccessful charge, please contact us for assistance.\\n\\t\\n\\n\\tIf you have a confirmed reservation that isn't long-term, remember that you've already paid in full through our payment system\\u2014so you won't need to change or update your payment method to enjoy your trip.", "question": "Can I use more than one payment method to pay for a reservation?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tPayoneer is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If the option appears for your selected country, you'll be able to sign up for Payoneer\\u2014if you already have a Payoneer card, contact them to connect Airbnb payouts to your existing account.\\n\\nSigning up with Payoneer\\n\\n\\tWhen you sign up for Payoneer as a new customer with Airbnb, be sure that you enter the same address that you provided on the Airbnb payout method page. After signing up, Payoneer will approve your details or ask for additional information (like a copy of your government issued ID or Social Security card) by email within 2 days. When approved by Payoneer, a card will be mailed to you within 4-15 business days. You need to activate the card to receive funds. If you don't receive the card, please contact Payoneer customer service.\\n\\nReceiving payouts\\n\\n\\n\\tPayoneer allows you to receive payouts directly to a Payoneer Prepaid Debit MasterCard. Once activated, Airbnb will load your payouts in USD or EUR, depending on your country, and you can view your balance on Payoneer's website. Airbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and Payoneer typically delivers the funds to your account within 1-3 hours.\\n\\nAdditional fees\\n\\n\\n\\tPayoneer applies fees for certain transactions, some of which are listed below. Additionally, there are fees for transactions originated outside of the Payoneer country of issuance. Please visit Payoneer's Help Center for more information.\\n\\n\\nAnnual Card Account Maintenance:\\nFree - Payoneer's regular $29.95 fee is waived for Airbnb customers\\n\\nPurchase Transaction:\\nFree, except when  transaction is made in a different currency (3% foreign transaction fee)\\n\\nCash Withdrawal Fee in the US (ATM and in-branch):\\n$1.75 per withdrawal - ATM surcharges may also apply\\n\\nCash Withdrawal Fee outside the US (ATM and in-branch):\\n$3.15 per withdrawal - ATM surcharges may also apply\\n\\nATM Withdrawal Decline Fee:\\n$1 per decline\\n\\nATM Balance Inquiry Fee:\\n$1 per inquiry\\n\\nCard Replacement:\\n$12.95 per replacement card\\n", "question": "How do I use Payoneer to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "\\nIt usually takes less than five business days for your new payout method to be able to accept Airbnb payouts. When the status updates to Ready, we'll be able to send you your payouts.\\n\\n\\n\\tThere are 4 different statuses your payout method may have:\\n\\t\\n    New: we can't send payouts to this payout method; the payout method is still editable\\n    \\n    Pending: please wait for the status to change, or for email communication about any additional verification needed; the payout method isn't editable\\n    \\n    Ready: we can send payouts to this payout method; the payout method isn't editable\\n    \\n    Error: please remove this payout method and add a new payout method; we can't send payouts to this payout method\\n\\n\\t\\n\\tIn some countries, we'll verify your account information when you provide it to us the first time by depositing a small sum (less than $1 USD) before sending you a payout. This is to make sure we avoid sending money to the wrong account, and we only need to verify it once. Go ahead and keep the change! It's on us.\\n\\t\\n\\n\\n  Related Articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     How do I add a payout method?\\n     How do I split income between multiple people?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How long does it take a host's payout method to become ready?"},
{"answer": "\\nPayPal is only available as an Airbnb payout method in certain countries at this time. To see if it's available to you, look for it when you add a payout method. If PayPal appears for your selected country, you'll be able to connect your existing PayPal account as a payout method.\\n\\nConnecting your PayPal account\\n\\n\\nYou need to have an existing PayPal account to successfully use PayPal as a payout method. Activate your PayPal account, which is associated with your email address, before adding it as an Airbnb payout method. Find out more about PayPal, including how to create an account, at PayPal.com.\\n\\n\\n\\nWhen you add PayPal as an Airbnb payout method, make sure that you enter the email address associated with your PayPal account correctly.\\n\\nReceiving payouts\\n\\nPayPal allows you to receive payouts directly to your PayPal account. Once the payout method is ready, Airbnb will deposit your payouts to your PayPal account and you can view and access your balance on PayPal's website.\\n\\nAirbnb releases payouts approximately 24 hours after the check-in date, and PayPal typically delivers the funds to your account within 1 business day.", "question": "How do I use PayPal to receive payouts?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is reviews. Leaving a review for your guests is a chance to show your gratitude and provide helpful feedback.\\n\\nBecause reviews are public, your reviews help other hosts know what to expect when they receive a reservation request from a guest who stayed at your listing. Similarly, when you receive a review, it's your opportunity to use your guests' feedback to make improvements to your listing or the hospitality you provide.\\nTimeline for reviews\\nYou have 14 days to complete your review after a trip has ended. You'll only see your feedback from a completed trip after both you and your guest have left a review, or at the end of the 14-day review period.\\nYou and your guest both have 2 weeks to respond to the review you receive. Your comments will appear on your listing page, directly below the review they refer to.\\nProviding constructive feedback\\nIf you have constructive feedback for a guest, give them guidance either in your review or in private feedback. Be sure to address sensitive feedback with kindness and professionalism. When possible, include concrete examples of the behaviors they can change. Particularly if your guest is new to traveling on Airbnb, your feedback will help them become expert travelers.\\n\\n\\n\\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "Why are reviews important?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is amenities. Amenities are the useful or fun features your space provides, and the set of amenities a listing offers can be one of the main things that helps it stand out.\\n\\nWhile all Airbnb hosts should consider providing basic amenities like soap, toilet paper, sheets, and towels, many travelers are also interested in specific amenities like a hair dryer, Wi-Fi, or a hot tub\\u2014or are specifically looking for things like family-friendliness. Even knowing small details, like whether or not you provide shampoo and conditioner in your space, can help guests plan for their trip.\\n\\nAccurately listing the amenities your space offers may be the reason a guest decides to stay in your space\\u2014and ensuring that every single one is available and operational during your guest's stay will help make it a great one.\\n\\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "What are amenities and why are they important to guests?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is cleanliness. Providing a clean and tidy space will make your guests feel comfortable from the moment they arrive\\u2014and show your commitment to making your guests feel welcome.\\n\\nTo make your listing shine, consider starting with these steps before each guest's arrival:\\n\\n  Clean every room that your guests can access during their stay and pay special attention to the bathroom and kitchen.\\n  If you provide towels and sheets, make sure they're freshly-washed.\\n  To show extra consideration, think about the small things, like dusting the bookshelves, wiping the mirrors, and emptying the wastebasket.\\n  Make room in the closet or dresser so that guests can store their belongings.\\n\\n\\nWe know that cleaning is one of the more challenging aspects of preparing your listing, particularly if you're traveling yourself. If you can't do the cleaning, you can always add a cleaning fee to your listing price and hire a professional cleaning service.\\n\\nIt's important to give yourself enough time to clean your space, particularly when you have back-to-back bookings. Giving your guests the ability to tidy up after themselves will be a big help, so consider leaving cleaning supplies in your space, so they can take care of spills and accidental messes.\\n\\n\\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I provide a clean space for my guests?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is support. Whether or not you're sharing a space with your guests, it's important to remain available and responsive throughout their stay. If they can't find the toaster or if the faucet starts leaking, your guests should know they can get help.\\n\\nAvailability\\n\\nMake sure your guests have your contact information, and respond to their questions or requests quickly. If you won't be greeting your guests when they arrive, send them a message at their check-in time to make sure everything went smoothly. If you won't be in the area during their stay, give your guests a local point of contact.\\n\\nExpectations and resources\\n\\nProvide detailed House Rules, so your guests know how you'd like for them to treat your space. In the listing, itself, anticipate their needs and provide items and resources that will help them feel at home. Leave a list of phone numbers for taxi companies, restaurants you recommend, and emergency contacts. Each guest will be different\\u2014some will prefer privacy, while others will want to interact with you more often.\\n\\nLiving like a local\\n\\nSometimes guests and hosts make plans together. For other trips, you may not be available, or your guests may prefer to explore the area on their own. To help them feel comfortable, create a host guidebook that highlights your favorite local sights and activities. In some cities, you can also point them to a city guidebook with further recommendations from other hosts in the area.\\n\\nDeparture\\n\\nMake sure your guests' departure is just as easy as their arrival. The process for returning keys and checking out should be clear and simple.\\n\\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I make my guests feel supported?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is welcome. One of the main ways you can make guests feel welcome in a new place is to provide a clear and simple check-in process:\\n\\n  Communicate your check-in procedure in advance, and make sure you're able to follow through with it at the check-in time you discussed.\\n  Make sure your guests know how to contact you in the event of a travel delay or last-minute question.\\n  Provide your guests with detailed directions so they can get to your listing from the highway, train station, or airport. Save time by putting it all in your House Manual.\\n  Let your guests know if you'll greet them at the door, or if they should plan on getting the keys from a lockbox or a neighbor.\\n\\nInterested in going beyond the basics? You could offer pick up your guests when they arrive in town, leave a welcome note to help them get acquainted with your space or neighborhood, or provide a fun welcome treat like flowers or a local snack.\\n\\nYou can also help guests get oriented to the area with a map or guidebook of your favorite places. Some cities also have city guidebooks that you can point them to for further recommendations from other hosts in the area.\\n\\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How can I help make my guests feel welcome?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is commitment. When you confirm you'll host someone, they're trusting you to take care of their needs. That's why it's important to make sure you are able to commit to a guest, before accepting a reservation.\\nIf the unexpected happens and you can't avoid cancelling a confirmed booking, here are some things to keep in mind:\\n\\n  As soon as you understand that you have to cancel, let your guest know right away. This will give them as much time as possible to find new accommodations.\\n  Be empathetic when you tell your guest that you need to cancel, and do it with a kind, thoughtful tone. You'll need to cancel the reservation within Airbnb to initiate the refund process.\\n  If you know other hosts in your area, consider asking them if they can accommodate this guest\\u2019s trip and offer to make an introduction.\\n\\n\\nOf course, hosts always decide who stays in their space. When there is an extenuating circumstance or a safety concern, we may make an exception to host cancellation penalties. In such cases, hosts should select the Extenuating Circumstance option when canceling the reservation.\\n\\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "What does commitment mean for hosts?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is availability. It's important to share up-to-date availability with potential guests to help them (and you!) make travel plans.\\n\\nCalendar availability\\nKeeping your listing calendar up to date is an ongoing commitment. Making sure it accurately reflects your availability, helps ensure that you won't receive reservation requests for dates that you can't accomodate.\\n\\nIf you need to decline a reservation request because you accidentally made your calendar available when it should be blocked, be sure to let the guest know you're declining because your space isn't available on the dates they requested. They may be interested in other dates.\\n\\nReservation requirements\\nSetting reservation requirements can help make sure you receive requests from guests who match your hosting style. You can also check out the reviews a guest received from other hosts to learn more about them.\\n\\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar?\\nHow do I set reservation requirements?\\nWhy are reviews important?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Why is availability important as a host?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is communication. It's important to respond to booking inquiries and reservation requests within 24 hours in order maintain your response rate. Before you confirm a booking, get to know your prospective guest to see if you're a good fit for one another. If their plans don't match your hosting style or what your listing has to offer, just decline the reservation promptly.\\n\\nResponding to guests\\n\\nEvery time a guest reaches out\\u2014whether you have a booking with them or not\\u2014it's important that you respond quickly. Timely responses show travelers that you\\u2019re an attentive and considerate host, but it's not the only thing that matters. Make sure you maintain a helpful and polite tone, and find opportunities to personalize your communication so that you can build trusting relationships with other members of the Airbnb community.\\n \\nBefore your guest arrives \\n\\nWhen you have a confirmed booking that's about to begin, you should communicate with your guest shortly before their arrival. Ensure they know how to reach you, and see if there\\u2019s anything you can do to help make their arrival more comfortable.\\n\\nUnexpected changes\\n\\nIf something about your listing has changed since the time you confirmed a booking, communicate it in advance. If your roommate moved out and took all the pots and pans with them, your guest deserves to know.\\n  \\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "How should I communicate with my guests?"},
{"answer": "One of Airbnb's Hosting Standards is accuracy. Giving travelers a sense of who you are and what your listing has to offer can help them feel more comfortable requesting a reservation. Creating a detailed profile and accurate listing will help attract guests and set their expectations.\\n\\nYour personal profile\\n\\nYour Airbnb profile is the first opportunity you have to introduce yourself to travelers and get them excited about staying with you. Use a photo that clearly shows your face, share some details about your hosting style, and add a fun fact about yourself.\\n\\nYour listing\\n\\nAn accurate and informative listing lets potential guests know what to expect from you space:\\n\\n  Use high-quality photos, write a detailed description of the space, select the correct room type, and highlight the amenities you have.\\n  Make clear what isn\\u2019t available to guests\\u2014if you don\\u2019t have reliable hot water, say so.\\n  Let guests know if there are parts of the listing that are off-limits, like a shared backyard or the attic.\\n  Provide detailed House Rules that address the situations that will matter to your guests. If you don't want your guests bringing other people into the space, tell them in advance.\\n  Be honest and candid about the unexpected factors that will impact your guests' stay. If your neighbors just started a noisy construction project, your guests deserve to know.\\n\\nPricing\\nGuests will evaluate the value of your listing, so it's important to set a price that balances expectations with what your listing has to offer. When you're setting your price, you may want to start with Airbnb's tips and make adjustments based on similar spaces nearby. You can always set weekend rates, or adjust your prices to match seasonal trends. If you're a first-time host, consider lowering your rate so that you can get a few bookings and reviews, gain some experience, and start developing your hosting style.\\n\\n\\nLearn more about our other Hosting Standards.", "question": "What does it mean to have an accurate profile and listing?"},
{"answer": "\\n  \\nNever pay for a reservation outside Airbnb's secure, on-site payment system. If a host or guest asks to pay for a reservation outside our on-site payment system, report the message by clicking  in the message thread with that person.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nAirbnb host payouts are available through Western Union in some countries. To see if Western Union is available to you as a payout method:\\n\\n\\n  Go to Account on airbnb.com.\\n\\nSelect Payout Preferences on the left.\\n\\nClick Add Payout Method. After entering your address, you'll see a list of your payout and currency options.\\n\\n\\nIf Western Union isn\\u2019t listed, it's not available as a payout method for your country.\\n\\nIf Western Union is available and you choose it as your payout method, enter your name as it appears on your government ID, including your first, middle, and last names. To collect your payouts, your official ID will need to match your account information.\\n\\nCollecting Western Union host payouts\\n\\nIf you choose Western Union as your payout method, you'll receive a unique confirmation number (called an MTCN) in an email from Airbnb 1-2 business days after each reservation begins. You need this number to pick up your money from a Western Union Quick Cash agent location. Western Union payouts expire after 30 days.\\n\\nFees and conditions\\n\\n\\nWestern Union processing fee: A $10 USD fee is deducted from each Western Union transaction to cover processing costs.\\n\\nMinimum payout amount: A minimum payout of $60 USD is required before your payout will be sent.\\n\\nMaximum payout amount: The maximum Western Union transaction amount is $2000 USD. If your payout is more than $2000 USD, it\\u2019s divided into several smaller transactions. Western Union can\\u2019t process identical sums on the same day, so if you have a payout of $4000 or more, only $2000 can be processed per day.\\n\\nCurrency and exchange rate: Western Union payouts are sent in USD. Western Union sets any exchange rates between USD and your local currency.\\n\\nAdditional fees: Additional fees may be required by the local government. These are not set or charged by Airbnb.\\n", "question": "I'm a host. Will Airbnb send payouts through Western Union?"},
{"answer": "Our Guest Refund Policy and Hospitality Standards help protect guests from things from things like last-minute host cancellations, lock-outs, and listings that are misrepresented, unsanitary, or lacking in promised amenities or items. If you don\\u2019t meet one or more of our Hospitality Standards, Airbnb may require you to refund a guest.", "question": "Do I have to refund my guests when they make a complaint?"},
{"answer": "\\n        \\n          \\n        Never pay for your reservation outside of Airbnb. If someone asks you to pay for a reservation outside our on-site payment system, report it to us\\u2014just look for the flag icon  in your message thread. Learn more.\\n        \\n  \\n\\n\\n        If you're a host, Airbnb can send you your payouts through international wire transfer. An international wire (or international wire transfer) is an electronic payment service for transferring funds. A wire transfer is considered international when Airbnb sends funds in a currency different from your local currency from a bank outside your country.\\n        Your bank may charge a fee to receive a foreign currency. If the funds are transferred using an intermediate bank, the intermediate bank may also deduct fees from the payout. Airbnb can't inform you on how much you'll be charged to receive an international wire. In addition, Airbnb is not responsible for any fees deducted during the international wire, by your bank, or by the intermediary bank.\\n        \\n            If you're a host and want to receive your payouts via international wire, please enter your local banking information in your payout preferences, even if your bank works with a specific intermediary bank. Airbnb's bank will take care of processing the international wire without the intermediary bank information.", "question": "I'm a host. Can Airbnb send my payouts by international wire transfer?"},
{"answer": "We've heard from hosts around the world that sometimes they'd like a little extra help with their listing. There are times when they'd love to have someone they trust, like a family member or friend, help out with messaging, check in, and more.\\n\\nFollowing extensive research into a number of ways we can help, we\\u2019ll be introducing a new feature that allows current hosts to add an additional host to their account. This is a simple and secure way to allow a family member or trusted friend to help with some of the hosting responsibilities. \\n \\n\\nThis feature will be available soon.", "question": "What can my additional hosts do?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\n\\n\\tSetting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set. \\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\tTo set a minimum payout amount:\\n\\n\\n\\n    Go to Account on airbnb.com\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tSelect Payout Preferences on the left\\n\\t\\n\\t  Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tSelect Set Minimum Payout Amount\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tEnter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tFor most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "Depending on when your guest canceled a reservation, you can refund them from their reservation on airbnb.com, or through the Resolution Center. \\n  \\n\\nGuest canceled before check-in date\\nIf your guest canceled the reservation before the check-in date, you can give them an additional refund beyond what the cancellation policy provides by going to Your reservations and clicking the Issue Refund button. \\nGuest canceled after check-in date\\n\\nIf your guest canceled the reservation after the check-in date, you can issue a refund to your guest in our Resolution Center:\\n\\nGo to the Resolution Center on airbnb.com\\nChoose the reservation you want to refund\\nUnder Select a Reason, choose Offer Partial Reimbursement \\nEnter the desired amount, currency, and a message to your guest\\n\\n\\nAfter you send the details, your guest will be notified and can choose to accept or decline the offer. If the offer has been accepted, we\\u2019ll process your transaction within 48 hours. You\\u2019ll be notified once the transaction is complete.\\n\\nOnce you submit the refund amount, the transaction is considered final. To ask your guest for any money back, you will need to submit a new request using the Resolution Center.\\n\\nService fees\\nAirbnb service fees are non-refundable for guests. However, your 3% host fee will be adjusted according to your final reservation total after the refund.", "question": "How do I refund my guest?"},
{"answer": "Soon, you'll be able to add a family member or trusted friend so they can help you with your listing from their own account. \\n \\n To add an additional host by (when available):\\n \\n  Go to Manage listings\\n  Select Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\n  Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\n  Under Management, select Additional Hosts\\n", "question": "How can I add an additional host?"},
{"answer": "To help you decide where to stay, you can search by neighborhood for a number of cities.\\nTo search by neighborhood:\\n\\n  Search for a city on airbnb.com.\\n    Under the price range slider, click More Filters.\\n  Next to the Neighborhoods section, choose a neighborhood you want to search. If you don\\u2019t see this section, that city doesn\\u2019t have any neighborhoods recorded on Airbnb.\\n\\nYou can also browse neighborhoods by clicking different locations on the map.\\n\\nHow do I know which neighborhood to choose?\\nIf you\\u2019re not sure which neighborhood is the best fit for your trip, you can use the Neighborhoods page for your destination to get a description of each neighborhood based on research with locals and city experts.\\nIn the Airbnb app, you can also provide extra information about your trip to see more personalized homes and neighborhoods. You can choose filters such as property type (for example, apartment or castle) and neighborhood type (for example, \\u201chip\\u201d or \\u201cquiet\\u201d). You can also indicate if you\\u2019re traveling with any children or pets. Using this information, along with a number of other search and ranking factors, we\\u2019ll display neighborhoods and homes for your specific trip, as well as \\u201cPopular\\u201d listings based on our existing ranking factors.\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nWhat are Neighborhoods?\\nHow can I edit my neighborhood?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I search by neighborhood?"},
{"answer": "We've heard from hosts around the world that sometimes they'd like a little extra help with their listing. There are times when they'd love to have someone they trust, like a family member or friend, help out with messaging, check in, and more.\\n\\nFollowing extensive research into a number of ways we can help, we\\u2019ll be introducing a new feature that allows current hosts to add an additional host to their account. This is a simple way to allow a family member or trusted friend to help with some of the hosting responsibilities, without giving someone access to their personal account. \\n \\n\\nThis feature will be available soon.", "question": "What are additional hosts?"},
{"answer": "Neighborhoods are a way to help travelers make informed decisions about where to stay when planning a trip. When visiting a new city, it can be helpful to know which neighborhoods may fit your interests and the purpose of your trip.\\nHow neighborhoods are determined\\nOn Airbnb, neighborhoods boundaries are based on research with locals and city experts. A cartographer helps make sure these boundaries are accurate and up-to-date. This research also informs the detailed descriptions, photos, and stories about each neighborhood.\\nSearch by neighborhood\\nYou can search by neighborhood to narrow your options when looking for a listing. You can also get additional information about neighborhoods, such as location, access to transportation, and map, by  browsing all available neighborhoods for the city you're interested in.\\nGive direct feedback or suggest changes\\nNeighborhood information is updated partly by using feedback from the community. If you feel that neighborhood information is incorrect, you can give us direct feedback. While we can\\u2019t respond to everything, we encourage you to share your knowledge and opinions because the Neighborhoods team uses feedback to improve our platform.\\nCan\\u2019t find a neighborhood\\nWhile we\\u2019ve recently updated neighborhood information for popular travel destinations worldwide, not all locations have neighborhoods on Airbnb.\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I search by neighborhood?\\nHow do I edit my neighborhood?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What are Neighborhoods?"},
{"answer": "If you want to see if a space would allow you to bring a pet on your trip, you can check the Amenities section of the listing description or contact the host.\\nCheck the amenities\\nEach listing on the site includes a section for amenities. Under the Amenities section below the listing description, check to see if  Pets Allowed is listed. If you don\\u2019t see it, or it\\u2019s crossed out, it means the host doesn\\u2019t allow guests to bring their pets along on their trip. This includes service animals.\\nContact the host\\nWhether or not the listing says that pets are allowed, you should contact the host to double check. In some situations, they may be willing to make exceptions. But sometimes allergies are an issue, so many hosts can\\u2019t accept pets.\\nPets already at the listing\\nIf you want to know if the hosts have a pet at the listing, you can also check In the  Amenities section of the listing. If you see  Pet Owner  listed, that means the host has a pet on the premises, although it doesn\\u2019t necessarily mean that a guest can bring a pet. Contact the host with any questions about pets at the listing.", "question": "How can I tell if a listing is pet-friendly?"},
{"answer": "As long as you enter your destination, travel dates, and number of dates when searching on Airbnb, all listings that appear should be available for your trip.\\nWhile we strongly encourage all hosts to keep their calendars up to date, consider sending a message to hosts to double check that their home is still available. You can also message the host to ask them about other details about their space you are wondering about.\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nHow do I book a place on Airbnb?\\nHow do I search for listings?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nWhat is Instant Book?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I know if a listing is available?"},
{"answer": "When you search for a place to stay on Airbnb, you can narrow your options by using filters and reading the descriptions of places to check if they\\u2019d be a good fit for your trip.\\n  To search for a place to stay:\\n  \\n    On airbnb.com, enter your destination, travel dates, and number of guests.\\n        Click Search.\\n    If you want, use the filters (for example, price range) to narrow your options. Click More Filters to see all available filters.\\n    Scroll through the listings or use the map to find listings in the location you want.\\n    Click on a listing to open it. To learn more about it, read the description, check the available amenities, review the House Rules, and see reviews that other guests have left for the host.\\n    If you have any questions, send the host a message. Or, if you\\u2019re ready to book, request to book the listing (or use Instant Book if the host has it turned on).\\n  \\n    \\nYou can also save your favorite places to a Wish List, which you can save for later or share with your friends.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I use search filters?\\nWhat are house rules?\\nHow do reviews work?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nWhat is Instant Book?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I search for listings?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tHosts on Airbnb offer a wide variety of spaces, ranging from shared rooms to private islands.\\n\\n\\tWhile you can filter searches to look for something more specific (like boats or castles), all listings are grouped into the following three room types:\\n\\t\\n\\t  Shared rooms\\n\\t  \\t  Private rooms\\n\\t  Entire homes/apartments\\n\\t\\n\\tShared rooms\\n\\n\\tShared rooms are for when you\\u2019d like a comfy, communal experience, and don't mind sharing a space with others. When you book a shared room, you'll be sharing your bedroom and the entire space with other people. These rooms work best for the flexible traveler looking for new friends and a budget-friendly stay.\\n\\tPrivate rooms\\n\\nPrivate rooms are great for when you prefer a little privacy, but still value a local connection. When you book a private room, you'll have a bedroom to yourself, but will share some spaces with others. With a private room, you'll be able to wake up to greet your new friends in the kitchen and have the freedom to bid them adieu at bedtime.\\n\\tEntire homes/apartments\\n\\nEntire homes/apartments are best if you're seeking a home away from home with complete privacy and the freedom to cook breakfast in your pajamas. With an entire home/apartment, you'll have the whole space to yourself. You can be your own host, make your own dinner, and remember to treat your listing with the respect and courtesy you would at your own home.", "question": "What does the room type of a listing mean?"},
{"answer": "To keep track of listings you\\u2019re thinking of booking, or simply find fun and inspiring spaces, you can create a wish list.\\n\\nCreate a wish list\\n\\nFrom a listing page:\\n\\nOn a listing you want to add to a wishlist, click Save to Wish List under the pricing details\\nClick the drop-down menu &gt; Create new\\nGive your new wish list a name (for example, \\u201cLos Angeles Trip\\u201d or \\u201cRomantic Getaway\\u201d) and choose whether to keep the wish list private or public\\nClick Save\\n\\nTo add more listings to this wish list, click Save to Wish List on a listing page and choose your wish list.\\nNote: New wish lists may take a couple minutes to show up on the website.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I manage my wish list?\\nHow do I search for listings?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I create a wish list?"},
{"answer": "If you want to narrow down your choices when looking for a place to stay, you can use search filters.\\nDescriptions for filters\\nFor the most accurate results, always start your search by choosing your destination, number of guests, and dates.\\nOther filters are available as well, some of which can be found by selecting More Filters below the filters that are showing.\\n\\n    Room type: Choose the type of space you'd like to book, for example a shared room or an entire home.\\n        Price: Use the sliding scale to find listings in your price range.\\n    Size: Pick the number of bedrooms, bathrooms, or beds you need.\\n    Instant Book: Find places that you can book instantly.\\n    Neighborhoods: Choose the parts of town that interest you the most, if available. For detailed information on some popular cities, check out our Neighborhood guides.\\n    Amenities: Select the amenities you want for your stay, for example breakfast or a hot tub.\\n    Property type: Find a specific type of space, like a treehouse, cabin, or even an igloo!\\n    Host Language: Choose hosts who speak a language you're comfortable with.\\n  \\n  \\n  Note: At this time, there is no way to search using keywords.", "question": "How do I use search filters?"},
{"answer": "When you book a place on Airbnb, you\\u2019re making arrangements to stay in someone\\u2019s home. Each host has their own style of hospitality, starting with how they like to get to know their guests. Some hosts want to approve reservations, while others are comfortable letting you book their place instantly without waiting for approval.\\n\\n1. Complete Your Profile\\nIn either case, it\\u2019s important to know that Airbnb is a community that relies on trust. Complete your profile before you request a reservation with a host, so they can know a little bit about you when they confirm. Your profile should include photos and verifications, especially because some hosts require guests to have a profile photo or Verified ID in order to book.\\n2. Find the Right Place\\nWith over 800,000 unique listings around the world, you\\u2019ll want to make sure the place you choose has everything you need for a comfortable and memorable trip.\\nWhen searching for a place, make sure to include your dates and number of guests to get the most accurate pricing. Read reviews, descriptions, house rules, and amenities for each place to see if it\\u2019s the right fit for your trip. You can always contact the host if you have any questions about their home.\\n3. Book It!\\nYou\\u2019ve found the perfect place, and now it\\u2019s time to make it official. This is where the host\\u2019s preferred way of booking will determine how you\\u2019ll confirm your reservation.\\nInstant Book\\nFor hosts who don\\u2019t want to approve each reservation, you\\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Instant Book. Like the name suggests, you can confirm a reservation at these places right away. Learn more about Instant Book.\\nRequest to Book\\nMany hosts prefer to approve reservations before they\\u2019re final. In this case, you\\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Request to Book. To submit a reservation request, you\\u2019ll need to enter your payment details. Hosts have 24 hours to accept your request, and your reservation is automatically confirmed once they do. Learn more about submitting a reservation request.\\nPre-approvals and Special Offers\\nIf you decide to contact the host to ask questions before attempting to book, the host may respond to your message by inviting you to make a reservation with either a pre-approval or Special Offer. A pre-approval is an invitation to finish booking for the dates and number of guests you noted in your message. A Special Offer gives the host the opportunity to provide special pricing, dates, and other reservation details before you book. Learn more about booking a pre-approval or Special Offer.", "question": "How do I book a place on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy.\\nThere are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:\\n\\n  Private messaging\\n    Profile verifications\\n  Reviews\\n  Verified photography\\n\\nHosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nWhy should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nWhat are profile verifications?\\nHow do reviews work?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "Yes. If the request hasn\\u2019t been accepted by the host, you can cancel the request and send a new one with the updated reservation details. \\n    \\n      To change a reservation request:\\n\\n  Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n  Find your reservation request under Pending Trips\\n  Click Cancel Request and then OK to confirm\\n  If you want, send a new request with your changed dates or number of guests\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nChange a confirmed reservation as a guest\\nChange a confirmed reservation as a host\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Can I make changes to a pending reservation request?"},
{"answer": "If you\\u2019ve submitted a reservation request with a host on Airbnb, a couple of things are required to confirm your reservation:\\n    \\n      You\\u2019ve added your payment information\\n      The host accepts your request (unless you sent a reservation request for a place with Instant Book turned on, which will automatically accept the request)\\n    \\n    When a host accepts your request, you'll receive an email and, depending on your account notification settings, a text (SMS) and push notification from Airbnb. Your reservation request status will also change to Accepted.\\n    Check your reservation status\\n    To check your reservation status from your computer:\\n        \\n          Your Trips: Pending and declined reservations show their status, and you can see if a reservation is accepted if you see the option to \\u201cChange Reservation\\u201d\\n            Your Inbox: Look for the status next to each message thread\\n        \\n    Read more about what each reservation status means or how to make reservation requests.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I submit a reservation request?\\nWhat does each reservation status mean?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I check if my reservation is confirmed?"},
{"answer": "If your reservation request is declined by the host or expires, meaning the host didn\\u2019t respond within 24 hours, no charge is made for the reservation and you\\u2019re free to book with another host.\\nWe urge our hosts to keep their calendars up to date and respond to requests in a timely manner. But, sometimes situations come up that prevent this from happening.\\nWe recommend messaging several hosts before submitting a reservation request to ask about their availability and ask any other questions you have.\\nTemporary authorizations\\nYour payment method may be temporarily authorized for a charge when you request a reservation, but this authorization is voided and released back to the payment method if your request is declined or expires. We complete a charge only when a reservation request is confirmed.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nShould I book if I have not heard back from the host?\\nHow do I check if my reservation is confirmed?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nWhat does my reservation status mean?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What happens if my reservation request is declined or expires?"},
{"answer": "Once you've created a wish list to keep track of listings you like, you can share it with others, add and remove listings, or delete the wish list altogether.\\n\\nShare a wish list\\nYou can share a wish list with the people you want to travel with and allow them to add listings and notes to the list.\\n\\nOn airbnb.com, go to Wish Lists.\\nAt the top of the page, choose My Wish Lists.\\nOpen your wish list.\\nAt the top of the list, click the plus button.\\nAdd the email addresses for the people you want to plan with and add a note.\\nClick Send Invites.\\n\\nTo remove someone from the wish list, hover over their profile picture in the wish list and click Remove.\\n\\n  The people you\\u2019ve shared with can now add and remove listings on the wish list and make comments on the existing listings.\\n\\n\\n\\nRemove a listing from a wish list\\n\\nOn airbnb.com, go to Wish Lists\\nAt the top of the page, choose My Wish Lists\\nOpen your wish list\\nHover over the listing you want to remove and click Remove\\n\\n\\n\\nDelete a wish list\\n\\nOn airbnb.com, go to Wish Lists\\nAt the top of the page, choose My Wish Lists\\nOpen the wish list you want to delete\\nNext to the name of the wish list at the top, click Edit\\nOn the right, click Delete Wish List &gt; OK\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I create a wish list?\\nHow do I search for listings?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I manage my wish list?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tHosts have 24 hours to officially accept or decline reservation requests. You'll be updated by email about the status of your request.\\n\\n\\tMore than half of all reservation requests are accepted within one hour of being received. The vast majority of hosts reply within 12 hours.\\n\\n\\tIf a host confirms your request, your payment is processed and collected by Airbnb in full. If a host declines your request or the request expires, we don't process your payment.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I check if my reservation is confirmed?\\nShould I book if I have not heard back from the host?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How much time does a host have to respond to my reservation request?"},
{"answer": "As long as your reservation hasn\\u2019t been accepted by the host, you can cancel the reservation. You won\\u2019t be charged for the reservation or Airbnb service fees.\\n\\n  But, if you cancel after the reservation has been accepted, your reservation will be subject to the terms of the cancellation policy selected by the host.\\n\\nSee how to check the status of a reservation request.\\nCancel a pending reservation request\\n\\n    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n    On the reservation request you\\u2019d like to cancel, click Cancel Request\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I check if a reservation is confirmed?\\nWhat is a cancellation policy?\\nHow do I cancel a reservation as a guest?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I cancel a reservation request?"},
{"answer": "\\nNo\\u2014if your reservation request isn\\u2019t accepted by the host or expires without a response, there\\u2019s no cost for the reservation or any Airbnb service fees.\\n\\nDepending on your payment method, you may see a temporary authorization or a refunded charge after a reservation request is declined or expires.\\n\\nTemporary authorizations and refunded charges\\n\\nBefore you submit a reservation request, you'll see whether your chosen payment method will place a hold (called an authorization) or charge on your account for the amount of the reservation.\\n\\nIf your payment method is authorized\\n\\nSome payment methods or locations require that the full amount of the reservation is authorized at the time of your request. If your reservation is accepted, the authorization will turn into a real charge and the amount will be deducted from your payment account.\\n\\nIf the reservation request is declined or expires, you\\u2019ll either see the authorization disappear altogether or appear as a refund in your payment account. Depending on the processing time of your bank, the release of the authorization may take up to 7 business days.\\n\\nIf your payment method is charged\\n\\nSome payment methods or locations require that the full amount of the reservation is charged at the time of your request. If your reservation request is accepted, the charge remains and your reservation is confirmed.\\n\\nIf the reservation request is declined or expires, you\\u2019ll be refunded immediately and automatically. Depending on the processing time of your bank, the refund may take up to 10 calendar days to process.\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nWhen do I pay for a reservation?\\nHow do I pay for my reservation?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Do I have to pay if my reservation request isn't accepted by the host?"},
{"answer": "\\nOnce you\\u2019ve found a listing for your trip, we recommend messaging the host to doublecheck the availability of the space for your dates.\\nMessage the host before requesting\\n\\nUnless you have found an Instant Book listing, you\\u2019ll have to request that the host accept your stay. It\\u2019s a good idea to message the host before requesting, since they can answer questions about their home, as well as let you know it\\u2019s available.\\n\\n\\tTo contact a host from the listing page, click Contact Host and ask the host any questions you have. Most hosts respond within a few hours. Keep in mind that you may be in different time zones or the host may not have Internet access at the moment.\\n\\tThe host isn\\u2019t responding\\n\\nIf a host hasn't responded, consider reaching out to other hosts in the area. You can message as many hosts as you'd like, so it's up to them to respond to you in a timely fashion or risk losing their chance at having you as a guest. \\nSending multiple requests\\nUnless you're planning on renting multiple locations for the same dates, make sure you don\\u2019t submit more than one reservation request at a time, as you may end up booking multiple reservations during the same time period.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I submit a reservation request?\\nHow do I cancel a reservation request?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?"},
{"answer": "If you\\u2019re ready to book a place on Airbnb, you can send a request to the host to book a reservation. If you\\u2019re unsure about the listing or its availability, you can also send a message to the host.\\nTo send a reservation request:\\n\\n  On a listing, click Request to Book.\\n   If you see Instant Book, the host is allowing you to book their place instantly. Your reservation will be automatically confirmed after step 4.\\n    Review your reservation details to make sure everything is correct.\\n  Add your payment information, including any coupon code you may have.\\n  Agree to the policies and terms, including the host\\u2019s cancellation policy and house rules.\\n  Wait for the host\\u2019s response. The host has 24 hours to reply, but most reply within a few hours.\\n\\nSome hosts require that you complete the Verified ID process before confirming a reservation, which allows the host to get more information about who they\\u2019re hosting in their home.\\nIf your request is accepted, you\\u2019ll be charged in full for the reservation. If the host declines the request or doesn\\u2019t respond within 24 hours, no charge is made and you can try booking those dates with someone else.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nHow do I use a coupon code?\\nWhen do I pay for a reservation?\\nHow do I check if my reservation is confirmed?\\nWhat happens if my reservation request is declined or expires?\\nWhat is Instant Book?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I submit a reservation request?"},
{"answer": "You\\u2019ll be charged for the total cost of your reservation when it's confirmed, which happens as soon as:\\n\\n\\n  You\\u2019ve added your payment information\\n    Your host accepts your request (or the request is accepted immediately with Instant Book)\\n\\n\\nRegardless of how far in advance your reservation is booked, we hold the payment for the host until 24 hours after check-in to make sure everything goes smoothly.\\n\\nLong term reservations\\n\\nFor reservations that are 28 nights or longer, you\\u2019ll be charged the first month\\u2019s payment when the host confirms the reservation. You\\u2019ll then be charged a recurring monthly payment during your reservation. In other words, you won't make a second payment until one month after you check in.\\n\\nSecurity deposits\\n\\nIf you make a reservation with a host who asks for a security deposit, you won\\u2019t be charged on the deposit unless a host makes a successful claim against the deposit after your trip.\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nHow do I check if a reservation is confirmed?\\nHow do I pay for my reservation?\\nHow do I pay for my long term reservation?\\nHow does Airbnb handle security deposits?\\nWhat is a payment authorization?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "When will I be charged?"},
{"answer": "If you want to see the status of your reservation, you can find your status in your Inbox on the right side of the message thread with the guest or host.\\nOnce you\\u2019ve found your status, you can see the details of the status below.\\nReservation statuses\\nInquiry: A guest sent a message to a host about certain dates, but hasn't submitted a reservation request. In response, the host can send a message, pre-approve, send a Special Offer, or decline the dates of the inquiry.\\nReservation Request: A guest sent a message to a host by submitting a booking request for specific dates. In response, the host will need to either accept or decline the request within 24 hours before it expires.\\nPending: A guest is waiting for a host to respond to a reservation request. The host has 24 hours to respond before the request expires.\\nConfirmed: A host accepted a guest's reservation request or the request was accepted automatically with Instant Book. Airbnb has collected full payment from the guest and the booking is complete.\\nDeclined: A host declined a guest's reservation request. No charge is made to the guest.\\nExpired: A host took more than 24 hours to respond to a pending reservation request. If the host wants to accommodate the expired request, the host will have to send a pre-approval or Special Offer, or the guest will need to send another reservation request.\\nCanceled: A host or guest canceled a confirmed reservation.\\nPre-Approval: A guest has contacted the host about specific dates and the host has responded by inviting them to book the dates. If the guest accepts the pre-approval request within 24 hours, their reservation will be confirmed.\\nSpecial Offer: A guest has contacted the host about specific dates and the host has responded by inviting them to book the dates with a different price than what is listed on their calendar. If the guest accepts the special offer within 24 hours, their reservation will be confirmed.\\nAwaiting Payment: A host chose to accept a guest's reservation request, but the guest's payment didn\\u2019t go through. The guest has 24 hours to successfully update their payment information for the reservation to be accepted. Otherwise, the reservation will be canceled without penalty.\\nAction Required: A guest submitted a reservation request to a host who requires they complete Verified ID, and they haven't completed the process yet. The request is on hold until Verified ID has been confirmed.\\nClosed: The guest is no longer looking for a place to stay for the dates they requested.\\nNot Possible: A guest contacted a host about specific dates and the host responded with a Special Offer or pre-approval, but some or all of the dates are no longer available on the host's calendar.", "question": "What does each reservation status mean?"},
{"answer": "Messaging on Airbnb starts when a guest makes an inquiry or reservation request. Afterward, all messages related to that inquiry or reservation request will appear in your inbox.\\nView or send a message\\n        \\n            On airbnb.com, go to your Messages\\n            In your inbox, you'll see a message thread for each inquiry or reservation. \\n            Click on a message thread to view old messages or send a new one.\\n        \\n        You must be logged in to your Airbnb account to view or send messages, and you can only send 30 messages within any 24-hour period.\\n    \\n     \\n    To remove a message from your inbox\\n        \\n          \\n            Go to your Messages\\n            In your inbox, you'll see a message thread for each inquiry or reservation. \\n            Hover over the message thread you'd like to remove and select Archive.\\n        \\nIf a message makes you feel uncomfortable or someone tries to get you to pay outside Airbnb, click the  next to it to let us know.\\nMessage Threads\\nWhen you click on a message, you can view the conversation and also the following information:\\n\\n  Host or guest profiles including number of reviews, verifications, and description.\\n  Reservation and payment details such as date of inquiry, number of guests, and price breakdown.\\n  Events such as reservation confirmation, pre-approvals, and special offers are notated in the timeline of the conversations.\\n  If any actions are needed from you, you\\u2019ll see the prompt at the top of the page, above the conversation. Guests can make booking inquiries or reservation requests, and hosts will be able to accept or decline requests. \\n   Hosts will see what the guest pays and what they will earn. They will also be able to see a snapshot of their calendar.\\n", "question": "How do I view and send messages?"},
{"answer": "Yes. Some hosts require guests to sign contracts or rental agreements prior to check-in.\\nFor hosts\\nIf you require guests to sign a contract, you must disclose the actual contract terms to them prior to booking. The easiest way to do this is to mention the contract in your listing's description, and include the terms in your message thread with the guest.\\nAirbnb can't help enforce any special policies in your contract.\\nFor guests\\nHosts may ask you to sign a contract, but they must disclose this requirement and its terms prior to booking.\\nIf you\\u2019re not comfortable with the contract, you may want to discuss your concerns with the host or look for another place to stay.\\nIf your host asks you to sign a contract that you weren\\u2019t notified about before you made the reservation, you can decline to sign the contract and ask your host to cancel your reservation instead.", "question": "Can hosts ask guests to sign a contract?"},
{"answer": "\\nOnce you\\u2019ve found a listing for your trip, we recommend messaging the host to doublecheck the availability of the space for your dates.\\nMessage the host before requesting\\n\\nUnless you have found an Instant Book listing, you\\u2019ll have to request that the host accept your stay. It\\u2019s a good idea to message the host before requesting, since they can answer questions about their home, as well as let you know it\\u2019s available.\\n\\n\\tTo contact a host from the listing page, click Contact Host and ask the host any questions you have. Most hosts respond within a few hours. Keep in mind that you may be in different time zones or the host may not have Internet access at the moment.\\n\\tThe host isn\\u2019t responding\\n\\nIf a host hasn't responded, consider reaching out to other hosts in the area. You can message as many hosts as you'd like, so it's up to them to respond to you in a timely fashion or risk losing their chance at having you as a guest. \\nSending multiple requests\\nUnless you're planning on renting multiple locations for the same dates, make sure you don\\u2019t submit more than one reservation request at a time, as you may end up booking multiple reservations during the same time period.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I submit a reservation request?\\nHow do I cancel a reservation request?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Should I book if I have not heard back from the host?"},
{"answer": "If you\\u2019re having trouble getting in touch with your host after you\\u2019ve made a reservation, consider a few things:\\n\\n  Most hosts respond within a few hours.\\n    We recommend giving the host a few days to respond. Sometimes things come up or your host might be on a different schedule from you.\\n  Try contacting your host using a different form of communication. For example, you can try reaching them through:\\n  \\n    Airbnb message: Find your host in your Messages and send them a note.  \\n\\nEmail or phone: Go to Your Trips, click View Itinerary next to your reservation, and use the email address or phone number listed. \\n          \\n  \\n  \\n      If your trip is starting or about to start, contact us.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\n  How do I contact a host?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nHow do I contact Airbnb?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What if I can't get in touch with my host?"},
{"answer": "We encourage all hosts and guests to complete their bookings through our website before meeting in person to best ensure their safety and privacy.\\nThere are many ways to learn more about the listing and the host without seeing the property, including:\\n\\n  Private messaging\\n    Profile verifications\\n  Reviews\\n  Verified photography\\n\\nHosts also need to provide information about themselves before accepting reservations on the site.\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nWhy should I pay and communicate only through Airbnb?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nWhat are profile verifications?\\nHow do reviews work?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Can I view a listing before I book?"},
{"answer": "It's up to each Airbnb host to decide whether or not to allow infants or children in their space during a reservation.\\n\\nLook for Family/Kid Friendly listings\\nIf a host adds Family/Kid Friendly as an amenity, this implies that infants, children, and families are welcome in their listing. You'll still need to disclose the total number of guests, including infants and children, accurately when making a reservation request.\\n\\nYou can also ask questions or clarify the details of your trip with your host by clicking Contact Host before submitting a reservation request. For example, if your host charges an extra guest fee, you may want to check if the fee applies to infants or children traveling with you.\\n\\nYou must be 18 or older to create an account\\nIn order to use the Airbnb site and services, you must be 18 years or older. It's against our Terms of Service to create an account to travel or host unless you're at least 18 years old.", "question": "Can children travel on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "If you want to contact a host before booking a reservation or after a trip, send them a message on Airbnb. Once a trip is confirmed, you can message, email, or call the host to communicate until the trip has ended.\\nBefore booking a reservation\\nIf you want to find out more about a listing or host before booking a reservation, you can message the host on Airbnb. Make sure to review the listing page (for example, reviews and amenities) to clarify anything you need from the host.\\nTo send a message:\\n\\n  On airbnb.com, go to the listing for the host you want to contact.\\n    Click Contact Host on the listing page.\\n  Enter the dates and number of guests for your trip. You can adjust this information before booking.\\n  Write your message and click Send Message.\\n\\n\\nFor your safety and privacy, you can\\u2019t call or email hosts before your reservation is accepted. Learn more about why it\\u2019s good to keep communication and transactions on Airbnb.\\nOnce a trip is confirmed\\nIf you have an accepted reservation, you can call or email the host, or message them on the site to communicate about your trip.\\nYou can find the host\\u2019s email and phone number in the message thread for your trip, where you can also send the host a message.\\n\\nAfter a trip\\nAfter a trip, you can send a message to your host in your Inbox if you have anything you need to follow up with them about.\\nIf you have any issues that you need to resolve, you can work through payment issues in the Resolution Center on the site.\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\n  What if I can't get in touch with my host?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nWhat is the Resolution Center?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I contact a host?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are experienced hosts who provide a shining example for other hosts, and extraordinary experiences for their guests.\\n\\nOnce a host reaches Superhost status, a badge will automatically appear on their listing and profile to help you identify them.\\n\\n\\n\\nWe check Superhosts\\u2019 activity four times a year, to ensure that the program highlights the people who are most dedicated to providing outstanding hospitality.\\n\\nThe Superhost Terms &amp; Conditions apply. Airbnb doesn't endorse or sponsor any host, including Superhosts, or their listings.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\n  How do I become a Superhost?\\n  What benefits do Superhosts receive?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is a Superhost?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests. \\nA host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation. \\n\\nThe Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nCancel a reservation as a guest\\nCancel a reservation as a host\\nWhat happens if my guest cancels a reservation?\\nWhat to do if your host cancels\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "Amex Express Checkout\\n\\n\\nWith Amex Express Checkout, eligible American Express Card Members who have an americanexpress.com account can complete bookings quickly and send information securely to Airbnb.\\n\\nOn the payment page, select Amex Express Checkout as your Payment type and enter your americanexpress.com User ID and Password in the Amex Express Checkout pop-up window. After you confirm your card information with Airbnb, American Express will share your card and billing information with Airbnb in order to process the booking.\\n\\nIf you have an eligible card to use American Express Membership Rewards points for your booking, you\\u2019ll see the option to use points. When you\\u2019re ready, submit your reservation request.\\n \\nAmerican Express Membership Rewards points\\n\\n\\nTo use points for all or a portion of your Airbnb reservation, you need an American Express Card enrolled in the US Membership Rewards program that\\u2019s active, in good standing and authorized to use points.  View eligible American Express Cards here.\\n\\nWhen you choose to pay with an eligible card, the maximum dollar value in points available for the booking will display. You can choose to apply the entire dollar value of points available, or enter the amount you prefer to use. To confirm your use of points, click Apply to Booking.\\n\\nWhether you use Membership Rewards points to for all or a portion of your booking, your American Express Card will be charged for the total amount of the reservation, and the dollar amount used in Membership Rewards points will appear as a statement credit on your card account in 2-4 business days.\\n\\nIf you\\u2019re issued a refund on a booking that used Membership Rewards points, we\\u2019ll credit the dollar amount of the refund to the American Express Card that you used. Please allow 2-4 days for the refund to post to your American Express Card billing statement. If you\\u2019d like to have points reinstated instead, please contact Amex Membership Rewards program Customer Care at 1-800-297-3276.\\n\\nFor questions about Amex Express Checkout and American Express Membership Rewards eligibility, or for more information about this program, visit amex.co/AirbnbFAQs.", "question": "Amex Express Checkout and American Express Membership Rewards\\xae points"},
{"answer": "After you\\u2019ve booked a reservation, you can add guest names and a business address to your billing receipt. Once the reservation ends, you won\\u2019t be able to make any changes to the receipt.\\n Information like passport numbers, birthdates, and tax identification numbers can\\u2019t be added to a receipt.\\n Add guest names\\n To add guest names to your receipt, you have to update the names on your itinerary.\\n \\n   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n      Next to the trip you want to edit, click View Itinerary\\n   Next to Guests, click Manage Guests\\n   Add or remove names of the other guests staying at the listing\\n   The names are automatically updated on the billing receipt\\n \\n \\n\\n Add a business address\\n  \\n \\n   Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n      Next to the trip you want to edit, click View Itinerary\\n   Next to Billing, click Detailed Receipt\\n   On the receipt, click Add billing details\\n   Add the business address and other relevant information\\n   Click Save\\n \\n Note: Adding VAT details to your business information is documentation only and won't affect VAT charged on your reservation. VAT invoices can't be changed. Learn more about how VAT may apply to you.\\n \\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I find my trip itinerary or receipt?\\nWhat is Airbnb for Business?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How can I add a guest or business address to my receipt?"},
{"answer": "When you book a place on Airbnb, you\\u2019re making arrangements to stay in someone\\u2019s home. Each host has their own style of hospitality, starting with how they like to get to know their guests. Some hosts want to approve reservations, while others are comfortable letting you book their place instantly without waiting for approval.\\n\\n1. Complete Your Profile\\nIn either case, it\\u2019s important to know that Airbnb is a community that relies on trust. Complete your profile before you request a reservation with a host, so they can know a little bit about you when they confirm. Your profile should include photos and verifications, especially because some hosts require guests to have a profile photo or Verified ID in order to book.\\n2. Find the Right Place\\nWith over 800,000 unique listings around the world, you\\u2019ll want to make sure the place you choose has everything you need for a comfortable and memorable trip.\\nWhen searching for a place, make sure to include your dates and number of guests to get the most accurate pricing. Read reviews, descriptions, house rules, and amenities for each place to see if it\\u2019s the right fit for your trip. You can always contact the host if you have any questions about their home.\\n3. Book It!\\nYou\\u2019ve found the perfect place, and now it\\u2019s time to make it official. This is where the host\\u2019s preferred way of booking will determine how you\\u2019ll confirm your reservation.\\nInstant Book\\nFor hosts who don\\u2019t want to approve each reservation, you\\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Instant Book. Like the name suggests, you can confirm a reservation at these places right away. Learn more about Instant Book.\\nRequest to Book\\nMany hosts prefer to approve reservations before they\\u2019re final. In this case, you\\u2019ll see a button on their listing that says Request to Book. To submit a reservation request, you\\u2019ll need to enter your payment details. Hosts have 24 hours to accept your request, and your reservation is automatically confirmed once they do. Learn more about submitting a reservation request.\\nPre-approvals and Special Offers\\nIf you decide to contact the host to ask questions before attempting to book, the host may respond to your message by inviting you to make a reservation with either a pre-approval or Special Offer. A pre-approval is an invitation to finish booking for the dates and number of guests you noted in your message. A Special Offer gives the host the opportunity to provide special pricing, dates, and other reservation details before you book. Learn more about booking a pre-approval or Special Offer.", "question": "How do I book a place on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "\\nBoleto payment is only available for guests in Brazil, and may not be available to all customers at all times. Additionally, Boleto cannot be used for Instant Book listings, for reservations that are longer than 28 nights, or for reservations that start in fewer than 7 days.\\n\\nWhen you submit a reservation request and select Brazil as your country of payment, you\\u2019ll see Boleto Banc\\xe1rio as an option in the payment type menu. Choosing this option will present a form that you\\u2019ll need to complete with your details.\\n\\nAfter the host accepts your reservation, Airbnb will issue a Boleto under your name. You can print it out and pay it through a bank branch, ATM or in a lottery store. Alternatively, you can copy the barcode number and pay via internet banking or through your bank's app on your smartphone. We\\u2019ll email you a copy of the Boleto so you\\u2019ll always have access to it.\\n\\nAfter the Boleto is issued to you, you\\u2019ll have 24 hours to make the payment, and we\\u2019ll confirm it within 96 hours. Your reservation may appear with the status Awaiting Payment for up to 96 hours.\\n\\nPlease keep in mind that this method of payment can take longer if you submit a reservation request on the weekend or within holiday periods.\\n\\nIn case of cancellation, Airbnb will issue a refund and our payment processing partner will send you an email with instructions for how to claim the refund.", "question": "How do I pay for a reservation with Boleto?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tPayPal is available in select countries for guests booking from the desktop version of Airbnb. Click Request to Book to see what methods are available to you. Payment methods differ depending on the country in which your account is located.\\n\\n\\tWhen you submit a reservation request and choose to use PayPal, you'll be redirected to the PayPal website. You'll need to log in to PayPal to make your payment.\\n\\n\\tOnce your payment for the full amount of the reservation is authorized, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply.\\n\\n\\tIf your request is accepted, the authorization on your PayPal account is processed as payment and you'll be able to access your Airbnb billing receipt and trip itinerary.\\n\\n\\tIf your request is retracted, declined, or expires, the authorization on your PayPal account is voided automatically and no charge is made.\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\n  How do I submit a reservation request?\\nHow do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I use PayPal to pay?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tNo, Airbnb can't split your reservation cost across multiple payment methods. To make a reservation, you'll need to make your payment with a single payment method.\\n\\n\\n\\tIf you need to update your payment method for a long-term reservation or an unsuccessful charge, please contact us for assistance.\\n\\t\\n\\n\\tIf you have a confirmed reservation that isn't long-term, remember that you've already paid in full through our payment system\\u2014so you won't need to change or update your payment method to enjoy your trip.", "question": "Can I use more than one payment method to pay for a reservation?"},
{"answer": "\\nIf you choose to pay with a credit card when you make a reservation request, you can edit or remove the credit card information later from your Airbnb account, as long as a default payment method remains. \\n\\nAt this time, it's only possible to add credit cards from the Payment Methods section of your account, although you can choose to add other types of payment methods on the checkout page when you book.\\n\\nRemoving or adding a payment method\\n\\n\\tTo view the credit card information on your Airbnb account:\\n\\nGo to Account on airbnb.com\\nSelect Payment Methods on the left\\n\\n\\n\\nIf you\\u2019ve added more than one credit card as a payment method, you\\u2019ll be able to remove any card that is not your default payment method by clicking Remove. You won\\u2019t be able to remove a card that\\u2019s currently being used on a pending or active reservation.\\n\\n\\tTo have a card appear first on your list of available payment methods the next time you make a reservation, click Set Default.\\n\\n\\nYou can click Add Payment Method to add new credit card information to your account at any time.", "question": "How do I remove credit card information from my Airbnb account?"},
{"answer": "Credit cards can be declined for a number of reasons. Airbnb generally isn't notified of the specific reason.\\n\\nCommon issues   \\n           Check that you're entering your credit card number and billing address correctly, that your card has available funds, and that your card hasn't expired.\\n   \\n   Contact your bank or card issuer        \\nIf you're getting an error when you try to pay, we recommend reaching out to your bank or credit card company for more information. Inform them of the amount  and when tried to make the charge so they can let the transaction go through.\\n\\nIf your bank or card issuer isn't able to help, you may want to try another payment method.", "question": "Why is my credit card getting declined?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tAlipay is available as a payment method for guests in China who are booking Airbnb reservations less than 28 nights long.\\n\\n\\tWhen you submit a reservation request and choose to use Alipay, you'll be redirected to the Alipay website. You'll need to log in to Alipay to make your payment.\\n\\n\\tOnce your payment for the full amount of the reservation is complete, the reservation request is sent to the host, who will have up to 24 hours to reply.\\n\\n\\tIf your request is accepted, you'll be able to access your billing receipt and trip itinerary.\\n\\n\\tIf your request is retracted, declined, or expires, your Alipay account will automatically be refunded in full. Refunds can take up to 3 business days to reflect in your Alipay account.\\n\\t\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\n  How do I submit a reservation request?\\nHow do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I use Alipay to pay?"},
{"answer": "\\nNo. The currency you pay in is controlled by your payment method and, in some cases, by your country. It\\u2019s not possible to manually choose what currency you'll use to pay.\\n\\nWhen you select your country and payment method on the checkout page, the currency in which you'd be charged will be clearly displayed before you confirm your reservation request.\\n\\nExchange rates and currency conversion\\n\\n\\nWhen the currency you\\u2019re paying with is different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we convert your payment automatically.\\n\\nThe base exchange rate uses data from one or more third parties, such as OANDA. It\\u2019s updated regularly, but may not be identical to the real-time market rate. If you\\u2019re paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we also charge a 3% conversion fee on your total cost; the conversion fee accounts for Airbnb\\u2019s holding costs and foreign currency risks.\\n\\nThe exchange rate used will display on the checkout page before you confirm your booking.\\n\\nThird-party fees\\n\\n\\nIf you pay in a currency that\\u2019s different from the designated currency of your payment method, your provider or third-party payment processor may apply a currency conversion rate or fees to your payment. Contact your provider (for example, your credit or bank card issuer) for information on what fees may apply, since they\\u2019re not controlled by Airbnb.\\n\\nCurrency view\\n\\nYou can view Airbnb listings in many currencies, but this won\\u2019t affect what currency you\\u2019ll be asked to pay in. To change your currency view, scroll to the bottom of any page on airbnb.com and click on the currency field to select what currency you want to view listing prices in.", "question": "Can I pay with any currency?"},
{"answer": "\\nWe support several payment methods, which depend on what country your payment account is located in. \\n\\n  You'll see which payment methods are available to you on the checkout page, before you submit a reservation request. After you select your country, all of your payment details will be shown.\\n\\n\\nOffline or cash payments are a violation of our Terms of Service, and can result in removal from Airbnb. We prohibit off-site payments because paying outside of Airbnb makes it harder for us to protect your information and puts you at a greater risk of fraud and other security issues.\\n\\n                Payment options may include:\\n            \\n                \\n                    Major credit cards and pre-paid credit cards (Visa, MasterCard, Amex, Discover, JCB)\\n                \\n                    Many debit cards that can be processed as credit\\n                \\n                    PayPal for select countries\\n                \\n                    Alipay for China only\\n                \\n                    Postepay for Italy only\\n                \\n                    Sofort \\xdcberweisung for Germany only\\n                \\n                    iDEAL for the Netherlands only\\n                \\n                    Boleto Banc\\xe1rio, Hipercard, Elo, and Aura for Brazil only                 \\n                \\n                    Google Wallet for US Android App only\\n                \\n                    Apple Pay for iOS App only\\n            \\n            \\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     When will I be charged?\\n     Can I pay with any currency?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "What methods of payment does Airbnb accept?"},
{"answer": "All pricing information is included when you book a reservation using Airbnb. After paying, there are a few situations where you may owe more money.\\n Know when to pay more\\n You may owe more money if:\\n \\n   You change your reservation \\u2014 for example, you need to add another guest\\n      Your host makes a claim on your security deposit\\n   Your host require taxes to be paid at check-in\\u2014this needs to be clearly stated on the listing prior to booking\\n \\n If a host asks you for more money than what you paid on the site and the extra charge wasn\\u2019t stated in the listing or in the message thread, you can dispute the charges in the Resolution Center. Never pay a host directly for these charges.\\n How to pay after booking the reservation\\n If you need to pay the host more money, use the Resolution Center on the site. You should keep all payment transactions on Airbnb because Airbnb can\\u2019t help with any issues related to off-site or cash payments.\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nWhy should I only pay and communicate through Airbnb?\\nWhat is the Resolution Center?\\nHow do I change a reservation as a guest?\\nWhat happens if a host makes a claim on my security deposit?\\nWhat is occupancy tax?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What if a host asks for more money?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tA pre-approval is a way for host to let guests know that their listing is available when asked about a potential reservation. Once pre-approved, the guest can automatically confirm a booking for the specific dates provided.\\n\\n\\tHosts\\n\\nWhen you pre-approve a guest\\u2019s inquiry, you give them permission to automatically confirm a booking for specific dates. The dates won\\u2019t be blocked on your calendar, so you can pre-approve multiple guests at one time. \\n\\n\\n\\tGuests have 24 hours to confirm a booking that has been pre-approved. After 24 hours, the guest can still request to book your listing with the price offered during the pre-approval, unless you remove the pre-approval. You can remove the pre-approval at any time in the message thread.\\n\\n\\tGuests\\n\\n\\tIf a host has sent you a pre-approval, your booking isn\\u2019t confirmed until you\\u2019ve clicked Book It in the message thread with the host and added your payment information. Hosts can send pre-approvals to many potential guests, so if you\\u2019ve found the perfect space, make sure to complete the booking process as soon as possible. \\nYou have 24 hours to accept a pre-approval before it expires. If 24 hours have passed, you can still accept the pre-approval but your host will have to approve your request before your reservation is confirmed.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I pre-approve a guest\\u2019s stay or remove a pre-approval?\\nHow do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is a pre-approval?"},
{"answer": "If you book a long term reservation that lasts 28 nights or more, you\\u2019ll be charged a first month down payment and the rest will be collected in monthly installments.\\nAt the moment, you can only pay for a long term reservation on a computer.\\nFirst month down payment\\nOnce you\\u2019ve booked a long term reservation, you\\u2019ll be charged for the first month of your stay upfront. We\\u2019ll hold this payment until 24 hours after check-in before giving it to the host.\\nPayment for future months\\nAfter check-in, we\\u2019ll charge you monthly, using the same payment method, for the duration of your reservation. In other words, you won\\u2019t make a second payment until approximately one month after you check in. The monthly price you pay is locked at the beginning of the reservation. \\nYou can see your total reservation cost and successful payments made on your billing receipt.\\nCancellation policy\\nThe Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice of lease termination.", "question": "How do I pay for my long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "\\nNo\\u2014if your reservation request isn\\u2019t accepted by the host or expires without a response, there\\u2019s no cost for the reservation or any Airbnb service fees.\\n\\nDepending on your payment method, you may see a temporary authorization or a refunded charge after a reservation request is declined or expires.\\n\\nTemporary authorizations and refunded charges\\n\\nBefore you submit a reservation request, you'll see whether your chosen payment method will place a hold (called an authorization) or charge on your account for the amount of the reservation.\\n\\nIf your payment method is authorized\\n\\nSome payment methods or locations require that the full amount of the reservation is authorized at the time of your request. If your reservation is accepted, the authorization will turn into a real charge and the amount will be deducted from your payment account.\\n\\nIf the reservation request is declined or expires, you\\u2019ll either see the authorization disappear altogether or appear as a refund in your payment account. Depending on the processing time of your bank, the release of the authorization may take up to 7 business days.\\n\\nIf your payment method is charged\\n\\nSome payment methods or locations require that the full amount of the reservation is charged at the time of your request. If your reservation request is accepted, the charge remains and your reservation is confirmed.\\n\\nIf the reservation request is declined or expires, you\\u2019ll be refunded immediately and automatically. Depending on the processing time of your bank, the refund may take up to 10 calendar days to process.\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nWhen do I pay for a reservation?\\nHow do I pay for my reservation?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Do I have to pay if my reservation request isn't accepted by the host?"},
{"answer": "\\nTo help cover the costs of running Airbnb, we charge guests a service fee every time a reservation is confirmed. The amount of this service fee varies and is based on a percentage of the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes).\\n\\nThe exact amount of the service fee is displayed before guests confirm a booking. Guest service fees are typically 6-12% but can be higher or lower depending on the specifics of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations.\\n\\nWe also charge hosts a host service fee to cover the cost of processing payments.\\nFind the service fee\\nAfter entering the exact dates and number of guests for a reservation, you\\u2019ll see the service fee included as part of the booking details.\\nThe exact amount of the service fee is also located on:\\n\\n  The checkout page before submitting a reservation request\\n  Any guest billing receipt\\n\\nVAT charges on service fees\\nDepending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable.\\nNote: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).\\nTrip cancellations and reservation changes\\nSee the effect on service fees for the following situations:\\n\\n  If a reservation request is retracted, expires or is declined, we don\\u2019t charge the guest a service fee\\n  If a guest cancels a reservation, the service fee charged to the guest is non-refundable\\n  If a guest chooses to be refunded after a host cancellation, the service fee charged to the guest is refunded \\n  If a reservation is changed, the service fee charged to the guest adjusts with to the new subtotal\\n", "question": "What are guest service fees?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount.\\n\\nService fees\\nService fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.\\n\\n\\nGuest service fee \\nWe add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services.\\n\\nThe exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt.\\n\\nIf you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full.\\n\\nHost service fee \\nWe deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments.\\n\\nYou can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb.\\n\\nVAT \\nDepending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable.\\n\\nConversion fee\\n\\nFor guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "The total price of a reservation on Airbnb is based on a few factors. Note that the price is charged in full once a host accepts your reservation request (or if you use Instant Book).\\n   Costs determined by the host:\\n   \\n     Nightly price: Nightly rate decided by the host\\n          Cleaning fee: One-time fee charged by some hosts to cover the cost of cleaning their space\\n     Extra guest fees: One-time fee charged by some hosts to cover other costs related to using their space\\n   \\nCosts determined by Airbnb:\\n\\n  Airbnb service fee: Guest service fee charged for all reservations to help Airbnb run smoothly and offer 24/7 customer support\\n\\nOther costs that may be included:\\n\\n  Currency exchange fee\\n  Value Added Tax (VAT): Tax charged to guests who live in the European Union, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, South Africa, and Japan (charged as JCT).\\n  Local taxes\\u2014Any taxes charged based on the location of the host's listing\\n  \\n\\nNote: Security deposits are only charged if the host needs to make a claim.\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nWhen do I pay for a reservation?\\nHow does Airbnb handle security deposits?\\nCan I use more than one payment method to pay for a reservation?\\nHow do I pay for my long-term reservation?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How is the price determined for my reservation?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb\\u2019s payment system is designed to make transferring money between guests and hosts as simple and reliable as possible. Here\\u2019s how it works:\\n\\n  Guests pay Airbnb when they book a place\\n  Airbnb releases the money to hosts 24 hours after the guest checks in\\n\\nUsing Airbnb\\u2019s payment system is required to make a reservation, and it helps ensure that both parties are protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation policies, Guest Refund Policy, and other safeguards.\\n\\nAirbnb automatically includes service fees in each transaction, and some government-required taxes where applicable.\\n\\n\\nRelated topics for guests:\\n\\nPrices &amp; Fees\\nPayment Methods\\n\\nRelated topics for hosts:\\n\\nHow Payouts Work\\nPayout Preferences\\n", "question": "How does Airbnb process payments?"},
{"answer": "\\n  Once you have a confirmed reservation, your billing receipt and itinerary are automatically generated and stored in Your Trips.\\n  They're updated in the event you cancel your reservation, change your reservation, or receive a refund.\\n\\nFind your itinerary\\n\\n  Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\nNext to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary.\\n\\nFind your receipt\\n\\nGo to Your Trips on airbnb.com.\\n  Next to the reservation you want to see the itinerary for, click View Itinerary. For receipts from past trips, click See Trip Details.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nInformation found in an itinerary\\nYour itinerary contains a lot of useful information about your reservation, including:\\n\\n  Check-in time\\n    Listing address\\n  Detailed directions from your host\\n  Telephone number for your host\\n  Direct link to message your host to confirm check-in details\\n  House manual\\n  House rules\\n  Your billing information\\n  Airbnb's contact information\\n\\nInformation found in a receipt\\nYour billing receipt is more of a summary of your itinerary. The receipt includes:\\n\\n  Name of the guest who made the booking\\n    Any additional guest names you've included\\n  Number of total guests for the reservation\\n  Address of the listing\\n  Name of the host\\n  Dates of the reservation\\n  Breakdown of the total price paid by your payment method.\\n  \\n    Note: If your payment has been processed, the Payment Details section will break down your total. Learn more about long-term payment schedules. In some cases, it might take our security system a couple of days to confirm your reservation and process your billing receipt.\\n  \\n  \\n\\nLearn how to add details to your billing receipt for visa applications or for a business expense.", "question": "How do I find my trip receipt or itinerary?"},
{"answer": "You\\u2019ll be charged for the total cost of your reservation when it's confirmed, which happens as soon as:\\n\\n\\n  You\\u2019ve added your payment information\\n    Your host accepts your request (or the request is accepted immediately with Instant Book)\\n\\n\\nRegardless of how far in advance your reservation is booked, we hold the payment for the host until 24 hours after check-in to make sure everything goes smoothly.\\n\\nLong term reservations\\n\\nFor reservations that are 28 nights or longer, you\\u2019ll be charged the first month\\u2019s payment when the host confirms the reservation. You\\u2019ll then be charged a recurring monthly payment during your reservation. In other words, you won't make a second payment until one month after you check in.\\n\\nSecurity deposits\\n\\nIf you make a reservation with a host who asks for a security deposit, you won\\u2019t be charged on the deposit unless a host makes a successful claim against the deposit after your trip.\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nHow do I check if a reservation is confirmed?\\nHow do I pay for my reservation?\\nHow do I pay for my long term reservation?\\nHow does Airbnb handle security deposits?\\nWhat is a payment authorization?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "When will I be charged?"},
{"answer": "Your payment information is collected when you submit a reservation request. Once the host accepts your request, or if you book a reservation with Instant Book, your payment method will be charged for the entire amount at that time.\\nWhether the reservation is two days or two months away, we hold the payment until 24 hours after check-in before giving it to the host. This hold gives both parties time to make sure that everything is as expected.\\nChanging your payment method\\nIf you've requested to book a listing but the host hasn't responded yet, you can cancel your reservation request and make another request with a different payment method.\\nOnce your reservation is confirmed, there isn't a way to change your payment method at this time.\\nLong term reservations\\nIf you book a reservation for 28 nights or more, you\\u2019ll be charged a first month down payment when the reservation is confirmed. Then, the rest of the nights will be charged on a monthly basis.\\nSecurity deposits\\nIf your listing requires a security deposit, you won\\u2019t be charged unless the host files a successful claim within 48 hours of your checkout.  \\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I submit a reservation request?\\nHow does Airbnb process payments?\\nWhat methods of payment does Airbnb accept?\\nCan I pay with any currency?\\nHow do I pay for my long term reservation?\\nHow does Airbnb handle security deposits?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "When do I pay for a reservation?"},
{"answer": "\\nAirbnb gift cards are a great way to give the gift of travel! Visit airbnb.com/gift to get started.\\n\\nIf you have a gift card to redeem, click Redeem a Gift Card and enter your code. Once a gift card has been added to an Airbnb account, the funds on it will not expire. Gift card balances are visible from your payment methods page. The balance from gift cards will be automatically applied when a trip is booked, but cannot be applied to long-term reservations (28 nights or longer).\\n\\nTo send a digital gift card to anyone in the United States, select Send a Gift Card. We\\u2019ll send the gift card by email, and the recipient can easily add it to their Airbnb account.\\n\\nThe recipient of a digital gift card has 90 days to claim it and link it to their Airbnb account. If the gift card is not claimed within that time, we'll send the gift card balance back to the purchaser on the same payment method they used to pay.\\n\\nRight now, gift cards can only be purchased in US dollars, but we\\u2019ll be expanding on the program in additional currencies in the future.\\n\\nGift Card Terms of Service", "question": "How do Airbnb gift cards work?"},
{"answer": "\\nNo. The currency you pay in is controlled by your payment method and, in some cases, by your country. It\\u2019s not possible to manually choose what currency you'll use to pay.\\n\\nWhen you select your country and payment method on the checkout page, the currency in which you'd be charged will be clearly displayed before you confirm your reservation request.\\n\\nExchange rates and currency conversion\\n\\n\\nWhen the currency you\\u2019re paying with is different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we convert your payment automatically.\\n\\nThe base exchange rate uses data from one or more third parties, such as OANDA. It\\u2019s updated regularly, but may not be identical to the real-time market rate. If you\\u2019re paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we also charge a 3% conversion fee on your total cost; the conversion fee accounts for Airbnb\\u2019s holding costs and foreign currency risks.\\n\\nThe exchange rate used will display on the checkout page before you confirm your booking.\\n\\nThird-party fees\\n\\n\\nIf you pay in a currency that\\u2019s different from the designated currency of your payment method, your provider or third-party payment processor may apply a currency conversion rate or fees to your payment. Contact your provider (for example, your credit or bank card issuer) for information on what fees may apply, since they\\u2019re not controlled by Airbnb.\\n\\nCurrency view\\n\\nYou can view Airbnb listings in many currencies, but this won\\u2019t affect what currency you\\u2019ll be asked to pay in. To change your currency view, scroll to the bottom of any page on airbnb.com and click on the currency field to select what currency you want to view listing prices in.", "question": "Can I pay with any currency?"},
{"answer": "If you want to use a coupon on a new Airbnb reservation, you can add it on the same page where you submit payment.\\n\\nFind your coupon code\\nIf you received a coupon from Airbnb, you will find the coupon in your email. At the moment, these coupons don\\u2019t automatically show up on airbnb.com. \\nUse a coupon on a reservation\\n\\n\\t\\n\\tOn the checkout page for a reservation, click Coupon code near your subtotal.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tEnter your code.\\n\\t\\tClick Apply.\\n\\n\\n\\tThere are a few things to know about using coupons:\\n\\n\\n  Only one coupon can be used for a reservation.\\n    If your coupon has expired, there is no way to re-activate it.\\n    Coupons can only be used once. If you cancel a reservation that used a coupon, the coupon is also no longer valid.\\n  We only accept coupons issued by Airbnb.\\n  If you don\\u2019t use the full amount of a coupon, you won\\u2019t receive the difference.\\n  Coupons can't be applied retroactively.\\n\\nUse travel credits\\n\\nYou can receive travel credits for referring people to travel or host on Airbnb. Unlike with coupons, these credits are automatically applied when you book a space.\\n\\nThere are a few things to know about using travel credits:\\n\\n\\n  Travel credits can\\u2019t be combined with any other coupons.\\n    Travel credits can only be used on qualifying reservations (usually $75 or more, before any guest fees or taxes).\\n  You won\\u2019t receive any travel credits until the person you referred has completed a qualifying reservation on Airbnb.\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n   \\nHow do referrals and travel credits work?\\nHow do Airbnb gift cards work?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I use a coupon code?"},
{"answer": "\\nIf you contact a host about their space before requesting to book it, the host has the option to invite you to book a couple of ways:\\n\\n  \\nPre-approval: The host invites you to book for the dates and prices shown when you contacted the host\\n\\n    Special offer: The host chooses a custom price (or other details) and invites you to book with the new details\\n\\nNote: A special offer will not include the guest service fee or relevant taxes charged for each reservation.\\nFind your pre-approval or special offer\\n\\tYou'll get an email notification when you receive a pre-approval or special offer. You can also check your reservation status by looking in the message thread where you're talking with the host.\\n\\n\\t\\nBook a pre-approval or special offer\\nYou won\\u2019t automatically be booked when you receive a pre-approval or a special offer. You still need to add your payment details and confirm the reservation.\\n\\t\\n\\t    On airbnb.com, go to your Inbox\\n\\t    \\t    Click the conversation with the host to open the message thread\\n\\t    Find the box that shows the details of your pre-approval or special offer\\n\\t    Click Book It!\\n\\t    Add your payment details, and click Book now\\n\\t    You\\u2019ll receive a confirmation email with your itinerary and a billing receipt\\n\\t  \\n\\t\\n\\tYou have 24 hours to book a pre-approval or special offer before it expires. If 24 hours have passed, you can still accept the pre-approval but your host will have to approve your request before your reservation is confirmed.\\n\\nChange your dates\\nIf you've already been pre-approved or given a special offer, you can still change your dates. On the listing page, click Contact Host  to send the host a new message and change the dates before sending the message. The host will then have the ability to pre-approve or give a special offer for your new dates.\\n\\t\\tThe option to book isn\\u2019t available\\nA host has the ability to pre-approve or extend a special offer to multiple people at once for a set of dates. If someone else booked the space before you, you won\\u2019t see the option to accept the reservation.\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nWhat is a pre-approval?\\nHow do I send a guest a special offer?\\nHow do I pre-approve a guest?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I book a pre-approval or special offer?"},
{"answer": "\\n    Inviting people to Airbnb can earn you\\u2014and the people you invite\\u2014travel credit to use toward a new reservation.\\n    Invite friends to use Airbnb\\n    \\n               To begin earning credit, visit the invitation page and send the link to your friends. When a friend clicks the link, they will receive credit that will automatically apply towards their first reservation with Airbnb. The credit will show up automatically on the checkout page of any qualifying reservation.\\n            \\n        \\n        \\nWhen your friend completes their first qualifying reservation, you'll earn travel credit to use for your own Airbnb reservations. You'll receive your travel credit after the departure date of your friend's trip.\\nFor each person you refer, there are two opportunities to earn travel credit. You earn credit when your friend completes a qualifying reservation as a guest and also when they complete a qualifying reservation as a host. You can earn up to $5,000 USD in travel credit overall.\\n     \\n                To see all of your current referral details, click Invite Friends on your Airbnb Dashboard. Terms apply.\\n        Qualifying reservations\\n        A qualifying reservation usually has a total value of $75 USD or more, excluding guest fees and any taxes. These amounts may vary during promotional periods.\\n        Use your travel credit\\n        Your available travel credits automatically appear as a coupon on the checkout page of your reservation request. If the travel credits aren't automatically added, it means the reservation doesn\\u2019t qualify.\\n        Travel credits can't apply to a trip that has already been paid for, but they will be available and applied to your next qualifying reservation. They expire one year from the date they're issued and can only be used once. They\\u2019re also not reusable if you cancel a reservation where the credits were applied.", "question": "How do referrals and travel credits work?"},
{"answer": "If you want to share your trip plans with the people traveling with you, add them to your reservation, which allows them to see your itinerary.\\n\\n    On airbnb.com, go to Your Trips\\n  Next to the trip you want to share, click View itinerary\\n  Next to Guests, choose Manage Guests\\n  Add the name and email address of the person coming with you\\n  Click Send Invites\\n  An email will be sent to the traveler and they can see your full itinerary by signing in (or signing up) for Airbnb\\n\\n\\n\\nIf you want to share your itinerary with people not going on your trip, you can add their emails in the message that appears after you\\u2019ve confirmed a reservation.", "question": "How do I share trip details with others?"},
{"answer": "\\nHosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked.\\n\\nIf a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary. \\n \\n\\nSecurity deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "If you\\u2019re having trouble getting in touch with your host after you\\u2019ve made a reservation, consider a few things:\\n\\n  Most hosts respond within a few hours.\\n    We recommend giving the host a few days to respond. Sometimes things come up or your host might be on a different schedule from you.\\n  Try contacting your host using a different form of communication. For example, you can try reaching them through:\\n  \\n    Airbnb message: Find your host in your Messages and send them a note.  \\n\\nEmail or phone: Go to Your Trips, click View Itinerary next to your reservation, and use the email address or phone number listed. \\n          \\n  \\n  \\n      If your trip is starting or about to start, contact us.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\n  How do I contact a host?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nHow do I contact Airbnb?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What if I can't get in touch with my host?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows hosts to choose among three standardized cancellation policies (Flexible, Moderate, and Strict) that we enforce to protect both hosts and guests. \\nA host's cancellation policy can be found in the Prices section of their listing page. Guests must agree to the host's cancellation policy when they make a reservation. \\n\\nThe Long Term cancellation policy applies to all reservations of 28 nights or more. Each listing and reservation on our site will clearly state the cancellation policy. Guests may cancel and review any penalties by viewing their travel plans and then clicking 'Cancel' on the appropriate reservation.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nCancel a reservation as a guest\\nCancel a reservation as a host\\nWhat happens if my guest cancels a reservation?\\nWhat to do if your host cancels\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is the Airbnb cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tThe Long Term cancellation policy is automatically applied to all long-term reservations of 28 nights or more and requires a 30-day notice for both changes and cancellations. \\n\\nChanges to long-term reservations\\nIf a guest wants to change their reservation, they must submit a change request to the host. \\nIf the guest gives more than 30-days notice, the changes will happen automatically and the guest will be charged or refunded accordingly. If the guest gives less than 30-days notice, or wants to extend their stay, the host will need to accept or decline the changes.\\nAirbnb service fees are also adjusted if any changes are made to the reservation price. \\n\\nCanceling long-term reservations\\nIf a guest cancels a long-term reservation before the check-in date, the first scheduled payment is paid to the host in full, and the guest is refunded the remaining amount. If the guest cancels during their stay, they'll only receive a refund for the nights of the reservation that start 30 days after the cancellation is made.", "question": "Can a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Even if you\\u2019ve already booked your reservation, it\\u2019s your choice whether to accept or decline a host\\u2019s offer to book an alternate listing.\\n    Before paying for a reservation\\n    If you don\\u2019t yet have a confirmed reservation and the host offers you a different listing from the one you discussed, you can book your reservation at this listing or simply look for a new place. You have no obligation to accept the new listing and you should make sure that it would work for your trip before booking.\\n    After you\\u2019ve paid for your reservation\\n    If your host is asking you to stay in a different listing than you originally booked and you\\u2019re okay with a switch, either you or your host can change your reservation. Make sure to check the details of the new listing before accepting a change.\\n    If you\\u2019re not okay with a switch or your host is asking you to switch without officially changing the reservation on Airbnb, ask the host to cancel your reservation so you can get a full refund or find another home that better accommodates your stay.\\n    After you\\u2019ve checked in\\n    If you\\u2019ve already checked in and you feel the listing is not what you booked on the site, follow the steps to document the issue and our Guest Refund Policy will make sure you either get the listing you booked or receive a refund.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I change my reservation as a guest?\\nWhat should I do if something's not missing or not as expected when I check in?\\nHow do I check if a reservation is confirmed?\\nHow can I find my trip receipt or itinerary?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What if a host informs me that the listing I already paid for is now unavailable but they have an alternative?"},
{"answer": "Yes. If the request hasn\\u2019t been accepted by the host, you can cancel the request and send a new one with the updated reservation details. \\n    \\n      To change a reservation request:\\n\\n  Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n  Find your reservation request under Pending Trips\\n  Click Cancel Request and then OK to confirm\\n  If you want, send a new request with your changed dates or number of guests\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nChange a confirmed reservation as a guest\\nChange a confirmed reservation as a host\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Can I make changes to a pending reservation request?"},
{"answer": "It depends. Refunds for confirmed reservations can be issued for a variety of reasons, but are typically dependant on the cancellation policy a host has selected for their listing.\\n\\nSituations that are eligible for a possible refund outside of a host\\u2019s cancellation policy include:\\n\\n    Host cancellations\\n    \\n    Extenuating Circumstances\\n    \\n    Cases covered by Airbnb\\u2019s Guest Refund Policy\\n    \\n\\n\\nIf you\\u2019d like to request a refund from your host for another reason, you\\u2019ll need to use Airbnb\\u2019s Resolution Center. Our Resolution Center allows you to easily connect with your host, discuss a possible refund, and request mediation from an Airbnb team member if you\\u2019re unable to reach an agreement.\\n\\nPlease note that if you are granted a refund, it will take some time to arrive in your account, dependent on your payment method.", "question": "Can I get a refund?"},
{"answer": "Before canceling a reservation, you should check your host\\u2019s cancellation policy to see if you\\u2019re eligible refund.\\n            \\n                        \\n                                Go to Your Trips.\\n                          \\n                        Next to the reservation you want to cancel, click View Itinerary.\\n                        \\n                        Under \\u201cCancellation Policy\\u201d, find the host\\u2019s policy.\\n                        \\n\\n                        See more information on the different cancellation policies.\\n    Cancel a reservation\\n                \\n  Go to Your Trips.\\n  Next to the reservation you want to cancel, click Change or Cancel.\\n  Choose Cancel Reservation.\\n\\n\\n\\n            \\n\\n           \\n        \\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nCan I cancel my reservation request?\\nWhat is a cancellation policy?\\nExtenuating circumstances for guest cancellations \\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Cancel a reservation as a guest"},
{"answer": "If you need to make a change to a confirmed reservation, you can submit a change request to your guest.\\n\\nChange a reservation\\n\\nGo to Your Reservations on airbnb.com.\\nClick Change or Cancel next to the reservation you want to change.\\nChoose Change Reservation.\\nClick Submit Alteration.\\n\\n If the guest accepts your request, the reservation will be updated and they'll be charged or refunded if necessary. If the request is declined or you don\\u2019t receive a response, the reservation will stay the same.\\n\\n\\nThere are a couple of other things to know about submitting change requests:\\n\\nYour chosen cancellation policy will apply based on the new dates.\\nIf the dates of the reservation have already passed, you can\\u2019t make any changes to the reservation.\\nIf you want to change the details of your requested changes, you\\u2019ll have to repeat the steps above and remove your request, and then submit a new one.\\nIf you changed your pricing, the new reservation will reflect this pricing if your change request is accepted.\\nTo request additional funds from your guest, you can do so directly from the Resolutions Center.\\n", "question": "Can I change a reservation as a host?"},
{"answer": "If you need to make a change to a confirmed reservation, you can submit a change request to your host.\\nChange your reservation\\n\\n    Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com.\\n    Next to the reservation you want to change, click Change or Cancel.\\n    Choose Change Reservation.\\n    Change the dates of your stay or the number of guests.\\n    Click Submit Alteration.\\n    If the host accepts your request, your reservation will be updated and you\\u2019ll be charged or refunded if necessary. If the request is declined or you don\\u2019t receive a response, your reservation will stay the same.\\n  \\n  \\n    \\nThere are a couple of other things to know about submitting change requests:\\n\\n \\n  If the dates of your reservation have already passed, you can\\u2019t make any changes.\\n  If you want to change the details of your requested changes, you\\u2019ll have to repeat the steps above and remove your request, and then submit a new one.\\n  If the host altered their pricing before you requested the change, your new reservation will reflect this pricing.\\n", "question": "Can I change a reservation as a guest?"},
{"answer": "Even if you\\u2019ve already booked your reservation, it\\u2019s your choice whether to accept or decline a host\\u2019s offer to book an alternate listing.\\n    Before paying for a reservation\\n    If you don\\u2019t yet have a confirmed reservation and the host offers you a different listing from the one you discussed, you can book your reservation at this listing or simply look for a new place. You have no obligation to accept the new listing and you should make sure that it would work for your trip before booking.\\n    After you\\u2019ve paid for your reservation\\n    If your host is asking you to stay in a different listing than you originally booked and you\\u2019re okay with a switch, either you or your host can change your reservation. Make sure to check the details of the new listing before accepting a change.\\n    If you\\u2019re not okay with a switch or your host is asking you to switch without officially changing the reservation on Airbnb, ask the host to cancel your reservation so you can get a full refund or find another home that better accommodates your stay.\\n    After you\\u2019ve checked in\\n    If you\\u2019ve already checked in and you feel the listing is not what you booked on the site, follow the steps to document the issue and our Guest Refund Policy will make sure you either get the listing you booked or receive a refund.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I change my reservation as a guest?\\nWhat should I do if something's not missing or not as expected when I check in?\\nHow do I check if a reservation is confirmed?\\nHow can I find my trip receipt or itinerary?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What if a host informs me that the listing I already paid for is now unavailable but they have an alternative?"},
{"answer": "If you\\u2019re having trouble getting in touch with your host after you\\u2019ve made a reservation, consider a few things:\\n\\n  Most hosts respond within a few hours.\\n    We recommend giving the host a few days to respond. Sometimes things come up or your host might be on a different schedule from you.\\n  Try contacting your host using a different form of communication. For example, you can try reaching them through:\\n  \\n    Airbnb message: Find your host in your Messages and send them a note.  \\n\\nEmail or phone: Go to Your Trips, click View Itinerary next to your reservation, and use the email address or phone number listed. \\n          \\n  \\n  \\n      If your trip is starting or about to start, contact us.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\n  How do I contact a host?\\nHow do I view and send messages?\\nHow do I contact Airbnb?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What if I can't get in touch with my host?"},
{"answer": "If you notice that something is missing, not working, or otherwise not what you expected when you check in, contact your host right away. Your host is often in the best position to help you\\u2014giving them the chance to fix an issue can be the fastest way to make sure you get what you need, and can continue on with your reservation as planned.\\n\\nIn the event that you experience a travel issue, and you and your host aren't able to resolve the issue on your own, please take the following required steps within 24 hours of your check-in to make sure you're covered by our Guest Refund Policy:\\n  \\n\\t  Contact us to document the issue and place a hold on the host's payment.\\n\\t  Message your host on Airbnb to notify them of the issue. We'll need to verify this in your account.\\n    Take photographs to document the situation. It's important that your photos show what's happening and where (in relation to the rest of the room or space) so we can verify what's going on.\\n  \\n\\nIf your host is unreachable or unresponsive, we'll work on issuing you an adequate partial refund if you decide to stay, or a full refund if you decide to leave, as we deem appropriate. You can see a complete explanation of coverage in our Guest Refund Policy.\\n\\n\\nThe Guest Refund Policy doesn't apply beyond 24 hours after check-in, but we can always help you mediate with your host if you've tried reaching out with no response.\\n\\n\\n      \\n        \\n        Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n        \\n      \\n", "question": "What should I do if something's missing or not as expected when I check in?"},
{"answer": "\\n  \\n   If your host already canceled your reservation, you can transfer your payment to a new Airbnb reservation or request a refund.\\n\\n\\n\\nIf your host let you know that they can\\u2019t accommodate your stay anymore, don\\u2019t cancel for them. If you cancel, you may not be eligible for a full refund depending on the host\\u2019s cancellation policy.\\n\\nInstead, send your host a cancellation request to make sure you receive a full refund.\\nTo send a cancellation request:\\n\\n  Go to Your Trips on airbnb.com\\n    Next to the trip, click Change Reservation\\n  Click Cancel Reservation\\n  Choose My host needs to cancel\\n  Click Send a Cancellation Request\\n\\nIf your trip starts within a week, the host has 24 hours to respond to the request. Otherwise, they have 48 hours to respond. If your host accepts the request, or doesn\\u2019t respond, you\\u2019ll have the option to find a new space for your stay or request a full refund including service fees. If they decline the request, your host is letting you know that they can still host your stay.", "question": "What should I do if my host needs to cancel?"},
{"answer": "The Resolution Center lets you request or send money for things related to your Airbnb trip. To open a refund or payment request, go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions. \\n    You have up to 60 days after your reservation's checkout date to submit a Resolution Center request.\\n\\nAsking for help from Airbnb\\n\\n    If you\\u2019re unable to reach an agreement, you can ask Airbnb to make the final decision 72 hours after the request was opened. To involve Airbnb:\\n    \\n    \\n      Wait 72 hours after you open the request\\n      Go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions \\n      Select the correct reservation\\n      Click Involve Airbnb\\n    \\n\\nWhen you involve Airbnb, our team will be notified and a dedicated team member will be assigned to your case. They\\u2019ll review the information provided by you and your host or guest, before making a final decision. In some cases, we may need to contact you to gather additional information, before we can make a decision.\\n\\n", "question": "What is the Resolution Center?"},
{"answer": "In the event that your reservation is canceled by a host, you have two options:\\n\\n  Transfer your payment to a new Airbnb reservation \\n\\n  Get a refund\\n\\n\\n\\nTransfer your payment to a new Airbnb reservation\\nYour money is immediately available to use towards a new reservation. Once you've found a new place, we'll automatically transfer your original payment to your new reservation request, along with any eligible credit from Airbnb.\\n\\n\\nRequest a refund\\nIf you\\u2019d prefer not to book another place on Airbnb, you can ask for a full refund online at any time. To get a refund:\\n\\n  \\n    Go to Your Trips from airbnb.com.\\n    Find your canceled reservation.\\n    Click Request a refund.\\n  \\n\\n  To ask for a refund, you\\u2019ll need to log into your airbnb.com account on a computer. At the moment, refunds can't be requested using the Airbnb app or mobile website. \\n", "question": "What to do if your host cancels"},
{"answer": "\\n\\nWhen a host payout is ready to be paid to you, it will be released to your payout method for processing. You can check the status of your payouts at any time from your Transaction History.\\n\\nTo add a new payout method:\\n\\nGo to Account on airbnb.com\\nSelect Payout Preferences on the left\\n Click Add Payout Method and enter your address to see the payout options available to you. Available payout methods and currencies differ by country.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nHere are tips for adding specific payout method types:\\n\\nACH/Direct deposit: Use information from a check to enter your ACH/direct deposit routing number and account number. For Further Credit accounts (FFC) are not supported. Wait for a small deposit to confirm your account is ready.\\nInternational wire: Depending on your location, you\\u2019ll need to enter your account number or IBAN, which your bank can provide. Fees may apply. Read more about international wire transfers.\\nPayoneer Bank transfer/debit card: Enter your name as it appears on your official ID. Payoneer needs to approve your details before you can receive payouts. Read more about Payoneer.\\nPayPal: Make sure that your account, which is an email address, is activated on PayPal before adding it as a payout method. Read more about PayPal.\\nWestern Union: Enter your name as it appears on your official ID. Fees apply. Read more about Western Union.\\n\\n\\n\\nIn order to protect your privacy, please do not include specific payout or bank account details in any written correspondence with Airbnb.\\n\\nManaging more than one payout method\\n\\nIf you\\u2019ve added more than one payout method, you can specify a default or add payout routing rules.\\n\\n\\nYour default payout method is noted next to your payout method type. To choose a different payout method as your default, first add the new payout method, then click Options and select  Make Default. To remove a payout method (and any settings associated with that payout method), click  Options and select  Remove Payout Method.\\n\\n\\nPayout routing rules let you split your payouts among different payout methods or set a different payout method for each listing in your account.\\n\\nTo add a payout routing rule:\\nGo to Account on airbnb.com\\nSelect Payout Preferences on the left\\nClick Add Payout Routing Rule. When you add a new payout routing rule, it won\\u2019t affect reservations that have already begun\\u2014only payouts for reservations that begin after the change will be affected.\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I add or change my payout method?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\n\\n\\tSetting a minimum payout amount for your payout method is optional. If selected, we'll hold your funds until you reach a payout amount over the minimum you've set. \\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\tTo set a minimum payout amount:\\n\\n\\n\\n    Go to Account on airbnb.com\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tSelect Payout Preferences on the left\\n\\t\\n\\t  Select Options to the right of your chosen payment method\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tSelect Set Minimum Payout Amount\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tEnter your chosen minimum payout amount and click Submit\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tFor most payout methods, minimum payout amounts up to $8000 USD are supported. For Western Union, the minimum payout amount must be more than $60 USD and less than $2000 USD. At this time, we're only able to support setting a minimum amount in USD, but this will not affect your chosen payout currency.", "question": "How do I set a minimum payout amount?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIn most states and localities in the United States, guests who stay in a home or apartment for approximately 30 days\\u2014the exact number depends on jurisdiction\\u2014may establish rights as a tenant. Generally, this means that local tenancy laws could protect them, and you may not be able to remove them from your property without proceeding through required eviction processes in court.\\n\\n\\tFor example, in California, Illinois, and New York, a residential tenancy may be created after 30 consecutive days of occupancy. Someone who stays with you for fewer than 30 days generally does not have the rights of a tenant unless there is a written agreement to the contrary, but every state is different.\\n\\n\\tLocal laws may differ from state laws regarding residential tenancies. We encourage you to review your local rules and regulations before accepting a long-term reservation.\\n\\n\\tGuests who refuse to leave\\u2014and how Airbnb can help\\n\\n\\tThese situations are incredibly rare, but if they happen, we'll work with you to try and help resolve the problem with your guest. Should you face such a situation, let our 24/7 support team know\\xa0as soon as possible and we'll get in touch with you.\\n\\n\\tAsking guests to sign a rental agreement\\n\\n\\tIf you rent your home or apartment for more than 30 days, consider whether you want guests to sign a rental agreement. If so, you should make these requirements clear in your House Rules before finalizing a booking. Laws governing these subjects vary widely depending on where you live, so be sure to contact a landlord-tenant attorney familiar with your local laws and regulations.\\n\\n\\tLocal rent control laws\\n\\n\\tRent control is a special set of laws that includes limits on rent increases and eviction restrictions. Some local rent control laws may override state law, and while many states or local jurisdictions do not have rent control, other laws may still protect tenants. For these reasons, we recommend you contact your local Rent board, Department of Consumer Affairs, Attorney General, or other agencies to learn more about rent control and rent stabilization and how these rules might impact a long-term reservation.\\n\\n\\tEvicting guests that overstay a long-term reservation\\n\\n\\tStatutes exist in nearly all jurisdictions that permit landlords to use summary proceedings to evict tenants. A summary proceeding is a judicial proceeding that lets a landlord regain possession of leased property in an expedited fashion. You should contact a landlord-tenant attorney or your local county courts to learn more about eviction laws where you live, as they may affect your ability to evict a guest who overstays a long-term reservation.", "question": "What are some things I should consider before hosting long-term guests?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb empowers hosts to set and manage their cancellation policies. If a host or guest needs to cancel a reservation, it\\u2019s their responsibility to cancel as soon as possible. At times, certain circumstances outside of a host or guest\\u2019s control can impact their ability to meet the terms of a reservation.\\n\\nIn rare instances, if Airbnb determines that a Guest\\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, Airbnb may override the Host's cancellation policy (ex: flexible, moderate, strict) and make refund decisions.  If Airbnb determines that a Host\\u2019s reason for cancellation falls within Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances policy, Airbnb may waive the host cancellation penalties outlined in Airbnb\\u2019s Terms of Service and Airbnb\\u2019s Payments Terms of Service.\\n\\nWhat might be covered?\\n\\nValid extenuating circumstances include:\\n\\n\\nUnexpected death or serious illness of a host, guest or immediate family member \\nSerious injury that directly restricts a guest\\u2019s ability to travel or a host\\u2019s ability to host\\nSignificant natural disasters or severe weather incidents impacting the location of destination or location of departure\\nUrgent travel restrictions or severe security advisories issued after the time of booking, by an appropriate national or international authority (such as a government office or department)\\nEndemic disease declared by a credible national or international authority (such as the US Center for Disease Control or the World Health Organization)\\nSevere property damage or unforeseen maintenance issues that directly impact the ability to host safely\\nGovernment-mandated obligations issued after the time of booking\\n\\n\\nIf you need to make a claim\\n\\nClaims can only be considered after a reservation has been canceled. Once you have informed your host or guest and canceled a reservation, if you feel that your reason for cancellation is covered by Airbnb\\u2019s Extenuating Circumstances Policy, contact Airbnb for consideration. We generally require claims to be submitted no later than 14 days from the original check-in date and we may require valid supporting documentation.", "question": "Extenuating Circumstances Policy"},
{"answer": "Guests and hosts work out details for checking in, exchanging keys, and checking out directly with each other. There is no online check-in or checkout process.\\nRead below for some guidelines to help you have a smooth check-in.\\nCommunication is essential\\nBefore the start of the reservation, message your host to figure out check-in and checkout times, make plans for the key exchange, and ask any other questions. Keeping communication in your message thread gives you and Airbnb a clear reference if any issues come up.\\nAlso, confirm your contact information and arrival details so you can reach each other in case plans change. Make sure to let each other know if you'll be without access to a phone or the Internet.\\nKnow your reservation details\\nAfter a reservation is confirmed, refer to your itinerary for useful information about your reservation, such as the check-in and checkout time, the listing's address, your host's contact information, and your billing receipt. If there's no check-in or check-out time specified within a listing's description, check-in is 3:00 PM local time and checkout is 12:00 PM local time.\\nStay tuned to flight information and weather forecasts\\nLook up travel advisories to make sure there is nothing impacting your reservation. With road closures and flight delays, guests and hosts might need a little extra time to safely meet up to exchange keys.\\nKey exchange\\nMany hosts greet guests in person to exchange keys. Others send keys and instructions in the mail, leave them in a lockbox, or have a neighbor meet a guest. The host can decide whether or not to give a guest a key. But, our Guest Refund Policy states that guests need to have reasonable access to the listing they booked. If you decide not to provide keys, you should mention in your listing\\u2019s description and house rules that keys will not be available to the guests so people are aware of the situation before booking.", "question": "How does check-in work?"},
{"answer": "\\nNo. To make sure guest payments are protected and to ensure that hosts are properly compensated for reservation damages, we ask that all security deposits be handled through the Airbnb website. Payments outside of the Airbnb website, including security deposits, are a violation of our Terms of Service.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nHow does Airbnb handle security deposits?\\nHow do I include a security deposit on my listing?\\nHow do I make a claim on the security deposit?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Can a security deposit be collected outside of the Airbnb website?"},
{"answer": "Go to your account settings and select Connected Apps. From there, you can change your app settings or remove the app from your Airbnb account. \\n\\nWant more information on Host Assist? Learn more.", "question": "How to remove Host Assist apps"},
{"answer": "If you need to make a claim on your security deposit, you can do so in the Resolution Center within 48 hours of your guest\\u2019s checkout date. \\n\\n\\nGo to the Resolution Center on airbnb.com\\nChoose the relevant reservation\\nUnder Select a reason, select Request compensation for damages\\nClick Continue to submit details about the damages and associated costs on the next page\\n\\n\\nIf your guest agrees to the amount you requested, we'll send you a payout between 5 to 7 business days. \\n\\nIf your guest declines or doesn't respond within 72 hours, click Involve Airbnb in your Resolution Center case. If we require additional documentation, you'll have 48 hours to provide this documentation. \\n\\nMost security deposit claims will be resolved within one week. We'll make sure you and your guest are represented fairly, and if we determine you're owed money, we'll send it to you in a separate payout.", "question": "How do I make a claim on the security deposit?"},
{"answer": "The Resolution Center lets you request or send money for things related to your Airbnb trip. To open a refund or payment request, go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions. \\n    You have up to 60 days after your reservation's checkout date to submit a Resolution Center request.\\n\\nAsking for help from Airbnb\\n\\n    If you\\u2019re unable to reach an agreement, you can ask Airbnb to make the final decision 72 hours after the request was opened. To involve Airbnb:\\n    \\n    \\n      Wait 72 hours after you open the request\\n      Go to www.airbnb.com/resolutions \\n      Select the correct reservation\\n      Click Involve Airbnb\\n    \\n\\nWhen you involve Airbnb, our team will be notified and a dedicated team member will be assigned to your case. They\\u2019ll review the information provided by you and your host or guest, before making a final decision. In some cases, we may need to contact you to gather additional information, before we can make a decision.\\n\\n", "question": "What is the Resolution Center?"},
{"answer": "\\nHost Assist apps and products are offered by different companies who have partnered with Airbnb. If you\\u2019re having trouble, you should contact the customer service team for the company offering the app.  \\n\\n\\nWant more information on Host Assist? Learn more", "question": "What should I do if I need help with one of my Host Assist apps?"},
{"answer": "Cleaning fees help hosts account for extra expenses they have getting their listing ready before guests arrive or after guests depart. \\nAdd a cleaning fee\\nTo add or edit a cleaning fee for your listing:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nSelect the listing you want to edit\\nGo to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner\\nUnder Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Cleaning fee \\n\\nEnter the one-time cleaning fee you want to charge each reservation\\n\\n\\nThe cleaning fee is only added to reservations booked after the change is made.\\nThere are a few things to know about cleaning fees:\\n\\nIn the search results, guests will see a nightly rate that includes the cleaning fee divided by the total number of nights in the reservation. When they submit a reservation request, the nightly rate and the cleaning fee will be listed separately in the price breakdown.\\nThe cleaning fee is part of the reservation total and is not returned to guests at the end of the reservation.\\nBecause the cleaning fee is included in the total guest payment and host payout, service fees apply.\\nCleaning fees are not automatically added to Special Offers so you should factor that in when setting an all-inclusive price.\\n", "question": "How do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?"},
{"answer": "\\n  \\n   Percentage discounts for long-term stays have replaced fixed prices for long-term stays. We made this change so that if your nightly prices change, your long-term prices will change with them.\\n\\n\\nIf you want to charge less for longer stays, you can set a weekly or monthly discount. Your weekly discount will apply to any reservation for 7-27 nights. Your monthly discounts will apply to any reservation for 28 nights or longer.\\n\\nSet a weekly or monthly discount\\nTo set a weekly or monthly discount:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\nClick Pricing\\nUnder Long-term prices, enter a discount from 0% to 99% (the update will automatically save) \\n\\n \\nGuests will be able to see your long term pricing in your listing page. When they make a long-term reservation request they'll see your discount in their price breakdown.\\nThere are a few things to know about long-term pricing:\\n\\nIf you want your listing to appear in searches for long-term reservations for 28 nights or more, you'll need to set a monthly discount. \\nAfter the discount is applied, the minimum daily price must be at least $10 per day. \\n\\nCustom pricing\\nAny custom weekly and monthly prices you set will not be overriden by your nightly, weekly, or monthly discounts.\\nIf you want to charge more for long-term stays, set custom prices for specific weeks or months.", "question": "How do I set prices for long-term stays?"},
{"answer": "If you don\\u2019t want to receive any inquiries or requests, you can either snooze or deactivate your listing. \\nTurning your listing off doesn\\u2019t affect your confirmed reservations. \\nSnooze your listing for a set period of time\\nTo pause your listing and hide it from search results for a set period of time: \\n\\n\\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to snooze\\nSelect Snoozed in the drop-down menu on the bottom-left\\nEnter the Start date and End date\\n\\nYour listing will automatically reactivate when the timeframe you set is over. The day before your listing reactivates, you'll get a reminder email.\\nTemporarily deactivate your listing\\nTo deactivate your listing:\\n\\n\\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to deactivate\\nUse the drop-down menu on the bottom-left to select Unlisted\\n\\nYou can reactivate your listing at any time from the Manage Listings page. \\nPermanently deactivate your listing\\nTo permanently deactivate your listing:\\n\\n\\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to deactivate\\nSelect Basics on the left-hand side of the screen\\nClick deactivate this listing at the bottom of the page\\n \\nYou won't be able to permanently deactivate your listing if you have any upcoming reservations or reservation requests. Past reviews of your listing will remain on your public profile\\u2014they cannot be removed.\\n\\nIf you would like to cancel your Airbnb account entirely,  learn how to cancel your account.\\n\\n", "question": "How do I snooze or deactivate my listing?"},
{"answer": "\\n            If you list your space on Airbnb and other websites, you can prevent multiple guests from booking the same dates by syncing your Airbnb calendar with your other calendars.\\nCalendar importing\\nCalendar importing allows you to automatically keep your Airbnb calendar up to date with an external calendar that supports the iCalendar format, including Google calendar or the calendar on HomeAway or VRBO.\\nTo import a calendar:\\n            \\n                Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit\\n                Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view\\nUnder Sync Calendars, select Import calendar                \\nPaste your calendar\\u2019s URL in the Calendar address (URL) field\\nName your calendar\\nClick Import calendar\\n            \\n        \\n           If you edit an external calendar that syncs with your calendar on Airbnb, it will take a few hours for those changes to be visible to guests viewing your listing.\\nCalendar exporting\\n        \\n            Calendar exporting lets you view your Airbnb calendar on an external calendar that supports the iCal format. To export your calendar in iCal format and add it to your external calendar:\\nTo export your calendar\\n            \\n                 Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit\\n                Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view\\nUnder Sync Calendars, select Export calendar                \\nCopy and paste the Airbnb calendar link into your iCal applications\\n            \\n      \\n\\n\\n  Related Content\\n\\n  \\n    \\n      How do I change my reservation settings?\\n      How do I manage my availability on my calendar?\\n      How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?\\n      How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?"},
{"answer": "Being a responsible host means being a considerate tenant, neighbor, and community member. Here are a few things you should consider when talking with others about hosting on Airbnb.\\nKnow the rules and regulations\\nBefore you start hosting, know what contracts and rules affect you, such as leases, condo board or co-op rules, HOA rules, or rules established by tenant organizations. Make sure you understand and comply with these rules before listing your space. Other laws in your city or state may also affect you, so be sure to review them as well.\\nTalk with your landlord or HOA\\nTalk to your homeowner\\u2019s association or landlord about how often you plan to have guests, and how Airbnb builds trust in its community. You can share information about Airbnb\\u2019s trust and safety resources, including community reviews and Verified ID. Remind them that you only host people you feel comfortable with. If applicable in your country, you can also explain that Airbnb offers a US$1M Host Guarantee.\\nTalk with your neighbors\\nNeighbors may want to know about many of the same things as your landlord or HOA, as well as more specifics about upcoming bookings, such as names, dates, and other information about your guests. Making sure your neighbors are comfortable might help address some of your landlord\\u2019s concerns. \\nBe a responsible host\\nHere are some things you can do to show your landlord, HOA, and neighbors that you care about the property and your neighbors as much as they do:\\n\\nSet an occupancy limit to only allow groups of a certain size \\nShare your home and building rules with each guest\\nProvide your guests with phone numbers for emergency responders and a map of emergency exits and evacuation routes\\nMake sure you have a working smoke and carbon monoxide detector\\nInform neighbors when a guest will be staying in your home\\nWith your guests\\u2019 permission, share names or Airbnb profile pages\\n", "question": "How should I talk to my neighbors, homeowners association, or landlord about Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb welcomes many different kinds of listings on our site as long as they meet the following criteria:\\n\\nThe space is only used for lodging\\nThe space, if a mobile home, sailboat, yacht, or other vessel, will be semi-permanently attached to a set location during the reservation\\nThe space is accurately represented, located where the host says it is, and is bookable by the host\\n\\n\\nListings that don\\u2019t meet these criteria include:\\n\\nMotor vehicles or watercraft intended for mobile use\\nAny listing whose primary purpose isn\\u2019t serving as a lodging\\n\\n\\nIf we discover a listing that doesn\\u2019t meet our guidelines, we may exercise our discretion to limit, suspend, deactivate, or cancel the host's account. Refer to our Terms of Service for more information and other requirements for listing your space on Airbnb.", "question": "Are there any restrictions about what can be listed?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIn most states and localities in the United States, guests who stay in a home or apartment for approximately 30 days\\u2014the exact number depends on jurisdiction\\u2014may establish rights as a tenant. Generally, this means that local tenancy laws could protect them, and you may not be able to remove them from your property without proceeding through required eviction processes in court.\\n\\n\\tFor example, in California, Illinois, and New York, a residential tenancy may be created after 30 consecutive days of occupancy. Someone who stays with you for fewer than 30 days generally does not have the rights of a tenant unless there is a written agreement to the contrary, but every state is different.\\n\\n\\tLocal laws may differ from state laws regarding residential tenancies. We encourage you to review your local rules and regulations before accepting a long-term reservation.\\n\\n\\tGuests who refuse to leave\\u2014and how Airbnb can help\\n\\n\\tThese situations are incredibly rare, but if they happen, we'll work with you to try and help resolve the problem with your guest. Should you face such a situation, let our 24/7 support team know\\xa0as soon as possible and we'll get in touch with you.\\n\\n\\tAsking guests to sign a rental agreement\\n\\n\\tIf you rent your home or apartment for more than 30 days, consider whether you want guests to sign a rental agreement. If so, you should make these requirements clear in your House Rules before finalizing a booking. Laws governing these subjects vary widely depending on where you live, so be sure to contact a landlord-tenant attorney familiar with your local laws and regulations.\\n\\n\\tLocal rent control laws\\n\\n\\tRent control is a special set of laws that includes limits on rent increases and eviction restrictions. Some local rent control laws may override state law, and while many states or local jurisdictions do not have rent control, other laws may still protect tenants. For these reasons, we recommend you contact your local Rent board, Department of Consumer Affairs, Attorney General, or other agencies to learn more about rent control and rent stabilization and how these rules might impact a long-term reservation.\\n\\n\\tEvicting guests that overstay a long-term reservation\\n\\n\\tStatutes exist in nearly all jurisdictions that permit landlords to use summary proceedings to evict tenants. A summary proceeding is a judicial proceeding that lets a landlord regain possession of leased property in an expedited fashion. You should contact a landlord-tenant attorney or your local county courts to learn more about eviction laws where you live, as they may affect your ability to evict a guest who overstays a long-term reservation.", "question": "What are some things I should consider before hosting long-term guests?"},
{"answer": "A listing is automatically assigned to a neighborhood based on its address and this neighborhood can\\u2019t be edited. The best way to make sure your listing\\u2019s neighborhood is correct is to make sure your address is as accurate as possible.\\nHow boundaries are determined\\nNeighborhood boundaries are based on research with locals and city experts. A cartographer helps make sure these boundaries are accurate and up-to-date, and we\\u2019re always looking for ways to improve how we use boundaries. Since neighborhoods evolve over time, we are continuously updating our maps to increase their accuracy. If your listing\\u2019s neighborhood is a subset of a larger neighborhood, or if two neighborhoods overlap, your listing may show in search results for both neighborhoods.\\nHow \\u201cneighborhood types\\u201d are defined\\nOn the mobile app, guests have the ability to filter their search by neighborhood type (for example, \\u201cquiet\\u201d or \\u201chip\\u201d). These descriptions allow guests to see the most relevant neighborhoods that best fit their trip, and were chosen based on research on the most common words guests use to describe a neighborhood they want to stay in.\\nAt this time, guests are asked in the review flow after checkout to choose which neighborhood types that best fit their listing. These guest selections are combined for every listing in a neighborhood, and the most frequently selected descriptions by guests are used to represent an important aspect of that neighborhood. These neighborhood types may change over time as guests and hosts provide more feedback.\\nLeave feedback about neighborhoods\\nIf you feel your listed neighborhood is wrong or information regarding a neighborhood is incorrect, you can provide us direct feedback. While we can\\u2019t respond to everything, we encourage you to share your knowledge and opinions because the Neighborhoods team uses feedback to improve our platform.\\nMy address is wrong\\nIf the address of your listing is wrong, the neighborhood for your home may be incorrect as well. To change the address before your first booking, you can edit your listing. If you\\u2019ve already booked a reservation, you\\u2019ll need to contact us to change your address.\\n\\nNo neighborhood showing for my listing\\nWhile we\\u2019ve recently updated neighborhood information for popular travel destinations worldwide, not all locations have neighborhoods on Airbnb. If no neighborhoods are available, the search results won\\u2019t display a neighborhood filter for that location.\\nDescribe your neighborhood for guests\\nMany travelers, instead of searching by neighborhood, use listing pages to learn about what location is right for their trip. Write a robust description of your listing so guests know your opinion of the surrounding neighborhood when looking at your listing page.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nWhat are Neighborhoods?\\nHow do I search by neighborhood?\\nHow are search results determined?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I edit my neighborhood?"},
{"answer": "You can edit the listing address or map location if they are incorrect. Your exact address will only be seen by guests with confirmed reservations.\\nEdit your listing address \\nTo edit your listing address:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\nClick Location\\nClick Edit Address and complete the fields\\nClick Save Address\\n\\n \\nEdit your listing\\u2019s location on the map\\n\\nTo edit your listing's location on the map:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\nClick Location\\nClick on the map and drag it until the location pin is in the right spot\\n\\n \\nIf you want to edit your address because you've moved to a new location or you're listing a new space, you need to create a new listing rather than updating the address.\\n\\n\\n  Related articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n      How do I edit my listing?\\n      How do I edit my neighborhood?\\n      Where can I see how my listing is performing?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I set my map or address?"},
{"answer": "To help make sure guests aren\\u2019t contacting you if you're unable to host, and to preserve your response rate, your listing may be deactivated:\\n\\nIf you let 4 consecutive reservation requests or booking inquiries expire \\nIf you decline consecutive reservation requests and booking inquiries over an extended period of time \\nIf you consistently take more than 7 days to pre-approve an inquiry \\n\\nReactivate your listing\\nIf your listing is temporarily deactivated, you\\u2019ll receive an email with instructions on how to reactivate it. You can also reactivate your listing at anytime from your dashboard. It may take up to an hour for your listing to appear in search results after it has been reactivated.", "question": "Why was my listing deactivated?"},
{"answer": "Hosts share their House Rules to set expectations with their guests, like limits on smoking, areas beyond the listing space that are off-limits, and permission to have visitors. \\nTo add or edit House Rules after you\\u2019ve listed your space:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick on the listing you want to edit\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\nUnder Hosting, click on Booking\\n\\nUnder House Rules, enter your expectations and rules for guests\\n\\n\\nIf a guest breaks a house rule, either before or during their stay, you can cancel their reservation without penalty. \\nHouse rules appear on your listing page, and guests must review and agree to them before requesting a reservation. They\\u2019re also sent directly to a guest once they\\u2019ve a confirmed reservation.", "question": "What are house rules?"},
{"answer": "If you don\\u2019t want to receive any inquiries or requests, you can either snooze or deactivate your listing. \\nTurning your listing off doesn\\u2019t affect your confirmed reservations. \\nSnooze your listing for a set period of time\\nTo pause your listing and hide it from search results for a set period of time: \\n\\n\\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to snooze\\nSelect Snoozed in the drop-down menu on the bottom-left\\nEnter the Start date and End date\\n\\nYour listing will automatically reactivate when the timeframe you set is over. The day before your listing reactivates, you'll get a reminder email.\\nTemporarily deactivate your listing\\nTo deactivate your listing:\\n\\n\\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to deactivate\\nUse the drop-down menu on the bottom-left to select Unlisted\\n\\nYou can reactivate your listing at any time from the Manage Listings page. \\nPermanently deactivate your listing\\nTo permanently deactivate your listing:\\n\\n\\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to deactivate\\nSelect Basics on the left-hand side of the screen\\nClick deactivate this listing at the bottom of the page\\n \\nYou won't be able to permanently deactivate your listing if you have any upcoming reservations or reservation requests. Past reviews of your listing will remain on your public profile\\u2014they cannot be removed.\\n\\nIf you would like to cancel your Airbnb account entirely,  learn how to cancel your account.\\n\\n", "question": "How do I snooze or deactivate my listing?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb listings are categorized into the following room types:\\n\\nShared rooms: Guests share the entire space with you or others and don't have a private room to themselves. \\nPrivate rooms: Guests share some common areas with you, like the kitchen, living room, or bathroom, but they have their own private room for sleeping. \\nEntire homes/apartments: Guests rent the entire unit and don't have to share the space with you or with anyone else. \\n\\nAs a host, you're responsible for accurately describing your listing, so make sure you choose the appropriate room type.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I list multiple rooms?\\nHow do I add the type of bed to my listing?\\n\\nHow do I edit my listing?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What do the different room types mean?"},
{"answer": "To edit your listing:\\n  \\n    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\n    Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\n    Click on the section of your listing that you want to edit.\\n  \\n\\nThere are a couple of other things to know about editing your listing:\\n  \\n           Some of your editing options (for example: calendar, reservation settings, and pricing) won't appear until you've finished listing your space.\\n        Edits only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes; they don't apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.\\n        While you edit, your changes will be automatically saved. Changes may take up to an hour to appear on your public listing. \\n        \\n\\n\\n        \\n        \\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Articles\\n\\n  \\n    Hosting\\n    \\n      How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar?\\n      How do I edit my pricing settings?\\n      How much should I charge for my listing?\\n      Instant Book settings\\n    \\n    Listing\\n    \\n      What should I choose for my room type?\\n      How do I set my map or address?\\n      How do I edit my neighborhood?\\n      How do I add amenities to my listing?\\n      How do I add and reorder my listing\\u2019s photos?\\n      What is Airbnb doing to help hosts make their homes safer for guests?\\n    \\n    Guest Resources\\n    \\n      What are house manuals and house rules?\\n      What's a Guidebook?\\n      How can I see or change the cancellation policy for my listing?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I edit my listing?"},
{"answer": "To add the type of bed:\\n\\n  \\n    Go to your Manage Listings page\\n      Click Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit\\n   Clicking Basics on the left hand side menu\\n   Navigate to the Rooms and Beds section\\n\\n\\nFrom there, you can add the number of rooms for your listing and select the number/type of bed for each room.\\n\\nNote: This feature is only available if your listing can accommodate more than 3 guests.", "question": "How do I add the type of bed to my listing?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can share your listing through different social media platforms or embed a preview of your listing on your website to reach people beyond those searching on Airbnb.\\n    \\n    Share your listing on social media\\n    To share your listing on Facebook, Pinterest, Google+, or Twitter:\\n      \\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick the name of the listing you want to share\\nOn your listing's page, under Save to Wishlist click ... More.\\nSelect the social media platform you want to use and follow the steps to share\\n\\n\\n    \\n        \\n    \\nEmbed a preview of your listing\\n    If you have your own website, you can embed a preview of your listing:\\n    \\n    \\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick the name of the listing you want to embed\\nOn your listing's page, under Save to Wishlist click ... More.\\nSelect Embed this listing\\n      Click Copy HTML in the preview window to save the HTML to your clipboard\\n      Paste the HTML code into your website where you\\u2019d like your listing preview to appear.\\n", "question": "How can I share or embed my listing on other websites?"},
{"answer": "If you want to list multiple rooms in your house, you can create a separate listing for each space you have available. Each room will have it\\u2019s own calendar and listing page that should accurately reflect the number of beds and amenities, as well as what space will be shared with others.\\n\\nTo create a new listing, log in to airbnb.com and go to List your space.\\n\\nYou can also create a listing for your whole house and separate listings for individual rooms in the house, but be sure to sync your calendars. If you rent your entire house, block those dates on all the individual rooms so you won't double-book.\\n\\nYou can offer guests a discounted rate for booking multiple rooms by sending a Special Offer and blocking the calendar of the other listings to avoid double-booking.", "question": "How do I list multiple rooms?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\n\\n\\nAdditional Fees\\n\\nCleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings.\\nOther fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I set my base price?\\n\\nHow do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?\\n\\nHow do I set custom or seasonal pricing?\\n\\nHow do I set up weekend pricing?\\n\\nSmart Pricing: Set prices based on demand\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "In addition to written reviews, guests can submit an overall star rating and a set of category star ratings. Hosts can view their star ratings on their Stats page, under Ratings from Guests. To see a breakdown of guest ratings by category, click Show Details.\\n Guests can give ratings on:\\n\\nOverall Experience. What was your guest\\u2019s overall experience?\\nCleanliness.  Did your guests feel that your space was clean and tidy?\\nAccuracy.  How accurately did your listing page represent your space?\\nValue.  Did your guest feel your listing provided good value for the price?\\nCommunication.  How well did you communicate with your guest before and during their stay?\\nArrival. How smoothly did their check-in go?\\nLocation. How did guests feel about your neighborhood? \\n\\n\\n In each category, you\\u2019ll be able to see how often you get 5 stars, how guests rated nearby hosts, and, in some cases, tips to help you improve your listing.\\n\\nThe number of stars displayed at the top of a listing page is an aggregate of the primary scores guests have given for that listing. At the bottom of a listing page there's an aggregate for each category rating. A host needs to receive star ratings from at least 3 guests before their aggregate score appears.", "question": "How do star ratings work?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIf you're a host, you can set the check-in and checkout times for your listing.\\n\\tEdit your check-in time\\n\\tTo edit your check-in time:\\n\\t\\n\\t   On airbnb.com, go to Manage Listings\\n    Click the listing you want to edit\\n    On the left side of the screen, click Check-in\\n    Set your Check-in window by selecting a check-in start time and end time\\n    (Optional) Set a checkout time\\n\\t\\n\\tNote: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.", "question": "How do I change the check-in time for my listing?"},
{"answer": "\\nHost Assist apps and products are offered by different companies who have partnered with Airbnb. If you\\u2019re having trouble, you should contact the customer service team for the company offering the app.  \\n\\n\\nWant more information on Host Assist? Learn more", "question": "What should I do if I need help with one of my Host Assist apps?"},
{"answer": "For the best experience using the Airbnb site, we suggest using the most up-to-date version of Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox.\\n\\nBrowser developers frequently make improvements to provide you with a faster, more secure online experience. Newer browsers also support a wider range of designs and features than older browsers.\\n\\nIf you prefer to use Internet Explorer, please upgrade to IE9 or higher. Many features of the Airbnb website don't work with older versions of Internet Explorer\\u2014and we often can't provide technical support if you're using an outdated browser.", "question": "Which Internet browsers work best on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "We expect hosts to respect their guests\\u2019 privacy. You must notify your guests about any security cameras or other surveillance devices at or around your listing, and get consent where required. \\nThe use of surveillance equipment may also be against the law in some places, so make sure you understand your local regulations.", "question": "Can I install video or audio surveillance in my listing?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tWe consider neighbors a part of the Airbnb community. Here's some information about our service, and a way for you to share feedback with us.\\n\\n\\tAirbnb takes trust seriously\\n\\n\\tWe're committed to helping our community build and maintain trust. That's why we've provided tools to help our community make the right decisions when it comes to hosting or traveling. Read more about our Trust and Safety initiatives.\\n\\n\\tAirbnb encourages responsibility\\n\\n\\tWe encourage hosts to think carefully about their responsibilities. We understand that hosting comes with a commitment to neighbors and to the community. Read more about our take on responsible hosting.\\n\\n\\tNeighbor resources\\n\\n\\tIf your neighbor is an Airbnb host and you need to get in touch with us, visit www.airbnb.com/neighbors. If you have more general questions about how Airbnb works, browse our Help Center.", "question": "My neighbor is an Airbnb host. What do I need to know?"},
{"answer": "When deciding whether to become an Airbnb host, it's important for you to understand how the laws work in your city.\\n\\t\\n\\tSome cities have laws that restrict your ability to host paying guests for short periods. These laws are often part of a city's zoning or administrative codes. In many cities, you must register, get a permit, or obtain a license before you list your property or accept guests. Certain types of short-term bookings may be prohibited altogether. Local governments vary greatly in how they enforce these laws. Penalties may include fines or other enforcement.\\n\\n  These rules can be confusing. We're working with governments around the world to clarify these rules so that everyone has a clear understanding of what the laws are.\\xa0\\n\\n  In some tax jurisdictions, Airbnb will take care of calculating, collecting, and remitting local occupancy tax on your behalf. Occupancy tax is calculated differently in every jurisdiction, and we\\u2019re moving as quickly as possible to extend this benefit to more hosts around the globe.\\n\\n  In the meantime, please review your local laws before listing your space on Airbnb. More information about your city's laws and regulations may be available on our  Responsible Hosting page in the Your City's Regulations section.\\n\\t\\n\\tBy accepting our Terms of Service and activating a listing, you certify that you will follow your local laws and regulations.", "question": "What legal and regulatory issues should I consider before hosting on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "\\nHost management services are third-party companies that assist with hosting responsibilities like key exchanges, cleanings, and listing management\\u2014they're not affiliated with Airbnb. \\n\\nIf you choose to use a host management service, you'll be held to the same standards and policies as other Airbnb community members.", "question": "Can I use a host management service?"},
{"answer": "We\\u2019re only able to offer one complimentary photography shoot per listing. \\n\\nIf your space has changed, we suggest taking your own photos and adding them to your listing's page. Get tips for taking your own great photos.", "question": "Can I receive a complimentary reshoot of my listing?"},
{"answer": "Hosts can require guests to complete Airbnb's Verified ID process. In order to require Verified ID, you must first verify your own ID.\\n        \\n            To set reservation requirements:\\n        \\n                Go to your Manage Listings page\\nClick Reservation Requirements in the menu on the left side of your screen\\nCheck the box next to Require guests to go through verification\\nClick Save Reservation Requirements\\n        \\n        \\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I change my reservation settings?\\nWhat is Verified ID?\\nIs verifying my ID secure?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Can I require guests to be verified before booking?"},
{"answer": "You need at least one photo in order to list a space, but we recommend you upload at least 10\\u2014enough to show potential guests a thorough view of the space they'll get to use if they stay with you.\\n\\nAdd photos\\nTo add photos to an existing listing:\\n\\t\\nGo to Your Listing on airbnb.com\\n\\tUnder the listing you want to edit, click Manage Listing and Calendar\\n\\tClick Photos on the left\\n\\tClick Add Photo and choose the photos you want to upload\\n\\n\\t\\nKeep in mind that resolution matters\\u2014take photos that are at least 1024 x 683px. When in doubt, a bigger photo is better.\\n\\nChanges to your photos may take up to 30 minutes to appear on your public listing. For a faster upload, we encourage you to use Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox web browsers.\\nReorder photos\\n\\n\\tTo reorder your uploaded photos, select a photo and drag it where you'd like it to go.\\n\\t The first three photos are the most important, since they\\u2019ll be prominently displayed on your listing. Your first photo will appear in search results and will be the largest image displayed at the top of your listing.\\nAdd captions\\n\\n\\tYou can add captions to each photo by clicking on the blank white box underneath the image. Your text will save automatically when you click out of the box.\\nDelete photos\\n\\n\\tTo delete a photo, click the trash can icon in the top-right corner of the photo.\\n\\n\\tIf a photo you upload is facing the wrong direction, you\\u2019ll need to correct the orientation from your computer. After you\\u2019ve rotated the image and saved the file, re-upload the new image to your listing.", "question": "How do I add and reorder my listing\\u2019s photos?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tAlmost anyone can be a host! It's free to sign up and list your space. The listings available on the site are as diverse as the hosts who list them, so you can post airbeds in apartments, entire houses, rooms in bed-and-breakfasts, tree houses in the woods, boats on the water, or enchanted castles. Find out more about room types to see how to describe your space.\\n\\n\\n\\tYou can list your space in almost any location worldwide. While we would like to keep the Airbnb marketplace open to the entire world, we are required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries.\\n\\nWhy can't I use Airbnb from my location?\\n\\tAirbnb is required to comply with international regulations that restrict the use of our site by residents of certain countries. Because of this, our services are not available in Crimea, Iran, Sudan, Syria, and North Korea.", "question": "Who can host on Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb offers free professional photography to hosts in many cities. For more information, visit airbnb.com/photography.\\n\\nIf a photographer is available in your area, they'll reach out within a few days. While you wait for professional photography, we recommend uploading your own images. Check out our Top 5 Photo Tips for a Stellar Listing.\\n\\nOnce you have a photo shoot scheduled, here are some tips to help you prepare:\\n\\n  \\n    Open any blinds or curtains to allow natural light in\\n    Organize or put away objects that clutter your space, and remove any valuables you don't want photographed\\n    Think about how you might want to highlight amenities your guest will enjoy\\n    Make your bed with nice, clean sheets\\n    Tidy up surfaces and bedside tables\\n    Open the shower curtain, clean the bathroom mirror, and close the toilet lid\\n    Fold your guest towels\\n\\n\\n\\nIf you have questions at any point about your photography shoot or timing, please reach out to your photographer. If your photo shoot's scheduled time doesn't work, please remember that you must cancel at least 24 hours before your scheduled shoot. You can cancel your request in the Edit Photos section of your account.\\n\\nAfter your shoot, your images will go through an editing process and will go live in approximately 4 weeks.\\n\\nIf you don\\u2019t hear from a photographer within a week of submitting your professional photography request, we may not have someone available in your area at the time. If this happens, please try canceling and requesting again in the future.", "question": "How should I prepare for my professional photography session?"},
{"answer": "High-resolution photographs that showcase your space can help your listing stand out\\u2014and help guests know what to expect. To make it easier for hosts to get access to beautiful, professional photographs, Airbnb offers professional photography in many cities.\\n\\t\\n\\tVisit airbnb.com/photography to see if this service is available in your area.\\n\\t\\n\\tIf it is, you'll see your listings appear at the bottom of the page. Select the listings you'd like to have photographed and click Check Availability. If professional photography is available in your area, you:\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tMust have a verified telephone number and email address on your Airbnb profile.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tCan apply for photography for up to 4 individual listings. To apply for photography for 5 or more listings, you need to have at least an equivalent number of accepted reservations. For example, if you have 10 accepted reservations, you can apply for photography of up to 10 individual listings.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tCan only have a listing photographed once.\\n\\n\\nIf professional photography isn\\u2019t available in your area, or while you wait for professional photography, we recommend uploading your own images. Photos don\\u2019t have to be professional-quality to help give your guests a good sense of what to expect from your space.\\n\\nLearn more about preparing your space, and what happens after you request a shoot.", "question": "Where can I learn more about Airbnb's professional photography service?"},
{"answer": "To reschedule your professional photography shoot, you can send your photographer a message through the Airbnb messaging system\\u2014you should already have a message thread with them if you've been communicating to organize the shoot.\\n\\n\\tYou can also cancel the request from your account:\\n\\n  Go to Your Listing on airbnb.com\\n\\tUnder the listing you want to edit, click Manage Listing and Calendar\\n\\tClick Photos on the left\\n\\tClick Cancel request\\n\\n\\nIf you cancel through your account, it's a nice idea to follow up with your photographer via message thread as well, just to let them know that your plans have changed or that you'd like to reschedule.\\n\\nNote: You must give at least 24 hours notice if you need to change or cancel your appointment time.", "question": "How do I reschedule or cancel my photography shoot?"},
{"answer": "After you request a photo shoot, Airbnb reaches out to independent, third-party photographers to handle the request. We do our best to connect hosts with freelance photographers, but due to high demand, professional photographer availability can\\u2019t be guaranteed at all times.We recommend uploading your own images while you wait for professional photography.\\n\\nPlanning to make changes to the appearance of your listing soon? Please wait to request. If you already requested photography, learn how to cancel your request.\\n\\nIf a photographer is available\\nIf a photographer is available, they should reach out to you via the Airbnb messaging system within 7 days of your request. All Airbnb photographers have a verified badge on their profile. You'll also receive their contact information when they accept the assignment.\\n\\nOnce a photographer accepts the assignment, you'll work together to set up a time that suits you both. Be sure that your contact details are up to date and to schedule the shoot for a date when you don't have guests.\\n\\nPhoto shoot timing\\nA photography shoot of an apartment typically takes 30 minutes, while larger spaces can take up to an hour. Check with the photographer to see how much time they think they'll need for your home\\u2014setting aside enough time for the shoot will help ensure you get the best photos possible. You'll also want to clean and tidy up your space in preparation for the shoot.\\n\\nAfter the shoot\\nAfter your shoot, photos are typically uploaded, reviewed, and made public on the Airbnb site within 4 weeks. We review every photo taken by our photographers and only accept shoots that meet our standards. Occasionally, photos need to be sent back for additional post-processing and editing, which can take additional time, or we may need a second photo shoot to get quality images. \\n\\nNote: We can't provide copies of these photos because they're copyrighted by Airbnb.\\n\\nAirbnb will hold all rights (including copyright rights), title and interest in the resulting images, and Airbnb may use the resulting images for advertising, marketing, commercial and other purposes in any media or platform, whether in relation to your listing or otherwise.", "question": "What happens after I request professional photography?"},
{"answer": "High-quality photos are a great way to showcase your space and help set guests\\u2019 expectations.\\n  \\nHere are a few tips for taking your own photos: \\n\\n  A few photos are better than none: Start by some of your own photos when you create a new listing\\u2014cell phone photos are fine.\\n  Resolution matters: Take photos that are at least 1024 x 683px. When in doubt, a bigger photo is better.\\n  Take your photos in landscape format: Vertical photos won\\u2019t showcase your space as well.\\n  Set the scene: Clean up, remove clutter and pretend you\\u2019re preparing for your first guest.\\n  Take photos during the day: Open the blinds and turn on the lights to brighten your space.\\n  Highlight unique amenities: Guests love to stay in spaces with character. Consider including photos of your space's exterior, too.\\n\\nRead more about uploading and arranging your listing photos. You can also visit the Airbnb blog to get detailed tips for taking your own photos.\\n\\nIn some cities, we offer free professional photography for hosts. For more info visit airbnb.com/photography.", "question": "How can I make my listing photos look their best?"},
{"answer": "To make your listing public in search results and on your profile page: \\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to activate\\nSelect Listed in the drop-down menu on the bottom-left\\n\\n\\n\\nKeep in mind that once you change your status to listed, it can take up to an hour for this update to be reflected in search results.\\nIf you don\\u2019t want to receive any inquiries or requests, you can either snooze or deactivate your listing.", "question": "How do I activate my listing?"},
{"answer": "You can manage nightly pricing directly from your calendar:\\n            \\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nSelect the dates you want to edit\\nIn the window that appears on the right, you can set your nightly price\\n[Optional] Click Add note to enter private notes to yourself\\nClick Save Changes after you\\u2019ve made your changes\\n\\n\\nYour nightly rate will show for each available night. If you set weekend pricing or custom pricing those prices will show on the appropriate dates. Long-term pricing options will not be displayed.\\n\\n        \\n\\n        \\n\\n        \\n\\n\\n  Related articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n      How do I manage my availability on my calendar?\\n      How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?\\n      How do I change my reservation settings?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?"},
{"answer": "To set a minimum or maximum night requirement for reservations:\\n\\n                Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit\\n                Click Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view\\nUnder Reservation preferences, enter the minimum and/or maximum nights you require for a reservation              \\n\\n\\n\\nMinimum night requirement for weekends\\nTo require a minimum number of nights for reservations that include a Friday or a Saturday:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar for the listing you want to edit\\nClick Availability Settings in the top-right corner of your calendar view\\nUnder Reservation preferences, click the link below Minimum Stay \\nIn the dropdown, select Fridays or Saturdays \\nEnter the minimum number of nights you require for weekend reservations      \\nClick Save\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n      How do I manage my availability on my calendar?\\n      How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?\\n      How do I edit my pricing settings?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I set the minimum and maximum number of nights a guest can book?"},
{"answer": "If you add Internet or Wi-fi as an amenity, your listing will appear when people search and filter for places with Internet.\\n\\nWe encourage you to password protect your network. You should only share your password with guests only after they\\u2019ve confirmed their reservation. \\n\\nIt may be useful to tell guests that if they use your network, they agree to use it only for legal purposes and they promise not to use it for illegal uploading, downloading, or other illegal activities.\\n", "question": "What should I consider when offering Internet access to guests?"},
{"answer": "What is Instant Book?\\nInstant Book is a host setting which lets guests who meet your requirements automatically book your space. Instant Book will apply to all available dates on your calendar. \\n\\nBenefits of Instant Book\\n\\n  Convenience: Book guests without having to respond to each request.\\n  More guest interest: Guests can use filters to search for listings that can be booked instantly. Instant Book listings are more popular with guests since they\\u2019re able to more easily plan their trip. \\n  Search placement: Instant Book positively affects your response rate for your listing, which can improve your listing\\u2019s placement in search results.\\n  Superhost Status: Instant book can also help you reach Superhost status, which requires that you maintain a 90% response rate\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nInstant Book settings\\nPrepare to host\\nWhat are house manuals and house rules?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Learn about Instant Book"},
{"answer": "Dates that are available to book on your calendar are white. Unavailable dates are greyed out. You can manage your availability in your calendar:\\n            \\n\\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nSelect the dates you want to edit\\nIn the window that appears on the right, you can set your nightly price or make dates either Available or Blocked \\n[Optional] Click Add note to enter private notes to yourself\\nClick Save Changes after you\\u2019ve made your changes\\n\\n\\n        \\n\\n        \\n        Request and reservations\\nDates for pending requests and confirmed reservations will be automatically blocked on your calendar. Because one reservation could start in the second half of a day after a previous reservation ends, start and end dates of requests and reservations are partially filled.\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n      How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?\\n      How do I sync my Airbnb calendar with another calendar?\\n      How do I edit my pricing settings?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I manage my availability on my calendar?"},
{"answer": "Guests can filter search results by the items hosts have in the amenities section of their listing, so it's important to include everything you offer. \\n  \\n  \\n  To edit the amenities section of your listing:\\n  \\n    Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\n    Hover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\n    Under Amenities check the boxes that correspond to the amenities you provide\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I add amenities to my listing?"},
{"answer": "Guidebooks let hosts suggest local spots, like restaurants, grocery stores, parks, and attractions. If you add a Guidebook to your listing, your recommended places will appear on the map on your public listing page. \\nSome cities also have city guidebooks, which are combined lists of recommendations that hosts have added to their own guidebooks.\\nAdd a host guidebook to a listing\\nTo create your guidebook:\\n\\n  Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com.\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit.\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu.\\nClick Guidebook.\\nUnder a category, enter a business name or address of a favorites place.\\nWrite a short recommendation and any tags that apply.\\nClick Add.\\n\\nYou'll need to create a separate host guidebook for each of your listings. You can only create a host guidebook once you've completed the steps to list your space.\\nSince these guidebooks are public, you\\u2019ll have to remove your recommendations if you don\\u2019t want them to appear for all guests.\\n\\nEdit or delete a host guidebook\\nYou can edit or remove recommendations from your guidebook, or delete your guidebook altogether.\\n\\n  Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\nClick Guidebook\\nNext to the business you want to edit, click Edit\\nIf you want to remove the business, click Delete. Otherwise, you can edit your recommendation.\\n\\nTo delete your guidebook, you need to remove each recommendation individually.\\nHost recommendations in city guidebooks\\nWith city guidebooks, recommendations from host guidebooks are used to provide a detailed picture of what guests can do in that city. Three recommendations will be featured and will include a link to the host\\u2019s guidebook and listing. These featured recommendations will change over time.\\nTo determine which recommendations to use, our algorithms look at the most interesting content created around each location, based on informativeness, uniqueness, and representation of the place. We then show the most helpful recommendations which seem to provide the most compelling information for guests.\\nThe best way to be featured in city guidebooks is to continue expanding your own host guidebook with your favorite places in the area.\\nCan\\u2019t find a city guidebook \\nAt this time, not all cities have a city guidebook but we\\u2019re actively looking to add more. The best way to help your city get a guidebook is to expand your own host guidebook with your recommendations. Once enough hosts create robust guidebooks, this information can be gathered together in a city guidebook.\\nLeave feedback about guidebooks\\nIf you have any thoughts or concerns about guidebooks, you can provide us direct feedback. While not all feedback will make it to the site or receive a response, we encourage you to share your knowledge and opinions.", "question": "What's a Guidebook?"},
{"answer": "Your base price is your default nightly rate. To set your base price:\\n  \\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nSelect the listing you want to edit\\nGo to Pricing settings in the top right-hand corner of the page\\nUnder Base price enter your nightly price\\nSelect your currency from the dropdown\\n\\n\\n  Edits you make to your pricing only apply to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted.\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     How do I manage my availability on my calendar?\\n      How do I manage my pricing on my calendar?\\n      How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?\\n      How do I set prices for long-term stays?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "How do I set my nightly price?"},
{"answer": "Nightly pricing\\nYou can set custom prices for any individual night or set of nights.\\n\\n\\nGo to Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nSelect any upcoming day or set of days\\nSet your nightly rate\\nClick Save changes\\n\\nYou\\u2019ll see your custom nightly prices on your calendar.\\n\\t\\nPricing for specific weeks or months\\n\\n  You can account for seasonal demand or local events like a conference or festival by setting custom prices for specific weeks or months. \\n  \\nSelect the listing you want to edit\\nGo to Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner\\nUnder Long-term prices, click the link to set custom weekly or monthly rates\\nSet your custom weekly or monthly rates\\nSave by clicking Apply\\n\\nCustom weekly and monthly prices will override your normal nightly, weekly, and monthly prices, as well as custom nightly prices you\\u2019ve saved on your calendar.\\nIf you have custom pricing set for specific weeks or months you'll see a notification on your Pricing page, in the Long-term pricing section.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related Articles\\n\\n  \\n     How do I use my calendar to check pricing and availability?\\n      How do I edit my pricing and availability on my calendar?\\n      How do I edit my pricing settings?\\n      How do I set prices for long-term stays?\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I set custom or seasonal pricing?"},
{"answer": "Set weekend pricing to change your nightly price for every Friday night and Saturday night.\\n\\tSet weekend pricing\\n\\tTo change your nightly price for Fridays and Saturdays:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick Manage Listing and Calendar on the listing you want to edit\\nHover on the left side of the page to open the menu\\n\\tSelect Pricing\\n\\tUnder Additional Pricing Options, check the box for Weekend Pricing and enter your nightly price.\\n\\n\\nThere are a few things to know about weekend pricing:\\n\\nYou can remove weekend pricing at any time simply by un-checking the box. If you turn weekend pricing off, prices on Friday and Saturday nights revert to your base price.\\nPending and accepted reservations are not affected by pricing changes, since your guest has already submitted their payment information.\\n\\n\\nCustom pricing\\nAny custom weekly and monthly prices you set after turning on weekend pricing will not be overriden. However, if you turn on weekend pricing after setting custom prices, weekend pricing will replace all Friday and Saturday nightly prices on your calendar.", "question": "How do I set up weekend pricing?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\n\\n\\nAdditional Fees\\n\\nCleaning fee: You can either incorporate a cleaning fee into your nightly price or you can add a cleaning fee in your pricing settings.\\nOther fees: To charge extra fees outside of your rates (like a late check-in fee, pet fee, or bike rental fee), you must first disclose these potential charges to guests prior to booking and then use the Resolution Center to securely request payment for additional fees. Airbnb is not responsible for the collection of payments on your behalf that are not incorporated into your pricing.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I set my base price?\\n\\nHow do I add a cleaning fee to my listing?\\n\\nHow do I set custom or seasonal pricing?\\n\\nHow do I set up weekend pricing?\\n\\nSmart Pricing: Set prices based on demand\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How much should I charge for my listing?"},
{"answer": "\\nYou can set your listing\\u2019s price to automatically adapt to changes in demand with Smart Pricing. If you turn on Smart Pricing, you instruct the tool to automatically adjust your daily prices within the minimum and maximum price range you have chosen. Adjustments are based on supply and demand in your area for that date, your listing\\u2019s features, location, amenities, booking history, and availability. \\nTurn on Smart Pricing\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nSelect the listing you want to edit\\nLook for Try Smart Pricing\\nSet your minimum price, which is the lowest nightly price you want to charge \\nSet your maximum price, which is the highest nightly price you want to charge\\nSelect how often you\\u2019d like to host\\nUnder Smart Pricing, toggle to turn on\\n\\nOnce you turn on Smart Pricing, your prices will be automatically updated within the parameters you set. Smart Pricing works for all open nights on your calendar, and you can still set custom prices for specific days.\\n\\n\\nTurn off Smart Pricing \\nYou can always go back to your previous prices or edit your prices. To turn off Smart Pricing:\\n\\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nSelect the listing you want to edit\\nClick Pricing Settings on the right hand corner of the page\\nUnder Smart Pricing, toggle to turn off\\n\\n", "question": "Smart Pricing: Set prices based on demand"},
{"answer": "Tips to get your listing ready\\n\\nKeep an updated calendar so that you\\u2019ll only get bookings when you\\u2019re available.\\nUse your calendar settings to control when and for how long guests can book your space, when guests can arrive, and to add preparation time between reservations. \\nImport and sync other calendars you use for your space.\\nDecide whether you\\u2019d like all of your guests to have verified their ID before they\\u2019re able to book your space.\\nWrite check-in instructions and include contact information, wifi passwords, your neighborhood guide, house rules, and any other vital information guests need to get situated and comfortable.\\n\\nTips to get your home ready\\n\\nProvide a way for guests to access keys and check in even when you\\u2019re not around. \\nBulk-buy amenity items you offer guests. Soap, bottled water, or snacks are a good start. \\nA few sets of sheets and towels will help you ready your space quickly without having to deal with laundry.\\nConsider getting professional help with cleaning and management. Many hosts include a small cleaning fee to offset the cost of hiring a professional. \\nGet to know your guests before they arrive by checking out profiles or starting a conversation to set the tone for their stay.\\n", "question": "Prepare to host"},
{"answer": "Instant Book lets guests who meet your requirements and agree to your house rules to book your space without requesting approval. \\n     Booking settings\\nYou can use Guest requirements and House rules to set requirements for guests that book your space. \\n\\nIn addition to Airbnb's requirements, you can also require guests to provide Airbnb with a government-issued ID and/or a 4.5 out of 5 star rating, including cleanliness and communication.\\n\\nGuests will need to agree to your House Rules before booking. If you feel like you are ever uncomfortable with your guests\\u2019 behavior, you can cancel penalty-free.\\n\\nAvailability settings\\nYou can use Reservation preferences and Calendar sync to help you manage when guests can book, how much advance notice you need, and whether you want time blocked before or between reservations.", "question": "What is Instant Book?"},
{"answer": "What is Instant Book?\\nInstant Book is a host setting which lets guests who meet your requirements automatically book your space. Instant Book will apply to all available dates on your calendar. \\n\\nBenefits of Instant Book\\n\\n  Convenience: Book guests without having to respond to each request.\\n  More guest interest: Guests can use filters to search for listings that can be booked instantly. Instant Book listings are more popular with guests since they\\u2019re able to more easily plan their trip. \\n  Search placement: Instant Book positively affects your response rate for your listing, which can improve your listing\\u2019s placement in search results.\\n  Superhost Status: Instant book can also help you reach Superhost status, which requires that you maintain a 90% response rate\\n\\n\\nRelated Content\\n \\n\\nInstant Book settings\\nPrepare to host\\nWhat are house manuals and house rules?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Learn about Instant Book"},
{"answer": "If you want to see the status of your reservation, you can find your status in your Inbox on the right side of the message thread with the guest or host.\\nOnce you\\u2019ve found your status, you can see the details of the status below.\\nReservation statuses\\nInquiry: A guest sent a message to a host about certain dates, but hasn't submitted a reservation request. In response, the host can send a message, pre-approve, send a Special Offer, or decline the dates of the inquiry.\\nReservation Request: A guest sent a message to a host by submitting a booking request for specific dates. In response, the host will need to either accept or decline the request within 24 hours before it expires.\\nPending: A guest is waiting for a host to respond to a reservation request. The host has 24 hours to respond before the request expires.\\nConfirmed: A host accepted a guest's reservation request or the request was accepted automatically with Instant Book. Airbnb has collected full payment from the guest and the booking is complete.\\nDeclined: A host declined a guest's reservation request. No charge is made to the guest.\\nExpired: A host took more than 24 hours to respond to a pending reservation request. If the host wants to accommodate the expired request, the host will have to send a pre-approval or Special Offer, or the guest will need to send another reservation request.\\nCanceled: A host or guest canceled a confirmed reservation.\\nPre-Approval: A guest has contacted the host about specific dates and the host has responded by inviting them to book the dates. If the guest accepts the pre-approval request within 24 hours, their reservation will be confirmed.\\nSpecial Offer: A guest has contacted the host about specific dates and the host has responded by inviting them to book the dates with a different price than what is listed on their calendar. If the guest accepts the special offer within 24 hours, their reservation will be confirmed.\\nAwaiting Payment: A host chose to accept a guest's reservation request, but the guest's payment didn\\u2019t go through. The guest has 24 hours to successfully update their payment information for the reservation to be accepted. Otherwise, the reservation will be canceled without penalty.\\nAction Required: A guest submitted a reservation request to a host who requires they complete Verified ID, and they haven't completed the process yet. The request is on hold until Verified ID has been confirmed.\\nClosed: The guest is no longer looking for a place to stay for the dates they requested.\\nNot Possible: A guest contacted a host about specific dates and the host responded with a Special Offer or pre-approval, but some or all of the dates are no longer available on the host's calendar.", "question": "What does each reservation status mean?"},
{"answer": "Guests want high-quality, accurate listings with hosts that offer and good trip experiences. Here are a few things you can do to make your listing stand out.\\n\\nComplete each section of your listing\\nA complete listing helps guests know what to expect from your space. Make sure you:\\n\\nDescribe your space: Make your title and description attractive, detailed, and informative. Clearly explain what makes your space unique, including any amenities you offer or rules you have. \\nUpload high-quality photos: Your photos are the guest\\u2019s first impression of your space on the search results page. \\nSet expectations: Lay out expectations for guests in the House Rules and House Manual sections of your listing. \\n\\n\\nUse your reviews to improve\\nThe quantity and quality of reviews from past guests can impact your search performance. Use your reviews and ratings to learn how you can improve your guest\\u2019s experience. \\n\\nMake it easier for guests to book\\nRespond quickly to booking inquiries and reservation requests to show guests that you\\u2019ll be an attentive, welcoming host.\\n\\nTurning on Instant Book can also help attract last-minute reservations.\\n\\nSet a competitive rates\\nTake a look at what other hosts in your area are charging and use a similar price. Set seasonal pricing to help your listing stay competitive during the off-season. \\n\\nLearn from other hosts\\nTrade tips with other hosts\\u2014Find a meetup in your area so that you can ask other hosts about how they stand out during slow months.\\n\\nRead more about how to optimize your listing for the off-season.", "question": "How do I make my listing more competitive?"},
{"answer": "If you\\u2019re having trouble getting in touch with your guest before their arrival you may want to try contacting them using a different form of communication. For example, you can try reaching them through:\\n\\nAirbnb message: Find your guest in your Messages and send them a note\\nEmail or phone: Go to Your Reservations, click on the reservation, and use the email address or phone number listed\\n\\nKeep in mind that many guests don\\u2019t have access to a phone or have an alternate phone number while traveling, or they may also be in-transit or encountering travel delays that will affect their arrival time.\\n\\nIf your guest decides to cancel or not show up for an active reservation, we\\u2019ll uphold your cancellation policy, and your payout will be released 24 hours after the originally scheduled check-in. A reservation is active if the reservation status is Accepted in Your Reservations.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nCancel a reservation as a host\\nWhere do I find information about my payouts?\\nWhen do I get paid?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What if I my guest doesn\\u2019t show up for their reservation?"},
{"answer": "Your response rate and response time measure how quickly and consistently you respond to inquiries and requests. You can view your response rate in your Dashboard in the Pending section. \\n\\nCalculating response rate and response time\\nYour response rate is the percentage of new inquiries and reservation requests you responded to within 24 hours in the past 30 days. Your response time is the average amount of time it took you to respond to all the new messages in the past 30 days.\\nIf you\\u2019ve received fewer than 10 new message threads in the past 30 days, your response rate and response time will be based on the 10 most recent message threads from the past 90 days.\\nThe response rate to determine Superhost status is calculated differently and is based on your responses over the past 365 days. \\nImproving response rate and response time\\n\\nDoing one of the following within 24 hours improves your response rate and response time: \\n\\nAccepting or declining a reservation request\\nSending a message back to a guest who has sent a reservation request or a booking inquiry\\nPre-approving or declining a trip described in a booking inquiry\\n\\n\\nResponses after 24 hours count as a late response, which will decrease your response rate and increase your response time. Your response rate can impact your position in search results. \\n\\nYour response rate and response time aren\\u2019t affected by follow-up messages between hosts and guests. You don't have to send the final message in a conversation to maintain your response rate.", "question": "How are my response rate and response time calculated?"},
{"answer": "We don't share your personal email address even after you have a confirmed reservation. Instead, we create a unique, temporary Airbnb address for you, and share that with your host or guest. Keeping your real personal email address hidden helps protect your privacy, and prevent unwanted communication from people who may abuse our system.\\n\\nAny emails sent to your temporary Airbnb address are forwarded to your personal email address. This lets you use your email provider to send or reply to messages, attach files (up to 15 MB), and include links.\\n\\nA host's anonymized email address might look like:\\n\\n\\tPersonal email address: john.lastname@exampleemail.com\\n\\tTemporary Airbnb address: john-abc123xyz@host.airbnb.com\\n\\nA guest's anonymized email address might look like:\\n\\n\\tPersonal email address: jane.lastname@exampleemail.com\\n\\tTemporary Airbnb address: jane-def456@guest.airbnb.com\\n\\n\\nWe recommend communicating using the Airbnb messaging system, but we recognize that sometimes you'll need to attach photos, directions, or other information in an email. These addresses let you send emails like your normally would\\u2014with an extra layer of security.", "question": "How will my email address look to other people?"},
{"answer": "Typically, Airbnb only releases contact information for hosts and guests after a reservation is confirmed. \\nIf a guest requests a viewing of your space before they book, encourage them to review your listing description and photos, and be available to answer any additional questions they have about your space.\\nReservation and payment also needs to be made directly through the Airbnb platform. This helps ensure that you're protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation and refund policies, Host Guarantee, Host Protection Insurance program, and other safeguards.", "question": "What should I do if a guest wants to see my place before booking?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb allows designated people at companies enrolled in Airbnb for Business to book business trips on behalf of other people\\u2014these people are called bookers.\\n\\nWhen a booker books a trip for someone else, the booker handles the reservation request, introductions, and payment for the reservation\\u2014then they transfer responsibility for the trip to your guest. Once a reservation is accepted, both the booker and your guest join the message thread with the host and receive all trip communication.\\n\\nIf you're a host, you'll see booked by and booked for in your communications with the booker and your guest.\\n\\nRead more about bookers and Airbnb for Business.\\n\\nPersonal travel\\nWe require Airbnb reservations booked for personal travel to be booked by the person who's going to stay at the listing.", "question": "Who can book trips on behalf of someone else?"},
{"answer": "You can decline any booking inquiries or reservations that you can\\u2019t accommodate, but you should do so within 24 hours. Whether you accept or decline, the amount of time it takes you to respond to requests is factored into your response rate.\\n\\nWhen you decline a reservation request, you can choose to keep the calendar dates blocked or make them available for someone else to book. Update your calendar regularly so you only receive reservation requests for when you're able to host.\\n\\nIf you change your mind and would like to accommodate a reservation you declined, ask the guest to send a new request, or send them a Special Offer or pre-approval.", "question": "Can I decline booking inquires or reservation requests?"},
{"answer": "Messaging on Airbnb starts when a guest makes an inquiry or reservation request. Afterward, all messages related to that inquiry or reservation request will appear in your inbox.\\nView or send a message\\n        \\n            On airbnb.com, go to your Messages\\n            In your inbox, you'll see a message thread for each inquiry or reservation. \\n            Click on a message thread to view old messages or send a new one.\\n        \\n        You must be logged in to your Airbnb account to view or send messages, and you can only send 30 messages within any 24-hour period.\\n    \\n     \\n    To remove a message from your inbox\\n        \\n          \\n            Go to your Messages\\n            In your inbox, you'll see a message thread for each inquiry or reservation. \\n            Hover over the message thread you'd like to remove and select Archive.\\n        \\nIf a message makes you feel uncomfortable or someone tries to get you to pay outside Airbnb, click the  next to it to let us know.\\nMessage Threads\\nWhen you click on a message, you can view the conversation and also the following information:\\n\\n  Host or guest profiles including number of reviews, verifications, and description.\\n  Reservation and payment details such as date of inquiry, number of guests, and price breakdown.\\n  Events such as reservation confirmation, pre-approvals, and special offers are notated in the timeline of the conversations.\\n  If any actions are needed from you, you\\u2019ll see the prompt at the top of the page, above the conversation. Guests can make booking inquiries or reservation requests, and hosts will be able to accept or decline requests. \\n   Hosts will see what the guest pays and what they will earn. They will also be able to see a snapshot of their calendar.\\n", "question": "How do I view and send messages?"},
{"answer": "Your safety and comfort are always a priority. If you find that a guest isn't a fit for your space or hosting style, you can decline their reservation request or cancel the reservation.\\n    \\n    Before you've accepted a reservation\\n    \\n    We encourage you to take advantage of the safety features we've built to help give you peace of mind and help you get to know potential guests.\\n    \\n    Declining an individual reservation request won't negatively impact your listing's placement in search results\\u2014however, if you decline many or most reservation requests, your search result placement may be negatively impacted.\\n\\n    After you've accepted a reservation\\n    \\n    If you've already accepted the reservation, you can cancel it. You may be subject to cancellation penalties.\\n    \\n    You won't be eligible for Superhost status if you cancel a confirmed reservation\\u2014unless it\\u2019s under extenuating circumstances.\\n    \\n    Flagging inappropriate messages\\n        \\n        If a message from a guest makes you uncomfortable, let us know by flagging it. To flag a message, open the message thread and click the flag icon  next to the message you want to flag to Airbnb for review.\\n        \\n        \\n\\n        \\n \\n\\nRemember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What should I do if I'm uncomfortable hosting someone?"},
{"answer": "Host Assist is a collection of apps that can help you share your space with ease. These apps are offered by companies who have partnered with Airbnb. \\n\\nCurrently, Host Assist apps are only offered in select locations. If there are any apps available to you, you\\u2019ll be able to see a Host Assist section near the top of the page, after navigating to your Airbnb dashboard.  \\n\\nFrom there, you\\u2019ll be able to see which apps are available for each of your listings and sign up for the ones you\\u2019re interested in using.", "question": "Host Assist and how to sign up"},
{"answer": "Yes. Some hosts require guests to sign contracts or rental agreements prior to check-in.\\nFor hosts\\nIf you require guests to sign a contract, you must disclose the actual contract terms to them prior to booking. The easiest way to do this is to mention the contract in your listing's description, and include the terms in your message thread with the guest.\\nAirbnb can't help enforce any special policies in your contract.\\nFor guests\\nHosts may ask you to sign a contract, but they must disclose this requirement and its terms prior to booking.\\nIf you\\u2019re not comfortable with the contract, you may want to discuss your concerns with the host or look for another place to stay.\\nIf your host asks you to sign a contract that you weren\\u2019t notified about before you made the reservation, you can decline to sign the contract and ask your host to cancel your reservation instead.", "question": "Can hosts ask guests to sign a contract?"},
{"answer": "You have 24 hours to accept or decline a reservation request before it expires. While a request is pending, the dates are automatically blocked on your calendar, so other guests can\\u2019t request them.\\n\\nYou can set up alerts on your mobile phone to get notified of reservation requests instantly.\\n\\nAccept or decline the reservation\\n\\nAccept or decline the reservation on your desktop or from your mobile app. You can also message the guest to review trip details before accepting or declining their request. A message doesn\\u2019t count as a response to a request. \\n\\nIf you accept, we\\u2019ll automatically update your calendar and schedule your payout for 24 hours after check-in. \\n\\nIf you decline, you may want to update your calendar to avoid receiving other requests for the same dates.\\n\\n\\nExpired reservation requests\\n\\n  \\n  \\n    \\n     If you don\\u2019t accept or decline a request within 24 hours it expires.\\n    \\nIf you\\u2019re still interested in hosting the guest, you can send a Special Offer .", "question": "What do I do after I receive a reservation request?"},
{"answer": "Special Offers allow you to set a custom price for a guest who has sent you a booking inquiry. Only send a Special Offer if you are ready to confirm a reservation. \\nSend a Special Offer\\nTo send a guest a Special Offer:\\n\\nGo to Your Messages on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message from the guest you want to send a Special Offer to \\nClick Send special offer\\nOn the left side of the page, in the Subtotal field, enter the price you\\u2019d like to offer your guest for their stay (be sure to include cleaning fee or your additional guest fee in this subtotal) \\nClick Send special offer\\n\\n\\nOnce you\\u2019ve sent a guest a Special Offer, we'll notify them. If the guest accepts the Special Offer, the reservation will automatically be confirmed.\\n\\nThere are a few things to know about Special Offers:\\n\\nA Special Offer doesn\\u2019t block dates on your calendar until after it is accepted by your guest.\\nIf you don't see the option to send a Special Offer, check that the dates on your calendar aren't blocked or that you don't have any pending reservation requests for the same dates. If you have a pending request from another guest, you'll need to decline it before you can send a Special Offer.\\nYou can offer multiple guests a Special Offer for the same dates until someone books. We recommend being open and transparent with your potential guests that other guests may be interested in the same dates.\\n\\nIf you have a security deposit on your listing, it will be handled as normal and you do not need to add it to your Special Offer total.\\n\\n\\nConfirmed reservations\\nIf the guest has already submitted a reservation request or confirmed a reservation, you won't have the option to send a Special Offer. You can still change the details on an existing reservation by changing the reservation.  \\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I cancel or remove a Special Offer?\\nChange a reservation as a host\\n\\n  \\n\\n\\n", "question": "How do I send a guest a Special Offer?"},
{"answer": "You can still make changes or cancel a Special Offer as long as a guest hasn't accepted it.\\n\\nCancel a Special Offer\\n\\nTo cancel a Special Offer:\\n\\nGo to Your Messages on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message from the guest you sent a Special Offer to \\nClick Remove Special Offer within the message thread\\n\\n\\n\\nEdit a Special Offer\\n\\nTo edit a Special Offer:\\n\\nGo to Your Messages on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message from the guest you sent a Special Offer to \\nOn the left side of the page under Payment click Send special offer\\nIn the Subtotal field, enter the new price you\\u2019d like to offer your guest for their stay (be sure to include cleaning fee or your additional guest fee in this subtotal) \\nClick Send special offer\\n\\n\\nIf the guest has already booked your place, use the alterations tool to make changes to accepted reservations.", "question": "How do I edit or remove a Special Offer?"},
{"answer": "Remove a pre-approval\\n\\nIf a guest hasn\\u2019t accepted a pre-approval and your situation has changed, you can remove a pre-approval. At the moment, you can only remove a pre-approval on a computer.\\n\\nGo to your Inbox  on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message thread with the guest\\nClick Remove Pre-approval\\n\\n\\nYou can't edit a pre-approval. If a guest wants to change their travel dates, they'll need to request a reservation for those dates.\\nWhy can\\u2019t I send a pre-approval?\\n\\nIf you don't see the option to pre-approve a guest, it means that your calendar is blocked for some or all of the guest\\u2019s reservation dates. \\n\\nTo send a pre-approval, edit your calendar to reflect that your listing is available.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\n  How do I pre-approve a guest?\\nWhat is a pre-approval?\\nHow do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest?\\nWhat does each reservation status mean?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I remove a pre-approval that I've sent to a guest?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tA pre-approval is a way for host to let guests know that their listing is available when asked about a potential reservation. Once pre-approved, the guest can automatically confirm a booking for the specific dates provided.\\n\\n\\tHosts\\n\\nWhen you pre-approve a guest\\u2019s inquiry, you give them permission to automatically confirm a booking for specific dates. The dates won\\u2019t be blocked on your calendar, so you can pre-approve multiple guests at one time. \\n\\n\\n\\tGuests have 24 hours to confirm a booking that has been pre-approved. After 24 hours, the guest can still request to book your listing with the price offered during the pre-approval, unless you remove the pre-approval. You can remove the pre-approval at any time in the message thread.\\n\\n\\tGuests\\n\\n\\tIf a host has sent you a pre-approval, your booking isn\\u2019t confirmed until you\\u2019ve clicked Book It in the message thread with the host and added your payment information. Hosts can send pre-approvals to many potential guests, so if you\\u2019ve found the perfect space, make sure to complete the booking process as soon as possible. \\nYou have 24 hours to accept a pre-approval before it expires. If 24 hours have passed, you can still accept the pre-approval but your host will have to approve your request before your reservation is confirmed.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I pre-approve a guest\\u2019s stay or remove a pre-approval?\\nHow do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is a pre-approval?"},
{"answer": "When you send a pre-approval, you\\u2019re giving the guest 24 hours to confirm a reservation without requiring any further action from you. \\n\\nYou should only send a pre-approval if you\\u2019re ready to confirm a reservation. If the guest books your space within 24 hours, the reservation will be confirmed automatically. \\n\\nPre-approve a guest\\n\\nGo to your Inbox  on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message thread with the guest\\nClick Pre-approve\\nIf you pre-approve multiple guests for the same dates, let each guest know that there are other people interested in booking\\n\\n\\nThere are a couple of things to know about pre-approvals:\\n\\nYour listing\\u2019s calendar is still marked as available when you pre-approve a guest. \\nYou can offer multiple guests a pre-approval for the same dates. Once the space is filled, other guests will be automatically notified. \\nGuests have 24 hours to accept your pre-approval before it expires.\\n Once a pre-approval expires, the guest will need to send another inquiry or request in order to book. The new inquiry or request will still reflect the price from the original pre-approval. You have to retract your original pre-approval for new prices to be reflected.  \\nPre-approvals do not override your reservation requirements.\\n\\nRemove a pre-approval\\n\\nIf a guest hasn\\u2019t accepted a pre-approval and your situation has changed, you can remove a pre-approval. At the moment, you can only remove a pre-approval on a computer.\\n\\nGo to your Inbox  on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message thread with the guest\\nClick Remove Pre-approval\\n\\nWhy can\\u2019t I send a pre-approval?\\n\\nIf you don't see the option to pre-approve a guest, it means that your calendar is blocked for some or all of the guest\\u2019s reservation dates. \\n\\nTo send a pre-approval, edit your calendar to reflect that your listing is available.\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nWhat is a pre-approval?\\nHow do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest?\\nWhat does each reservation status mean?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I pre-approve a guest?"},
{"answer": "You can see if your listing is showing up in search results by checking the number of views your listing has:\\n\\nGo to your Stats on airbnb.com\\nUnder Views, you can check how many times your listing was viewed by Search Date\\n\\n\\n Search for your listing\\nYou can also see how your listing appears in search results by searching for it yourself. Keep in mind that each guest will see different results when searching based on the preferences they add, their past booking history, and other search criteria.\\n\\n\\nGo to airbnb.com and enter the location of your listing\\nSelect dates that you\\u2019ve confirmed are available and that fit within your calendar settings and requirements\\nSelect the number of guests that your listing can accommodate and click Search\\nOn the results page, use search filters to narrow down to a set of listings you can easily look through to find your own\\n \\n\\nKeep in mind that the location pins on the map are approximate, so that people don\\u2019t know exactly where a listing is until they have confirmed a reservation.", "question": "How do I confirm that guests can see my listing?"},
{"answer": "At a high-level, the factors that affect search ranking can be broken down into the following categories: listing quality, trip experience, ease of booking, and guest preferences. As a host, you have control over many of these factors. Learn more about  making your listing more competitive.\\nKeep in mind that each guest will see different results when searching based on the preferences they add, their past booking history, and other search criteria.\\n  Listing quality\\n  The way you list your space and how well you look after your guests impacts where you appear in search compared to other listings.\\n  \\n    Booking appeal: If guests frequently click through to your listing page or try to book your space, this can also positively affect your placement in search. High-quality photos that accurately depict your space can attract interest from guests. \\nReviews: Both the quantity and quality of reviews from past guests can impact your search performance. \\n  \\n  Ease of booking\\nHow reliably and easily guests can book your space impacts search results.\\n\\n  Response rate and response time: The quicker and more consistently you respond to guests, the better your listing can do in search. Search also considers how many guests you accept. Rejecting a large number of requests, or failing to respond to inquiries will affect your placement and visibility in search.\\n Cancellations: If you do cancel on a guest, it can negatively impact where your listing appears in search.\\n\\nGuest preferences\\nSearch results may vary depending on the person, their preferences, and the specifics of their trip.\\n\\n  Location relevance: Guests can search broadly at the city level or narrow into specific neighborhoods, so we try to show search results that are most relevant to their location preferences. We may use past booking information to determine which locations are most relevant for a given search. On mobile, guests can specify travel preferences such as neighborhood types (for example, \\u201cquiet\\u201d or \\u201cscenic\\u201d). If they specify these preferences, they\\u2019ll still see \\u201cPopular\\u201d listings as well based on our existing ranking factors.\\n\\nPersonalized results: We try to understand a guest\\u2019s preferences and trip characteristics, so search results may vary depending on the person or the specifics of their trip.\\n\\nWe understand that new hosts may not have had a chance to get many inquiries and bookings yet, so we also take this into account.", "question": "How are search results determined?"},
{"answer": "If you're a host, you can share your listing through different social media platforms or embed a preview of your listing on your website to reach people beyond those searching on Airbnb.\\n    \\n    Share your listing on social media\\n    To share your listing on Facebook, Pinterest, Google+, or Twitter:\\n      \\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick the name of the listing you want to share\\nOn your listing's page, under Save to Wishlist click ... More.\\nSelect the social media platform you want to use and follow the steps to share\\n\\n\\n    \\n        \\n    \\nEmbed a preview of your listing\\n    If you have your own website, you can embed a preview of your listing:\\n    \\n    \\nGo to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nClick the name of the listing you want to embed\\nOn your listing's page, under Save to Wishlist click ... More.\\nSelect Embed this listing\\n      Click Copy HTML in the preview window to save the HTML to your clipboard\\n      Paste the HTML code into your website where you\\u2019d like your listing preview to appear.\\n", "question": "How can I share or embed my listing on other websites?"},
{"answer": "If you need to cancel a guest\\u2019s reservation:\\n  \\nOn your computer\\n\\nGo to Your Reservations on airbnb.com\\nFind the reservation you need to cancel\\nSelect Change or Cancel to start the cancellation process\\n\\nOn the Airbnb app\\n\\nGo to Host Home section of the mobile app\\nSelect the reservation you need to cancel\\nTap Cancel Reservation to start the cancellation process\\n\\n\\n\\nOn mobile browser\\nYou can\\u2019t currently cancel a reservation on Airbnb's mobile website. Use your desktop computer or download our iPhone or Android app to cancel a reservation.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nCancellation Penalties\\nCanceling a guest's reservation can have serious implications on their trip, so penalties will be applied unless there is an extenuating circumstance.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nHow do the cancellation penalties work?\\n\\nWhat is the Guest Refund Policy?\\nExtenuating Circumstances for Host Cancellations\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Cancel a reservation as a host"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tIf you're a host, you can always see and update the cancellation policy for your listing. The cancellation policy is automatically set as Flexible when you list your space.\\n\\tView or change policy\\n\\tTo view or change your cancellation policy:\\n\\t\\n\\t  On airbnb.com, go to Your Listings\\n\\t   Next to the listing you want information for, click Manage Listing and Calendar\\n\\t  On the left side of the screen, click Check-in and your policy will be listed\\n\\t\\n\\tNote: The Check-in section only appears as an option after you complete the required steps and list your space.\\n\\n\\tIf you update your cancellation policy, it only applies to reservations booked after you make the changes. Changes do not apply to upcoming reservations that were already accepted. \\n\\tAvailable cancellation policies\\n\\tThere are a few cancellation policies you can choose from:\\n\\t\\n      Flexible: full refund up until 1 day prior to arrival, except fees.\\n      \\n      \\n\\tModerate: full refund up until 5 days prior to arrival, except fees.\\n\\n\\tStrict: 50% refund up until 1 week prior to arrival, except fees.\\n\\t\\n\\n\\n\\tThere are additional policies that are only available to select hosts:\\n\\n\\n\\tSuper Strict: 50% refund up until 30 days prior to arrival, except fees.\\xa0Available by invitation only\\xa0and\\xa0requires an increased host fee of 5%.\\n\\tSuper Strict 60 Days: 50% refund up until 60 days prior to arrival, except fees.\\xa0Available by invitation only and also requires an increased host fee of 5%.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\tFor all long-term reservations (28 nights or more), the Long Term policy is automatically applied:\\n\\n\\tLong Term: first month down payment, 30-day notice for lease termination. Automatically applied to all reservations of 28 nights or more.\\n\\t\\n\\n\\tIf your guest cancels the reservation, your payout is determined by the cancellation policy you had in place at the time of booking. You can refund your guests more than the policy allows.", "question": "How can I see or change the cancellation policy for my listing?"},
{"answer": "If your guest changes a long-term reservation with less than 30 days notice, you have the option to either enforce or waive your cancellation policy. \\n\\nIf you enforce your cancellation policy: \\n\\nYour guest is charged for the remaining nights of the original reservation up to 30 nights from the date of the alteration request \\nYour cancellation policy is immediately reinstated after the alteration is accepted\\nYour calendar will be updated with the new dates\\n\\n\\nIf you waive your cancellation policy: \\n\\nYour guest is only charged for the actual nights stayed \\nYour cancellation policy is only waived temporarily to allow for the alteration, but it\\u2019s not waived for the entire reservation \\nYour cancellation policy is immediately reinstated after the alteration is accepted\\nYour calendar is updated according to the new dates\\n\\n\\nIf your guest alters the dates of a long-term reservation with more than 30 days notice, you won't see the option to accept or decline the alteration request since the long-term cancellation policy already covers those 30 nights. \\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nCan a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?\\nLong-term Cancellation Policy\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What does it mean to enforce or waive my cancellation policy?"},
{"answer": "If you need to make a change to a confirmed reservation, you can submit a change request to your guest.\\n\\nChange a reservation\\n\\nGo to Your Reservations on airbnb.com.\\nClick Change or Cancel next to the reservation you want to change.\\nChoose Change Reservation.\\nClick Submit Alteration.\\n\\n If the guest accepts your request, the reservation will be updated and they'll be charged or refunded if necessary. If the request is declined or you don\\u2019t receive a response, the reservation will stay the same.\\n\\n\\nThere are a couple of other things to know about submitting change requests:\\n\\nYour chosen cancellation policy will apply based on the new dates.\\nIf the dates of the reservation have already passed, you can\\u2019t make any changes to the reservation.\\nIf you want to change the details of your requested changes, you\\u2019ll have to repeat the steps above and remove your request, and then submit a new one.\\nIf you changed your pricing, the new reservation will reflect this pricing if your change request is accepted.\\nTo request additional funds from your guest, you can do so directly from the Resolutions Center.\\n", "question": "Can I change a reservation as a host?"},
{"answer": "Remove a pre-approval\\n\\nIf a guest hasn\\u2019t accepted a pre-approval and your situation has changed, you can remove a pre-approval. At the moment, you can only remove a pre-approval on a computer.\\n\\nGo to your Inbox  on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message thread with the guest\\nClick Remove Pre-approval\\n\\n\\nYou can't edit a pre-approval. If a guest wants to change their travel dates, they'll need to request a reservation for those dates.\\nWhy can\\u2019t I send a pre-approval?\\n\\nIf you don't see the option to pre-approve a guest, it means that your calendar is blocked for some or all of the guest\\u2019s reservation dates. \\n\\nTo send a pre-approval, edit your calendar to reflect that your listing is available.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\n  How do I pre-approve a guest?\\nWhat is a pre-approval?\\nHow do I book a pre-approval or special offer as a guest?\\nWhat does each reservation status mean?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I remove a pre-approval that I've sent to a guest?"},
{"answer": "Your safety and comfort are always a priority. If you find that a guest isn't a fit for your space or hosting style, you can decline their reservation request or cancel the reservation.\\n    \\n    Before you've accepted a reservation\\n    \\n    We encourage you to take advantage of the safety features we've built to help give you peace of mind and help you get to know potential guests.\\n    \\n    Declining an individual reservation request won't negatively impact your listing's placement in search results\\u2014however, if you decline many or most reservation requests, your search result placement may be negatively impacted.\\n\\n    After you've accepted a reservation\\n    \\n    If you've already accepted the reservation, you can cancel it. You may be subject to cancellation penalties.\\n    \\n    You won't be eligible for Superhost status if you cancel a confirmed reservation\\u2014unless it\\u2019s under extenuating circumstances.\\n    \\n    Flagging inappropriate messages\\n        \\n        If a message from a guest makes you uncomfortable, let us know by flagging it. To flag a message, open the message thread and click the flag icon  next to the message you want to flag to Airbnb for review.\\n        \\n        \\n\\n        \\n \\n\\nRemember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What should I do if I'm uncomfortable hosting someone?"},
{"answer": "If your guest cancels their reservation, we\\u2019ll notify you and automatically unblock the dates on your calendar so that you can host other guests. Any payout for a canceled reservation will be released 24 hours after the originally scheduled check-in date. \\n\\nIf the reservation status hasn\\u2019t changed to Canceled in Your Reservations, it's still considered active, and will appear on your calendar. \\n\\nGuest refunds\\nGuests who cancel are automatically refunded according to your cancellation policy\\u2014unless the cancellation qualifies as an extenuating circumstance or a Guest Refund Policy case.\\nIf you\\u2019d like to offer your guest more money back, learn how to issue an additional refund. \\n\\nCancellations after check-in\\n\\nIf your guest cancels after they\\u2019ve already checked in:\\n\\nThey\\u2019re required to to leave your space as soon as they cancel\\nThe terms of your cancellation policy will still apply\\nYou must make any security deposit claims within 48 hours of the original checkout date, which you can check in your Transaction History\\n\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I refund my guest?\\nChange a reservation as a host\\nWhat if I can't get in touch with my guest?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What happens if my guest cancels?"},
{"answer": "You can still make changes or cancel a Special Offer as long as a guest hasn't accepted it.\\n\\nCancel a Special Offer\\n\\nTo cancel a Special Offer:\\n\\nGo to Your Messages on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message from the guest you sent a Special Offer to \\nClick Remove Special Offer within the message thread\\n\\n\\n\\nEdit a Special Offer\\n\\nTo edit a Special Offer:\\n\\nGo to Your Messages on airbnb.com\\nOpen the message from the guest you sent a Special Offer to \\nOn the left side of the page under Payment click Send special offer\\nIn the Subtotal field, enter the new price you\\u2019d like to offer your guest for their stay (be sure to include cleaning fee or your additional guest fee in this subtotal) \\nClick Send special offer\\n\\n\\nIf the guest has already booked your place, use the alterations tool to make changes to accepted reservations.", "question": "How do I edit or remove a Special Offer?"},
{"answer": "To add or edit a security deposit in your pricing settings:\\n    \\n      Go to Manage Listings on airbnb.com\\nSelect the listing you want to edit\\nSelect Pricing settings in the upper right-hand corner\\nUnder Additional Pricing Options, check the box next to Security deposit\\nEnter an amount between $95 and $5,100 USD\\n\\n\\n\\nThe security deposit only applies to reservations booked after the changes are made; they don't retroactively apply to existing reservations. Security deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How do I add a security deposit to my listing?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tTo submit a Host Guarantee payment request, read through the terms and conditions of the Host Guarantee (www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee), then contact your guest to notify them of your complaint\\u2014often hosts and guests resolve issues on their own via our Resolution Center.\\n\\t\\n\\tIf you and your guest aren't able to come to an agreement, update your case in the Resolution Center accordingly. Gather as much documentation as possible to submit to Airbnb, including photos, receipts, a police report, and any other documentation that proves ownership, damage, or estimates the fair market value of items damaged.\\n\\t\\n\\tIn the very rare occasion of malicious damages or damages involving any kind of illegal activity, please also file a police report with your local authorities. We'll ask you to provide Airbnb with an official copy of the report, so please be sure to ask for a paper copy for your records.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tYou must submit the request either 14 days from the guests check out or before the next guest checks in, whichever is earlier. For payment requests submitted on time, well send a confirmation email and follow-up emails to discuss next steps.\\n\\n\\tOnce we receive sufficient information from both the host and the guest, well review all documentation and evaluate the payment request. The length of the process will vary depending on the severity of the case, the quality of documentation, and the cooperation of the host and guest.\\n\\n\\n      \\n        \\n        Remember: In an emergency situation, or if your personal safety is threatened, contact local police or emergency services immediately.\\n        \\n      \\n", "question": "How do I submit a Host Guarantee payment request?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tThe Airbnb Host Guarantee provides protection for up to $1,000,000 to a host for damages to covered property in the rare event of guest damages above the security deposit\\u2014or if no security deposit is in place.\\n\\n\\tThe Host Guarantee Program doesn't cover cash and securities, collectibles, rare artwork, jewelry, pets or personal liability. We recommend that hosts secure or remove valuables when renting their place. The program also doesn't cover loss or damage to property due to wear and tear. For these types of incidents, hosts can add a security deposit in their pricing settings.\\n\\n\\tThe Host Guarantee Program isn't insurance and doesn't replace your homeowners or renters insurance. Make sure you review and understand the terms of your insurance policy and what it covers and doesn't cover. Not all insurance will cover damage or loss to property caused by a guest renting your space. Filing a host guarantee request doesn't preclude a guest from financial responsibility for the damages claimed if Airbnb determines a guest was at fault.\\n\\n\\tLearn more about the Host Guarantee at: www.airbnb.com/guarantee.\\n\\t\\n\\tView the Host Guarantee terms and conditions at: www.airbnb.com/terms/host_guarantee. If you can't view this page, the country you're accessing Airbnb from doesn't have Host Guarantee coverage right now.", "question": "What is the Airbnb Host Guarantee?"},
{"answer": "Our system only processes whole numbers, and all fees and totals are rounded to the nearest whole amount.\\n\\nService fees\\nService fees are calculated from the reservation subtotal, excluding any security deposit amount. The subtotal is the complete price of the reservation before service fees have been added. If you change your reservation, the service fees adjust according to the new subtotal.\\n\\n\\nGuest service fee \\nWe add a percentage-based service fee to guest payments every time a reservation is booked. This helps cover the cost of running our site and services.\\n\\nThe exact percentage depends on the subtotal of the reservation. The higher the subtotal, the lower the percentage so you can save money when booking large reservations. You'll see the exact amount in the price breakdown on the checkout page before you confirm and pay, and on your billing receipt.\\n\\nIf you cancel a reservation you booked as a guest, the service fee is non-refundable. If your reservation is canceled by the host and you choose to be refunded, the service fee is refunded in full.\\n\\nHost service fee \\nWe deduct a 3% service fee from host payouts every time a reservation is booked at their listing. This helps cover the cost of processing guest payments.\\n\\nYou can see the exact amount by clicking on the reservation code in your Transaction History from the desktop version of Airbnb.\\n\\nVAT \\nDepending on the country of residence of the host or guest, VAT on the service fees may be included as an additional amount over and above the total Airbnb service fee. Your guest or host service fee includes VAT, when applicable.\\n\\nConversion fee\\n\\nFor guests paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, a 3% currency conversion fee applies in addition to any system wide base exchange rate in effect.", "question": "What are the service fees?"},
{"answer": "\\nHosts can add a security deposit to their listing, as long as they add it before a reservation is booked.\\n\\nIf a host wants to make a claim on the security deposit, they must do so within 48 hours of the checkout date. If a claim is made, Airbnb will mediate and collect payment from the guest, as necessary. \\n \\n\\nSecurity deposits can't be handled off-site in cash, as off-site payments are a violation of our terms.", "question": "How does Airbnb handle security deposits?"},
{"answer": "\\nTo help cover the costs of processing guest payments, we charge hosts a 3% service fee every time a reservation is completed. The amount of this service fee is calculated from the reservation subtotal (before fees and taxes).\\n\\nWe also charge guests a guest service fee to cover the cost of running Airbnb.\\nFind the service fee\\n\\n\\tTo see the amount of the service fee:\\n\\t\\n\\t  Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com\\n\\t  Click on the reservation code next to the reservation you're interested in\\n\\t  Under Payout, you'll see Airbnb Service Fee\\n\\t\\n\\t You'll also  be able to view the service fee in the message thread with the guest under Payments\\nVAT charges on service fees\\nDepending on the laws of the jurisdiction involved, VAT may be charged on top of the service fee. The service fee will include these VAT charges when applicable.\\nNote: Accommodation fees are charged to the guest directly by the host and may contain local taxes (including VAT).", "question": "What are host service fees?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tAn adjustment is an amount of money a host owes as a result of a cancellation, reservation change, or violation of our Guest Refund Policy. \\n\\t\\n\\tTo check the status of an adjustment:\\n\\t\\n\\t  Go to your Account Settings\\n\\t  Click Transaction History\\n\\t\\n\\t\\n\\n\\tAdjustments are automatically deducted from the next scheduled payout or payouts until the full amount is collected.", "question": "What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tTo print individual receipts for a reservation:\\n\\t\\n\\t  Go to Your Reservations on airbnb.com\\n\\t  Click Print Confirmation to view the details of a reservation\\n\\t\\n\\t\\nTo see all of your payouts and transaction details in a CSV file: \\n\\n  Go to your Transaction History on airbnb.com\\n  Click Export to CSV to download the file\\n", "question": "How do I access receipts and payout details for completed reservations?"},
{"answer": "\\nYou can check the status of your payouts and view detailed information on your earnings at any time from your Transaction History.\\n\\n\\nYou can filter transactions by payout method, listing, and date. View details of your payouts by clicking on the reservation code.\\n\\nCompleted payouts\\n\\n\\nTo see payouts that have been released by Airbnb, view Completed Transactions. We release payouts to hosts 24 hours after a guest checks in, but the time it takes to receive a payout after it\\u2019s released depends on the payout method you\\u2019ve selected.\\n\\n\\nWhen we release a payout to you, it appears as a line item with the type \"Reservation.\" Once the payout is processed, a \\u201cPayout\\u201d line appears. Hovering over the question mark next to the date of a payout will tell you when you can expect to see the funds in your account.\\n\\n\\nIf you have multiple listings with reservations that begin on the same day, any payouts going to the same payout method will display as paid out together. Adjustments or any other fees are displayed separately.\\n\\nUpcoming payouts\\n\\n\\nTo see your upcoming scheduled payouts, view Future Transactions. Before a payout is released, it will display as a \"Reservation\" with the date \"Pending\". If the payout is still pending, you can change your payout method for a particular reservation using the drop-down menu. Adjustments or any other fees are displayed separately.\\n\\nGross earnings\\n\\n\\nFor each reservation, the gross amount is the price agreed upon before Airbnb service fees and any taxes being collected on your behalf. Gross Earnings displays the total amount you've earned, which includes the 3% host fees. Earnings will appear in this tab after the payout for that reservation has been released.\\n\\nExporting to a spreadsheet\\n\\nYou can click Export to CSV to download a .csv file of your transactions from any tab. The CSV file can be opened by any standard spreadsheet program (like Microsoft Excel, Google Docs, or Apple Numbers) to give you a display of the data. This spreadsheet includes additional information, including host service fees paid and cleaning fees (if you charge one).\\n\\n\\n\\n  Related articles\\n\\n  \\n    \\n     When do I get paid?\\n     What does an adjustment on my transaction history mean?\\n    \\n  \\n", "question": "Where do I find information about my payouts?"},
{"answer": "For long-term reservations, payments are collected and released in monthly installments. \\n\\nWe charge your guest the first month upfront and release that first payment to you 24 hours after their check-in date. Future payments are released to your payout method on a monthly basis for the duration of the reservation. \\n\\nYou can check the status of the monthly payouts in your Transaction History. The reservation code and guest name is recorded on each payout line in both Future Transactions and Completed Transactions. \\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nWhere do I find information about my payouts?\\nLong-term Cancellation Policy\\nCan a guest alter or cancel a long-term reservation?\\nHow do I set prices for long-term stays?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "When do I get paid for a long-term reservation?"},
{"answer": "Airbnb\\u2019s payment system is designed to make transferring money between guests and hosts as simple and reliable as possible. Here\\u2019s how it works:\\n\\n  Guests pay Airbnb when they book a place\\n  Airbnb releases the money to hosts 24 hours after the guest checks in\\n\\nUsing Airbnb\\u2019s payment system is required to make a reservation, and it helps ensure that both parties are protected under our Terms of Service, cancellation policies, Guest Refund Policy, and other safeguards.\\n\\nAirbnb automatically includes service fees in each transaction, and some government-required taxes where applicable.\\n\\n\\nRelated topics for guests:\\n\\nPrices &amp; Fees\\nPayment Methods\\n\\nRelated topics for hosts:\\n\\nHow Payouts Work\\nPayout Preferences\\n", "question": "How does Airbnb process payments?"},
{"answer": "\\n    Airbnb releases your payout about 24 hours after your guest\\u2019s scheduled check-in time. The time it takes for the funds to arrive in your account depends on your payout method.\\n    \\nIf your guest is staying for longer than 29 nights, payouts for that reservation are released monthly.\\n\\nPayout status\\n\\nTo check the status of your payout, visit your Transaction History. Once we\\u2019ve sent your payout, a \\u201cPayout\\u201d line item appears for that reservation.\\n\\nIf you have a minimum payout amount set, your payout won\\u2019t be released until that amount is met. If you have multiple listings with check-ins on the same day, any funds going to the same payout method will be deposited as a single payout.\\n\\nProcessing time\\n\\nAfter Airbnb releases the payout, it takes some additional time for the money to get to you.\\n\\n The average processing time for each payout method is:\\n\\nACH / Direct deposit: Up to 3 business days\\nBank transfer or international wire: 3\\u20137 business days\\nPayPal: Within 1 business day\\nWestern Union: 1 business day (US Pacific Time)\\nPayoneer Prepaid Debit Card: Within 1 business day\\n\\n\\nWeekend or holiday delays\\n\\n  Many banking systems don't process transactions on weekends or holidays. If your payout from Airbnb is completed between Friday and Sunday, it might not be processed until the next week.\\n\\n  If you have any questions about processing time after your Airbnb transaction history shows a payout as completed, contact your payment processor directly.", "question": "When do I get paid?"},
{"answer": "The payout you\\u2019ll receive is your nightly rate minus the 3% host service fee. To view information about any of your payouts, visit your Transaction History.\\nGuests pay a 6-12% service fee to Airbnb in addition to the cost of your listing, which is why the total price guests see is higher than your payout. \\nHere are some things that can impact your payout:\\n\\nYour weekly discount or monthly discount may have been applied to the reservation \\nWeekend pricing or custom pricing may have been applied to the reservation\\nThe Airbnb payment system rounds to the nearest whole amount\\nWhere applicable, Value-added tax (VAT) may be added on top of the Airbnb service fee\\n\\nIf you receive a booking inquiry, but want to charge a different price, you can send the guest a Special Offer.\\nIf you want to change the price of an accepted reservation, you\\u2019ll need to submit a request to your guest.\\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I set prices for long-term stays?\\nHow do I set up weekend pricing?\\nHow do I set custom or seasonal pricing?\\nWhat is VAT and how does it apply to me?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I calculate my payout?"},
{"answer": "If you\\u2019ve added more than one payout method, you can specify a default or add payout routing rule.\\n\\nYour default payout method is noted next to your payout method type. To choose a different payout method as your default, first add the new payout method, then click Options and select Make Default. To remove a payout method (and any settings associated with that payout method), click  Options and select  Remove Payout Method.\\n\\nPayout routing rules let you split your payouts among different payout methods or set a different payout method for each listing in your account.\\n\\nTo add a payout routing rule:\\n\\nGo to Account on airbnb.com\\nSelect Payout Preferences on the left\\nClick Add Payout Routing Rule. When you add a new payout routing rule, it won\\u2019t affect reservations that have already begun\\u2014only payouts for reservations that begin after the change will be affected.\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Managing more than one payout method"},
{"answer": "Social Connections shows you how you're connected to others, either directly or through mutual friends, depending on your Facebook privacy settings. It also highlights your Airbnb activity, which may include your username, Facebook profile photo, and recent locations you visited to your Facebook friends who are also on Airbnb.\\n  \\n  Turn Social Connections on  \\n    To turn Social Connections on:\\n    \\n  \\n        Go to Profile on airbnb.com\\n        Select Trust and Verification on the left\\n        Next to Facebook, click Connect\\n      \\n      \\n   Turn Social Connections off  \\n      \\tTo turn Social Connections off:\\n      \\t\\n      \\t  Go to Privacy on airbnb.com\\n      \\t  Uncheck the box next to Share my activity with my Facebook friends that are also on Airbnb\\n      \\t  Click Save Social Connections\\n      \\t\\n      \\n  \\n\\n\\tIf you turn Social Connections off, your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook, but your Airbnb activity won't be shared with your Facebook friends on Airbnb. Your public Airbnb activity, such as Wish Lists you've created or reviews you've written, will still be shown to other people on Airbnb.\\n\\n\\tIf you've enabled Social Connections but don't see any connections, it might be that your Facebook friends aren't active yet on Airbnb. Refer them to earn travel credits.", "question": "What is the Social Connections feature?"},
{"answer": "To connect your Airbnb and Facebook accounts:\\n    \\n      Go to Profile on airbnb.com\\n      Select Trust and Verification on the left\\n      Under Add More Verifications, find Facebook and click Connect\\n    \\n\\nTo disconnect your accounts, follow the steps above to get to Trust and Verification, then under Your Current Verifications, find Facebook and click Disconnect.\\n\\n    \\n\\n\\n  Connecting your Airbnb and Facebook accounts helps personalize your Airbnb experience. Based on your Facebook privacy settings, you'll be able to filter searches by Social Connections to show listings that your friends have reviewed, or where you have mutual friends with a host.\\n  \\n  Connecting with Facebook also adds the Online ID verification to your profile, and can help fill out other sections like School and Work. You can edit your profile at any time to modify or remove this information. You'll still keep the Online ID verification.", "question": "How do I connect my Facebook and Airbnb accounts?"},
{"answer": "\\nNo. The currency you pay in is controlled by your payment method and, in some cases, by your country. It\\u2019s not possible to manually choose what currency you'll use to pay.\\n\\nWhen you select your country and payment method on the checkout page, the currency in which you'd be charged will be clearly displayed before you confirm your reservation request.\\n\\nExchange rates and currency conversion\\n\\n\\nWhen the currency you\\u2019re paying with is different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we convert your payment automatically.\\n\\nThe base exchange rate uses data from one or more third parties, such as OANDA. It\\u2019s updated regularly, but may not be identical to the real-time market rate. If you\\u2019re paying in a currency different from the default currency of the country where the listing is located, we also charge a 3% conversion fee on your total cost; the conversion fee accounts for Airbnb\\u2019s holding costs and foreign currency risks.\\n\\nThe exchange rate used will display on the checkout page before you confirm your booking.\\n\\nThird-party fees\\n\\n\\nIf you pay in a currency that\\u2019s different from the designated currency of your payment method, your provider or third-party payment processor may apply a currency conversion rate or fees to your payment. Contact your provider (for example, your credit or bank card issuer) for information on what fees may apply, since they\\u2019re not controlled by Airbnb.\\n\\nCurrency view\\n\\nYou can view Airbnb listings in many currencies, but this won\\u2019t affect what currency you\\u2019ll be asked to pay in. To change your currency view, scroll to the bottom of any page on airbnb.com and click on the currency field to select what currency you want to view listing prices in.", "question": "Can I pay with any currency?"},
{"answer": "Text message (SMS) notifications\\n    \\n\\t    We can let you know when you have new Airbnb messages, reservation requests, and more via text message (SMS) alerts. These notifications may be sent at any time, based on your notification settings.\\n\\t  \\n\\t    \\n\\t      To turn text message notifications on or off and manage the types of mobile notifications you receive, visit the notifications menu in your account settings.\\n\\nIn the Airbnb app on your phone or tablet:\\n\\nIn the Airbnb app, tap the profile icon .\\nTap Settings &gt; Notifications.\\nManage your notifications.\\n\\nOn the web:\\n\\t  \\n\\t      Click your name in the top-right corner of airbnb.com.\\n\\t      Select Account.\\n\\t      Click Notifications in the menu on the left side of your screen.\\n\\t      Look for the Mobile Notifications / Text Messages pane. You can manage your settings here.\\n\\t   \\n    \\n      When you opt in to text message (SMS) notifications, we'll send you a text to confirm your signup.\\n      \\n    \\n      We only support sending SMS on carriers in North America and Europe. Standard message and data rates may apply for any messages sent or received, so it's best to contact your wireless provider to confirm. Participating carriers: AT&amp;T, CBW, nTelos, Sprint, Nextel, Boost, Virgin Mobile, Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, and Alltel.\\n\\tPush notifications\\n\\t\\n\\t      If you use Airbnb's mobile app, we can also send push notifications straight to your smart phone. You can enable them from the app's Settings menu.      \\n\\t  \\n\\t\\n\\t\\t", "question": "How do text message and push notifications work?"},
{"answer": "If you didn\\u2019t receive an email notification from us, there are a few different steps you can try to figure out the issue.\\nMake sure your email address is correct\\n\\n\\nWe might be sending emails to an old or incorrect email address. To check the email being used:\\n\\nGo to Edit Profile.\\nLook for the Email Address field. Make sure your address is correct.\\nIf it\\u2019s incorrect, add the correct address, scroll to the bottom of the page, and click Save.\\n\\nCheck your email notification settings\\n\\n\\n\\nWe'll only send the emails you tell us you want. Check your notification settings to make sure you haven't opted out of the email type you're looking for:\\n\\nGo to your Notification Settings.\\nLook for the \"Email Settings\" field. Make sure you\\u2019ve chosen the email types you want to receive.\\nAfter adding or removing checkmarks from the right boxes, scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save.\\n\\nSearch all messages in your email inbox\\nSometimes emails can get lost in your inbox. In your email account, search for terms like \"Airbnb\", \"reservation\", \"verification\", or other words related to the email you're looking for.\\nCheck your spam and other email filters\\nIt's possible your email provider mistakenly sent our messages to your spam or junk folder. To avoid this:\\n\\nRemove Airbnb messages from your spam list\\nAdd automated@airbnb.com, express@airbnb.com, and response@airbnb.com to your personal email address book\\n\\nIf you have other filters or routing rules in your email account that may have sorted Airbnb emails elsewhere, be sure to check those, too.\\nCheck for issues with your email service provider\\nDepending on your provider, emails can take up to a few hours to be delivered. If undelivered or delayed emails continue to be an issue, check with your provider to see if there are any configuration issues or problems with their network that might be affecting your account.", "question": "Why didn't I receive my email notification?"},
{"answer": "Login notifications are an extra security feature that can help alert you if someone accesses your Airbnb account without your permission. \\n\\n    When you turn on login notifications, we\\u2019ll send you an email each time someone logs ins. In these emails, we\\u2019ll give you information on the type of Internet browser used to access your account, the time your account was accessed, and where we believe it was accessed from. \\n\\n        To turn login notifications on:\\n  \\n      \\n        Go to Account\\n        Select Security on the left\\n        Look for Login Notifications and click the check box next to Enable login notifications\\n        Click Save\\n      \\n\\nIf you use certain browsers often, you can mark them as trusted. We won\\u2019t notify you when your account is accessed from a trusted browser.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nWhat is a trusted browser?\\nMy account details changed, but I didn\\u2019t update them. What should I do?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What are login notifications?"},
{"answer": "If you've forgotten your password or are having trouble logging in to your Airbnb account, visit: www.airbnb.com/forgot_password.\\n\\t\\n\\tEnter the email address you use for Airbnb, and you'll be emailed a link to reset your password.\\n\\t\\n\\tI want to update my password\\n\\nIf you know your current password, but you want to change it:\\n\\n\\t\\n\\t  Go to Account on airbnb.com\\n\\t  Select Security on the left.\\n\\t  Under Change Your Password enter your password and follow the instructions on screen\\n\\t\\n\\nI use Facebook to log in, but I want to create an Airbnb password\\n\\tIf you created an Airbnb account by connecting to Facebook, you weren't required to create a password.\\n\\tYou can continue to log in via Facebook, or if you'd like to create an Airbnb password, first log out of your Airbnb account, then follow the steps as if you forgot your password. Once you create an Airbnb password, you'll no longer be able to sign in using Facebook, but your Airbnb account will still be connected to Facebook.", "question": "How do I reset my password?"},
{"answer": "If you turn on login notifications, you can mark the browser you use to access your Airbnb account often as trusted\\u2014when you use a trusted browser to access your account, we won\\u2019t notify you.\\n\\n    To mark a browser as trusted: \\n      \\n        Enable login notifications.\\n        Log in to your Airbnb account from the browser you want to trust.\\n        You\\u2019ll see a Add to trusted browsers? window appear. Select the option next to Trust this browser.\\n        Click Save.\\n      \\n\\nYou should only mark a browser as trusted if you're on a private computer or phone.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nWhat are login notifications?\\nMy account details changed, but I didn\\u2019t update them. What should I do?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is a trusted browser?"},
{"answer": "To change the email address you use for your Airbnb account:\\n\\n  Go to Profile on airbnb.com\\n\\tNext to Email Address, enter the email address you want to use\\n\\tScroll to the bottom of the page and click Save\\n\\nYour email address can only be associated with one Airbnb account at a time. If you get a notification that your email address is already in use but you can't remember your password for that account, you can reset your password.", "question": "How do I change the email address I use for Airbnb?"},
{"answer": "\\n            Hosts and guests can receive public references from friends, family members, and colleagues to help build their profile. References help people throughout the Airbnb community get to know you, and feel more comfortable booking a reservation with you.\\n        \\n            You need an Airbnb account to request and write references, and references will only display on the recipient\\u2019s profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo.\\n        \\n            To request a reference:\\n        \\n                \\n                    \\n                        Go to Profile on airbnb.com\\n                    \\n                    \\n                        Select References on the left\\n                    \\n                    \\n                        Use the Request References section to send emails to the people you want to get a reference from\\n                \\n\\n        \\n            In the References About You section, you'll see references that you\\u2019ve received. You have to approve each reference before it will appear on your profile.\\n        \\n            In the References By You section, you\\u2019ll see reference requests you\\u2019ve received. The only way you can write a reference for someone else in the Airbnb community is in response to a reference request\\u2014you can\\u2019t proactively leave a reference for someone.\\n        \\n            References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip.", "question": "How do references work?"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are experienced hosts who provide a shining example for other hosts, and extraordinary experiences for their guests.\\n\\nOnce a host reaches Superhost status, a badge will automatically appear on their listing and profile to help you identify them.\\n\\n\\n\\nWe check Superhosts\\u2019 activity four times a year, to ensure that the program highlights the people who are most dedicated to providing outstanding hospitality.\\n\\nThe Superhost Terms &amp; Conditions apply. Airbnb doesn't endorse or sponsor any host, including Superhosts, or their listings.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\n  How do I become a Superhost?\\n  What benefits do Superhosts receive?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What is a Superhost?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tAfter you receive a reference from another member of the Airbnb community, you'll need to approve it before it will appear on your profile. You'll receive an email and an alert on your Dashboard when you receive a reference. You can also go directly to the reference:\\n\\n  \\tGo to Profile on airbnb.com\\t\\t\\n  \\tSelect References on the left\\n\\nReferences will only display on your profile if the author of the reference has a profile photo.\\n\\nNote: References are different from reviews, which hosts and guests write after a completed trip, and referrals, which let you earn credit for inviting people to Airbnb.", "question": "Why isn't a reference appearing on my profile?"},
{"answer": "\\n    Inviting people to Airbnb can earn you\\u2014and the people you invite\\u2014travel credit to use toward a new reservation.\\n    Invite friends to use Airbnb\\n    \\n               To begin earning credit, visit the invitation page and send the link to your friends. When a friend clicks the link, they will receive credit that will automatically apply towards their first reservation with Airbnb. The credit will show up automatically on the checkout page of any qualifying reservation.\\n            \\n        \\n        \\nWhen your friend completes their first qualifying reservation, you'll earn travel credit to use for your own Airbnb reservations. You'll receive your travel credit after the departure date of your friend's trip.\\nFor each person you refer, there are two opportunities to earn travel credit. You earn credit when your friend completes a qualifying reservation as a guest and also when they complete a qualifying reservation as a host. You can earn up to $5,000 USD in travel credit overall.\\n     \\n                To see all of your current referral details, click Invite Friends on your Airbnb Dashboard. Terms apply.\\n        Qualifying reservations\\n        A qualifying reservation usually has a total value of $75 USD or more, excluding guest fees and any taxes. These amounts may vary during promotional periods.\\n        Use your travel credit\\n        Your available travel credits automatically appear as a coupon on the checkout page of your reservation request. If the travel credits aren't automatically added, it means the reservation doesn\\u2019t qualify.\\n        Travel credits can't apply to a trip that has already been paid for, but they will be available and applied to your next qualifying reservation. They expire one year from the date they're issued and can only be used once. They\\u2019re also not reusable if you cancel a reservation where the credits were applied.", "question": "How do referrals and travel credits work?"},
{"answer": "\\nThe Superhost section of your dashboard helps you track your progress toward becoming a Superhost\\u2014a host who receives a badge and other benefits for providing outstanding hospitality.  \\n\\nThe Superhost section of your dashboard shows:\\nThe number of trips you\\u2019ve hosted\\nYour response rate over the last year\\nThe % of 5-star primary reviews you've received\\nThe number of confirmed reservations that you\\u2019ve canceled \\n\\nYour dashboard automatically reflects your activity from the past year, but in some instances it may take a day or two for your dashboard to reflect your most recent trips. It also tells you when the next Superhost assessment date will be. \\n\\n  If you meet the program requirements on the assessment date, you'll qualify for Superhost status. Keep in mind that you\\u2019ll need to continue to meet the program qualifications to maintain your Superhost status on the next assessment date.\\n", "question": "What\\u2019s the Superhost section of my dashboard?"},
{"answer": "If you earn Superhost status, potential guests will see a Superhost badge on your host profile and each of your listings.\\n\\n\\n\\nOther benefits\\n    Superhosts are also rewarded with:\\n\\n\\n    Priority support: You\\u2019ll receive priority phone support whenever you call Airbnb or tweet @AirbnbHelp.\\n    Search filter: A Superhost search filter lets guests search only for recognized hosts like you.\\n    Travel coupon: If you maintain your Superhost status for a full year (4 evaluation periods) and have an active listing on the day that marks the 1 year anniversary of your Superhost status, you\\u2019ll receive a $100 travel coupon to use towards your own Airbnb trip. Learn how to apply this coupon.\\n    Product exclusives: You'll be invited to preview upcoming releases and attend exclusive events.\\n\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\n  What is a Superhost?\\n  How do I become a Superhost?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "What benefits do Superhosts receive?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tTo record a profile video using your webcam:\\n\\n  Go to Profile on airbnb.com\\n\\tSelect Photos, Symbol, and Video on the left\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tClick Record a new video and follow the instructions\\n\\n\\n\\tYou can use a profile video to express yourself to the Airbnb community and make a great first impression. We recommend you start with your first name and where you\\u2019re from, and then let us know your interests, a fun fact about yourself, or why you love Airbnb.\\n\\n\\tAt this time, we don't support uploading saved videos from your computer, or uploading videos to your listing's page.", "question": "How do I make a profile video?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tYour profile is a great way for others to learn more about you before they book your space or host you. When your profile is robust, it helps others feel that you're reliable, authentic, and committed to the spirit of Airbnb. Whether you're a host or a guest, the more complete your profile is, the more reservations you're likely to book, too.\\n\\n\\tWe require all hosts to have a profile photo, and we require all guests to upload a profile photo before making their first reservation. \\n\\n\\n  A great profile includes:\\n\\n\\tAt least one profile photo\\n\\tMultiple verifications and a Verified ID\\n\\tA description of at least 50 words highlighting why you decided to join the Airbnb community, your interests or hobbies, or anything else you think someone would want to know\\n\\n\\tTo view someone's profile, just click their profile photo.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I edit my profile or profile photo?\\n\\nWhat is Verified ID?\\nWhat are profile verifications and how do I get them?\\n\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Why do I need to have an Airbnb profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "\\n  \\nYou can edit information that appears on your Airbnb profile, such as your main profile photo or email address. If you\\u2019re a host looking to make changes to your listing profile, learn how to edit your listing.\\n\\n\\n\\tTo edit your profile information:\\n\\n  \\n\\tGo to Edit Profile on airbnb.com.\\n\\t\\n\\t\\tUse the menu on the left to choose different sections of your profile to edit.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\tThe different sections of your profile include:\\n\\t\\n\\n\\tEdit Profile: Update the basics about who you are and where you live, including the phone number and email address you\\u2019ll share when you have a confirmed reservation. Click Save at the bottom of the page to save your changes. \\n\\n\\tPhotos, Symbol, and Video: Upload a photo from your computer, or take one with your webcam. A photo that clearly shows your face is needed before booking or hosting a reservation.\\n\\t\\n\\n\\tTrust and Verification: Add verifications to complete your Verified ID, which is required by some hosts.\\n\\n\\n\\tReviews: After you complete a reservation, write and read reviews that have been left for you.\\n\\n\\tReferences: To build trust in the community, you can request friends, family members, and colleagues to post a reference on your profile explaining why you're a great host or guest.\\n\\t\\n\\n\\tTo see what your profile looks like to others, you can also click View Profile. \\n\\t\\n\\t  \\n\\nRelated articles\\n \\n\\nHow do I complete my Airbnb account?\\nHow do I edit my listing as a host?\\nWhat is Verified ID?\\nHow do I cancel my account?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "How do I edit my profile or profile photo?"},
{"answer": "If you didn\\u2019t receive an email notification from us, there are a few different steps you can try to figure out the issue.\\nMake sure your email address is correct\\n\\n\\nWe might be sending emails to an old or incorrect email address. To check the email being used:\\n\\nGo to Edit Profile.\\nLook for the Email Address field. Make sure your address is correct.\\nIf it\\u2019s incorrect, add the correct address, scroll to the bottom of the page, and click Save.\\n\\nCheck your email notification settings\\n\\n\\n\\nWe'll only send the emails you tell us you want. Check your notification settings to make sure you haven't opted out of the email type you're looking for:\\n\\nGo to your Notification Settings.\\nLook for the \"Email Settings\" field. Make sure you\\u2019ve chosen the email types you want to receive.\\nAfter adding or removing checkmarks from the right boxes, scroll to the bottom of the page and click Save.\\n\\nSearch all messages in your email inbox\\nSometimes emails can get lost in your inbox. In your email account, search for terms like \"Airbnb\", \"reservation\", \"verification\", or other words related to the email you're looking for.\\nCheck your spam and other email filters\\nIt's possible your email provider mistakenly sent our messages to your spam or junk folder. To avoid this:\\n\\nRemove Airbnb messages from your spam list\\nAdd automated@airbnb.com, express@airbnb.com, and response@airbnb.com to your personal email address book\\n\\nIf you have other filters or routing rules in your email account that may have sorted Airbnb emails elsewhere, be sure to check those, too.\\nCheck for issues with your email service provider\\nDepending on your provider, emails can take up to a few hours to be delivered. If undelivered or delayed emails continue to be an issue, check with your provider to see if there are any configuration issues or problems with their network that might be affecting your account.", "question": "Why didn't I receive my email notification?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\tThe information you provide Airbnb during the Verified ID process is governed by our Privacy Policy and transmitted using SSL\\u2014the same secure encryption that websites use to transmit credit card numbers.\\n\\n\\tWhen we receive information from your driver\\u2019s license or passport, we store the number in an encrypted form, so you should only have to verify your ID once. For countries with knowledge-based authentication, we don't store the questions or your answers.\\n\\n\\tOnly a small number of authorized Airbnb employees are allowed access to your original documentation for troubleshooting or internal purposes.\\n\\n\\tOur third-party partners store information from the Verified ID process according to our written instructions and under our\\xa0Privacy Policy.", "question": "Is verifying my ID secure?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\nTo verify your phone number:\\n\\n\\n  Go to Profile on airbnb.com.\\n  Next to Phone Number, click Add a phone number.\\n  Use the drop-down menu to select your country, and we\\u2019ll automatically insert the right country code.\\n  Enter your area code and phone number.\\n  Click Verify via SMS or Verify via Call. We'll send you a 4-digit code via text message (SMS) or an automated phone call.\\n  Enter your code and click Verify\\n\\n\\nIf you don\\u2019t see a confirmation message, try refreshing the page. If the method you chose isn't working, try the other one.\\n\\n\\n\\nAfter verifying your phone number, you can manage text message notifications by going to Account and choosing Notifications on the left. As always, standard message and data rates may apply for any calls or messages sent or received. For questions about these rates, get in touch with your phone provider.\\n\\n\\n\\n\\nWhy verify?\\nHaving a verified phone number gives your hosts, guests, and Airbnb a way to contact you about your reservations or your account. Hosts are required to verify their phone numbers before listing their homes, and guests must have a verified phone number before booking a reservation. You also need a verified phone number to complete Verified ID.", "question": "How do I verify my phone number?"},
{"answer": "\\n\\n    We created the Verified ID process to build trust in our community and help give you more information when you're deciding who to host or stay with.\\n      \\n      How Verified ID works\\n        Verified ID connects your Airbnb profile with other information about you. As part of Verified ID, you might be asked to:\\n          \\n          \\n            Take a photo or upload an image of your government-issued ID, such as your driver's license or passport\\n            Depending on where you live, you may have the option of answering a few questions about yourself instead\\n            Connect another online profile to your Airbnb account, such as a Facebook, Google, or LinkedIn account\\n            Upload an Airbnb profile photo and provide a phone number and email address\\n            \\n        Visit airbnb.com/verify to get started at any time.\\n      When you'll need to complete it\\n        Under certain circumstances, you might be required to complete Verified ID. For example, hosts can require that guests complete Verified ID before booking their place.\\n        \\n        If your host requires you to complete Verified ID, you'll be directed to complete the process right after you send your reservation request, and will have 12 hours to complete it. If you need to come back later, go to airbnb.com/verify and pick up where you left off.\\n        \\n        \\n        The Verified ID badge\\n      \\n      When you complete Verified ID, you'll earn a badge on your profile. Many hosts and guests look for this badge when deciding whether to host or stay with someone\\u2014but it's not an endorsement or guarantee of someone's identity.\\n      \\n            Privacy and encryption\\n        We take privacy seriously. The information you provide during this process is encrypted and governed by our Privacy Policy.\\n            \\n        We won't share the government ID or personal details you provide during Verified ID with your host or guest\\u2014they'll only know that you\\u2019ve successfully completed the process. And we\\u2019ll never post to your Facebook, Google, LinkedIn, or other connected accounts without your permission.\\n        \\n        Other ways your ID info is used\\n\\n    Where permitted by applicable law, we may also provide information from your government ID, such as your full name and date of birth, to our service providers to run checks against public records for criminal convictions and sex offender registrations. For now, these checks are limited to users in the United States about whom we have adequate identifying information, such as the user\\u2019s full name and date of birth. While we believe these checks help us deter fraud and misuse of our services, they don\\u2019t guarantee that interactions with people who book through Airbnb will be safe or problem-free. Please carefully review our notice about the limitations of background and registered sex offender checks.\\n            \\n    \\n    \\n", "question": "What is Verified ID?"},
{"answer": "\\nTo become a Superhost, you need to have an account in good standing, and over the past year you must have:\\n  \\n    Hosted at least 10 trips\\n    Maintained a 90% response rate or higher\\n    Received a 5-star review at least 80% of the time you\\u2019ve been reviewed, as long as at least half of the guests who stayed with you left a review\\n    Completed each of your confirmed reservations without canceling \\n  \\n\\n\\n  You don\\u2019t need to apply to become a Superhost. If you meet the program requirements on the assessment date, you'll qualify for Superhost status. We\\u2019ll notify you of your Superhost status at the end of each assessment period\\u2014usually 10 days after the assessment begins.\\n \\n  You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.\\n  \\nMeasuring your activity\\n\\n  The Superhost requirements are measured every 3 months, and are based on your activity over the past year. The assessment dates are the first of the month in January, April, July, and October. If you meet the program requirements on the assessment date, you'll qualify for Superhost status, though it may take a couple days for your Superhost badge to appear on your listing. This process is automated, which means we can't update your status in between assessment dates.\\n  Keep in mind that you\\u2019ll need to continue to meet the program qualifications to maintain your Superhost status on the next assessment date.\\n\\nSuperhost response rate\\nIn your progress toward receiving Superhost status, we look at your response rate for a longer period of time than the one we use to calculate the response rate that appears on your listing, where guests can see it. \\n\\nOn your listing, your response rate is based on the responses you send within 24 hours to the reservation requests and booking inquiries you\\u2019ve received in the past 30 days. The response rate in the Superhost section of your dashboard is based on the responses you send within 24 hours to the reservation requests and booking inquiries you've received in the past 365 days. We use a longer period of time to determine your Superhost status, because having it should reflect a year-round commitment to providing outstanding hospitality. \\n\\nStar reviews\\n\\n  The requirement that you receive a 5-star review at least 80% of the time is based on the primary reviews you\\u2019ve received from guests, not the individual category reviews that you see directly above the written reviews on your listing page.\\n\\n\\n  Keep in mind the number of stars you see at the top of your listing page is rounded to the nearest half of a star, and it\\u2019s a cumulative average of the primary reviews you\\u2019ve received since you started hosting. Those stars don\\u2019t represent the percentage of 5-star reviews you\\u2019ve received in the past year\\u2014the only place to find the percentage is in the Superhost section of your dashboard. \\n\\n\\n  If you\\u2019ve received 5-star reviews 80% of the time or more, but fewer than half of your guests have left you a review, you won't receive Superhost status.\\n\\nExtenuating circumstances\\n\\n  Cancellations you make under extenuating circumstances won\\u2019t count against your Superhost status, but all other cancellations will. We can't mark previous cancellations as \"made under extenuating circumstances,\" unless they're reported to us within two weeks of the cancellation. \\n\\nSuperhost Terms &amp; Conditions\\n  Airbnb doesn't endorse or sponsor any host, including Superhosts, or their listings.", "question": "How do I become a Superhost?"},
{"answer": "Profile verifications are a way to connect your Airbnb profile to other information about you, such as your Facebook profile, phone number, email address, or photo ID.\\n  \\n  Adding verifications\\n    \\n  To add verifications to your account:\\n    \\n    Go to Profile on airbnb.com\\n    Tap Trust and Verification\\n    Under Add More Verifications choose a verification to add\\n    \\n  \\n  Certain verifications like reviews and professional photography can't be added from this page.\\n    \\n    Available verifications\\n    \\n        Available verifications include:\\n    \\n        Email address: Confirm that you receive email notifications and messages\\n        Phone number: We'll share your verified phone number with your host or guest once a reservation is accepted\\n        Online ID: Connect your Airbnb profile to Google, Facebook, LinkedIn, Verify with Amex, or by having pre-existing reviews\\n        Reviews: Build a reputation in the Airbnb community from your Reviews tab after completing reservations\\n        Verified photos: We offer free professional photography in many cities\\n    \\n  Verified ID\\n    You may also want to get a Verified ID badge. To get a Verified ID badge, go to the Trust and Verification area of your profile and click the Verify Me button or visit our Verified ID page.", "question": "What are profile verifications and how do I get them?"},
{"answer": "\\n  The Superhost requirements are measured every 3 months, and are based on your activity over the past year. You can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.\\n  \\nMeasuring your activity\\n  \\n  The assessment dates are the first of the month in January, April, July, and October. If you meet the Superhost program requirements on the assessment date, you'll qualify for Superhost status, though it may take a couple days for your Superhost badge to appear on your listing. This process is automated, which means we can't update your status in between assessment dates.\\n  Keep in mind that you\\u2019ll need to continue to meet the program qualifications to maintain your Superhost status on the next assessment date.\\n\\nSuperhost response rate\\nIn your progress toward receiving Superhost status, we look at your response rate for a longer period of time than the one we use to calculate the response rate that appears on your listing, where guests can see it. \\n\\nOn your listing, your response rate is based on the responses you send within 24 hours to the reservation requests and booking inquiries you\\u2019ve received in the past 30 days. The response rate in the Superhost section of your dashboard is based on the responses you send within 24 hours to the reservation requests and booking inquiries you've received in the past 365 days. We use a longer period of time to determine your Superhost status, because having it should reflect a year-round commitment to providing outstanding hospitality. \\n\\nStar reviews\\n\\n  The requirement that you receive a 5-star review at least 80% of the time is based on the primary reviews you\\u2019ve received from guests, not the individual category reviews that you see directly above the written reviews on your listing page.\\n\\n\\n  Keep in mind the number of stars you see at the top of your listing page is rounded to the nearest half of a star, and it\\u2019s a cumulative average of the primary reviews you\\u2019ve received since you started hosting. Those stars don\\u2019t represent the percentage of 5-star reviews you\\u2019ve received in the past year\\u2014the only place to find the percentage is in the Superhost section of your dashboard. \\n\\n\\n  If you\\u2019ve received 5-star reviews 80% of the time or more, but fewer than half of your guests have left you a review, you won't receive Superhost status.\\n\\nExtenuating circumstances\\n\\n  Cancellations you make under extenuating circumstances won\\u2019t count against your Superhost status, but all other cancellations will. We can't mark previous cancellations as \"made under extenuating circumstances,\" unless they're reported to us within two weeks of the cancellation. \\n\\nSuperhost Terms &amp; Conditions\\n  Airbnb doesn't endorse or sponsor any host, including Superhosts, or their listings.", "question": "Tracking your Superhost status"},
{"answer": "Superhosts are evaluated 4 times a year. During each assessment period, hosts can gain, keep, or lose their Superhost status based on their activity within the last year. \\n\\nTo keep your Superhost status, you must continue to meet the Superhost requirements during each assessment period. \\n\\nYou can track your progress in the Superhost section of your dashboard.\\n\\n\\nRelated Articles\\n \\n\\n  What is a Superhost?\\n  How do I become a Superhost?\\n\\n  \\n", "question": "Can I lose my Superhost status?"}]